Is there someone you want to kill?
Everyone has several people
around them
whom they hate, or want to punch,
or want them to disappear.
Among those people,
there must be at least one
you would even want dead,
or to kill, if possible.
For example...
No, it is your fault.
The document you prepared
was inadequate,
that's why the client is angry.
Yes.
Why the pause?
You think it's my fault?
I don't, but I wrote that
according to what you said...
Even so, correct it
if it's a mistake!
Our division doesn't need someone
who takes no initiative.
Our company doesn't need one,
and society itself
doesn't need one either!
Forget it. You should quit.
Quit your job and quit being a man!
Just quit!
It feels much better.
However, not many people can
go so far in real life.
Why doesn't anyone do that, then?
Because our ethics
tell us it's not good to kill?
Or is it the moral values?
A sense of justice?
Because our logical mind as a person
is functioning?
The biggest reason is...
Because we don't want to
get arrested.
Do you know what the relationship
between the murderers and
the victims in this country is?
"Relationship between
murderers and victims"
As you can see,
about 90 percent of the victims
were killed by someone they knew.
In other words,
if you were killed by someone,
there's a 90 percent chance
that it was by a family member,
someone you were seeing,
a friend, or a colleague.
For example...
You might be killed
by the person sitting next to you,
whom you're watching the telly with.
That is why the police...
checks out
the victim's social network.
That means...
Society itself
doesn't need one either!
Forget it. You should quit.
Quit your job and quit being a man!
Just quit!
Just now, because I'm an outsider
and I have no motive,
almost nobody would suspect me.
Let's say you want to kill person A.
If you aren't related to A
in any way,
even if you kill A,
the chance of you being arrested
is nearly zero.
The above is only a theory.
Who would've thought that
some people actually
try to carry out the theory?
It has been Naoto Takenaka.
"Your Turn to Kill"
"Chiunque Kuramae"
"Episode 1"
- Have you got that?
- Yes.
Let's lean it back, then.
- All right?
- Yes.
Okay...
Ready, go! Lift!
Sorry, it's difficult to
follow your call.
What should I do?
"Room 302, Shota Tezuka"
I don't know.
Third floor.
- I'll lean it back.
- Okay.
Okay... Great.
- Turn left.
- Okay.
- Sorry, we're at the farthest back.
- It's okay.
Please put it in front of
the bookshelf.
- Where should I put it?
- In the bedroom, please.
Over there. Thank you.
Great. Is this the one?
"Room 302, Nana Tezuka"
Nana, we're moving the fridge in!
Hang in there for a bit longer!
I'm all right.
Sorry! What is it?
I'm so sorry!
It's okay. I'll fix it in no time.
Can you?
Yeah. Give me a year.
I'm sorry!
It's so heavy!
Sorry, put it down first.
- Thank you!
- Handsome guys!
Thank you so much!
Thanks for helping.
But we've only started.
But...
My reward for
completing the first step.
There are children looking.
"Room 104, Yoko Ishizaki"
"Room 104, Kenji Ishizaki,
Fumiyo Ishizaki, Kazuo Ishizaki"
I'm hungry.
I'm glad we took the plunge
and bought it.
Yeah.
You had to pay
the whole sum of deposit, though.
You said that again.
- It's our money, right?
- Yeah.
Should I buy us lunch at
the convenience store?
- No, I'll go with you.
- It's okay. Have a rest.
Where is the convenience store?
I don't know.
Oh?
Go to the main road, turn right,
and there is one 100 metres ahead.
"Room 202, Sawa Kuroshima"
Thank you!
It's that way.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot my wallet!
Nana!
Nana, sorry. Throw it down, please.
- Hurry up!
- Catch it, okay?
I will...
Okay!
- I caught it!
- Yes!
Yes!
Oh, look out...
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, it's totally all right.
"Room 502, Misato Akaike"
"Room 502, Sachiko Akaike,
Goro Akaike"
I wish we could grow old like them.
I haven't been
getting enough sleep lately.
Like a child on the night
before going hiking,
when I think about the next day,
I get so excited that I can't sleep.
In addition, my husband
who is over 10 years younger than me
happily has me
twisted around his little finger.
It appears that...
I am never going to get enough sleep
from now on.
Coming.
I am Tokoshima, the manager here.
"Manager, Hiroshi Tokoshima"
Hello. Nice to meet you.
You didn't come to say hello,
so I came myself.
Sorry.
I'm joking.
Excuse me.
What?
All right.
Excuse me, what's the matter?
I'm checking the current state.
We have many issues
regarding returning tenants
their deposit when they move out.
Excuse me, we bought this flat.
Two gross stains on the ceiling.
Where are they?
Over there.
- Is this a bookshelf?
- Yes.
Use metal fittings
to prevent it from overturning.
It's dangerous.
Okay.
"Mystery Series"
Wow.
Excuse me.
May I close it?
Newlyweds got themselves
a semi-double bed.
Excuse me.
We didn't rent the flat.
Is this necessary?
No, it isn't.
Whatever. Out of my way.
This.
I give everybody one.
Wow, he gave us this?
It seems that
the manager made it himself.
He made it himself?
That's impressive.
He said he gives one to everyone who
moves in, and hung it there.
Wow, isn't it nice?
You're kidding, right?
Wait... Isn't it rude
to take it off right away?
But the flat opposite
doesn't hang it either.
But look... Look!
This person uses it.
What?
I wonder what our neighbour is like.
Hello?
Hello, I am Tezuka
and we've moved in next door.
Oh! Coming!
Hello.
I am Ono, nice to meet you.
"Room 301, Mikiha Ono"
Nice to meet you.
Please have this if you don't mind.
Thank you!
- See you.
Are you siblings?
No, we're a married couple.
I see.
Well, our residents' association
will have a meeting later.
I will introduce you to
the other residents.
Residents' association?
Only one person per household
has to come.
It's held once a month.
It's too trivial to be held
once a month, though.
Well, I'll see you later.
Okay.
I'll close my door.
Excuse me.
I'm Tezuka and we've moved in
to the flat opposite.
Hello.
"Room 304, Sora Kitagawa"
- Hello.
This is just to say hello.
No, I don't live here.
I am Kojima,
and I live in Room 102.
"Room 102, Kayo Kojima"
See you, Sora.
Bye.
I'll give it to you, then.
Thank you very much.
You're upstanding!
We live opposite you,
so let's be friends.
Okay!
Should we have given a gift
to the lady on the first floor?
- It was a bit awkward.
- Yeah.
We don't know
how many people we should greet.
Yeah.
Is this broken? It doesn't ring.
The flat there is unoccupied.
"Room 501, Go Sano"
Thank you.
My mind is exhausted!
No way! You can't be tired.
Aren't you happy to
have more friends?
I'm jealous of how tough you are.
Anyway, have you realised something,
Detective Nana?
Don't call me that.
Among the people we met, there was
something wrong with someone.
But there's something wrong
with all of them.
Be serious.
Are we doing our usual thing?
Orangutan Time starts now!
But I am tired.
Tell me, who was the weirdest
among the people we just met?
Well... The last man we met.
Yes. Why was he weird?
The flat there is unoccupied.
He was carrying a very large bag.
No, not that.
His boots.
The flat there is unoccupied.
It was sunny outside,
but he was wearing rain boots.
Yes, I realised that too.
Why do you think?
Well...
Wait.
The residents' association meeting.
We don't have to go.
We have to.
First impression is important.
But we haven't unpacked our stuff.
Maybe I'll go.
Only one person needs to go.
Then...
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
All right.
Ready? Rock, paper, scissors!
We think alike,
so it always ends in a draw
when we play rock-paper-scissors
and it makes me happy.
My husband works as
a fitness trainer at a gym,
I am a designer and I work at home.
Wow, you are a designer?
"Room 101, Yuzuru Kuzumi"
Do you participate in fashion shows?
I design sports equipment, so I
don't participate in shows often.
Who is a designer?
"Room 403, Atsushi Fujii"
Oh, it's the lady...
I am Tezuka, nice to meet you.
She said her husband works as
a fitness trainer.
Both you and your husband
have a job?
"Room 402, Sanae Enomoto"
The gentleman is your husband?
I assumed
he is your younger brother.
Your age gap is so huge.
I am 15 years older.
By the way, they have no children.
I've verified that
they have no pet too.
People don't like the manager
checking their flat
on the very first day.
But many married couples
that have no children keep cats!
Why do you have the prejudice?
"Room 304, Sumika Kitagawa"
By the way,
it was 37,800,800 yen, wasn't it?
Your flat!
It's been advertised many times,
so we all know. Right?
Anyway, it has gotten a lot cheaper.
Well, an accident happened there.
"Room 201, Keisuke Ukita"
He is just joking!
Oh, Mr Ukita!
I was joking.
It gets older every year,
so the price becomes lower too.
But I was surprised that
the price got lower than 40 million.
It means that
the money we have is getting less!
Exactly!
If there are so many bugs,
what did you update it for, then?
"Room 404, Yuki Etou"
The meeting is going to start.
I won't attend today.
Oh, sorry about that.
"Room 103, Junichiro Tamiya"
What caused it?
Sorry, I'm late.
I am very sorry!
We won't start in three minutes.
We should be here five minutes
earlier, but I'm two minutes late.
I'm ashamed of myself.
Never mind...
Chairlady, please start.
Okay.
13 residents are present
and five are absent. Is that okay?
Okay, let's start this month's
residents' association meeting.
Thank you, everyone...
Let's see...
So... Regarding the person in charge
this year,
we haven't appointed the person
in charge of cleaning last time,
would anyone volunteer?
But isn't it the manager's job?
No.
Someone is against
the raise of management fees!
That's why in exchange,
you guys will clean
the rubbish dump!
- The majority agreed last time!
- Fine.
"Fine"? The majority agreed...
Mr Tokoshima,
please speak a bit more softly.
- Mr Tamiya...
- Mr Tokoshima.
I don't know what the right amount
of management fee is,
so I won't judge anyone.
But I think cleaning the place where
we live, by ourselves,
is a rudiment of day-to-day living.
I think there are people
busy working every day,
but why don't we clean
the rubbish dump ourselves?
You are right.
Excuse me.
What's the matter?
What Tamiya said
was a bit too difficult.
What did you say?
"Room 203, Xinyi"
Xinyi, when you talk to
someone older,
you'd better address them
more politely.
Oh, is that so?
Sorry, mate.
The way you apologise too...
Well, let's forget it.
It's not too bad. I'm sorry.
"Detective novels"
Miss Kinoshita.
All right.
Okay, Miss Kinoshita.
Mrs Tezuka.
Miss Kinoshita.
That's all.
Okay, we've decided that
Room 401's Miss Kinoshita
will be in charge of cleaning.
No objection.
Excuse me.
Miss Kinoshita didn't come today.
Is this okay?
Indeed.
If she's got a problem,
complain to the seven people
who voted for her.
I didn't vote for her.
That means either Mr Tamiya
or Mrs Tezuka did.
I voted for myself.
Why not?
She's fussy about
sorting rubbish to begin with.
Miss Kinoshita might be happy
to be in charge of cleaning.
Well, she might open our big bags
to check them too.
Right? You see?
In other words, you'll just make
Miss Kinoshita do the job, right?
How can you say that?
What's wrong with you?
Excuse me!
We've decided,
so let's stop our discussion.
- See you, guys!
- See you...
Well then, let's have
our usual little chat.
- Mrs Tezuka.
- Yes?
The residents have a chat now,
as communication.
Do join them.
Well, I...
Don't say no.
People in charge of
money-collection and snacks,
- please help.
- Okay...
I have to work.
Ms Kitagawa, do stay behind
occasionally.
Mrs Tezuka wants to talk to you too.
Okay?
Okay.
Everyone,
Mrs Kitagawa will join too.
- Have you done that?
- Yes, but...
Thank you.
What is this?
We collect money from all residents
for snacks.
How much should I give?
You are free to give
the amount you want,
but if you give less than 1,000 yen,
someone will complain later.
Guys, you're staring!
I see.
Should I lend you?
Sorry, I will give you back later.
What is your flat number?
Next meeting will be fine.
I am sorry.
This is the amount you gave.
Thank you so much.
Have some.
We don't want any leftovers.
Thank you.
I'm Room 502's Akaike,
and I'm in charge of the snacks.
Nice to meet you. I'm Tezuka.
- You know...
- Yes?
I can remember something I've heard.
I have heard what your name is just
now, you don't have to repeat it.
Okay.
- Newcomer.
- Yes?
Do you want to kill me?
Pardon?
- Wait a second!
- You said that!
- What's the matter?
- This guy said...
that all the residents here hate me.
He said you wanted to kill me
three minutes after you met me.
It was only at first, but not now.
That's why I asked the newcomer!
You're so noisy.
So...
When we met just now,
did you want to kill me?
Don't be silly!
Why would she think so?
It's fine.
Because everyone has a moment
when they want to kill someone,
or just want the person dead, right?
No, I don't!
Usually people do! You do, right?
See? Nobody does!
But their reaction shows
that they do!
Either way,
why don't we change the topic?
Mr Tamiya, I hate people
who give fancy talk.
I'm sure that everyone does!
If you mean I just want them gone
and isn't necessarily dead,
then I do.
They're the same thing.
What are you talking about?
Hey, Fujii, you're the most likely
one to have one.
I don't know why you said
I'm the most likely,
but I was bullied
when I was in middle school.
You want the bully dead?
Not just the bully,
I want all the people who pretended
they saw nothing gone too.
You're so scary!
When I was still working, I was
always sexually harassed by my boss.
I used to want that guy dead.
I wanted him to die once,
come back to life,
then die once more.
Why would he want to
sexually harass Mrs Akaike?
Saying that is
sexual harassment too.
Pardon?
He was too nervous
to harass the pretty ones,
that's why he harassed me.
I see.
Oh, I hate people who doesn't put
their wind chime away in autumn.
The tinkle is so noisy.
Right?
Indeed,
it makes you go crazy when it keeps
tinkling on a windy day.
But would you kill someone for
something like this?
I want to,
if I wouldn't be arrested.
But I would be arrested.
But the police...
But the police first check
among the people the victim knows,
whether someone has a motive
to kill the victim or not.
That's why even if it's trivial,
if you have a motive,
you'll end up being arrested.
You know a lot.
My husband and I
love mystery novels.
"The Murders in the Rue Morgue"
"Detective Conan"
So, on the contrary, they won't find
out if we have no motive?
Don't kill someone without a motive!
I mean, for example,
if I ask a killer to kill you,
but the killer and you
don't know each other.
It's difficult to find out.
Where can you find a killer?
And I think they're expensive.
I'll do it.
If you pay me.
How much can make you do it?
10 million.
- 10 million?
- It's too much!
In that case...
- What? You can pay 10 million?
- I can.
That's how rich you'd expect
a doctor would be.
I can, but I won't pay you.
What is it, then?
You can kill
the person I hate instead.
I will kill the person
you want to kill, in exchange.
What the heck?
But keeping the secret would be difficult.
Yes!
When knowing the victim and motive are removed,
creating a situation where murders
are mutually exchanged
will make it more difficult for secrets to leak out
Right?
It's murder-swap, right?
But the person I want to kill and I
don't know each other.
You can kill them yourself?
That's good.
Somehow our chat is
getting frightening.
It is just an example.
But now I'm curious about
what the person is like.
Indeed.
I can tell you, Mrs Tezuka,
if you tell me
whom you want to kill.
- Me?
- I know.
You don't seem to want to kill
anyone, that's why we asked.
You look like
you wouldn't even kill a bug.
Oh, of course I kill bugs.
You love killing bugs, don't you?
I don't love it.
Do you live on macarons?
I don't.
Well, I want to ask who each one of
you want to kill, though.
Okay.
Why don't we reveal it together?
No! What do we do that for?
Frankly, you must be tired of
the Werewolf game.
Indeed, I am executed by
the villagers every time.
See? It's villager again!
So, for example,
we can write names on
ballot papers like just now
and show everyone without letting
anyone know who wrote it.
Why do you have to go so far?
I don't want to show everyone.
I will, if I'll show
only one person in secret.
All right, then.
Why don't we do this?
Well, it's the box we just used.
We'll write whom we want to kill...
If I don't participate,
maybe they'll talk behind my back.
The other people besides me
seem to be bothered by that too.
Don't look at other people's paper.
One, two, three, four, five.
Yours.
There you go.
Please write the name.
Excuse me...
I think we'd better not do this.
This is just a game.
Or is there someone
that you really want to kill?
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
May I borrow a pen?
Sure.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Everyone, put the piece of paper
in the tin after you've finished.
Okay, as we said just now,
we'll do it like exchanging gifts
at the Christmas party.
- Okay.
- Good.
There you go.
It's said that
what is left behind brings you luck.
Thank you.
Do not show other people.
Well then...
Open it!
Although it's a game,
it's the first time I see
words written...
when someone was thinking about
wanting to kill another person.
I'm sure...
"Takafumi Kono"
that this person has no idea...
that someone wants to kill him.
Welcome home!
I am home!
Wow, you've tidied it up! Thank you.
Okay. How did it go?
Nothing in particular.
I see.
- Thanks for attending it.
- Don't worry about it.
In that case,
will we submit this later?
"Marriage registration form"
- Yeah.
- Oh.
Your reply is not serious!
I'm sorry.
You said you wanted to submit it
after we move here.
Does our age gap still bother you?
Having a 15 year age gap
is quite common.
Quite common is exaggerating it.
I want to tell everyone properly
that we are married too.
You see, I feel a bit like I'm lying
to our neighbours now.
I am a bit scared.
Just a bit.
I feel that you are
very close to me, Shota,
I feel that you've gotten a lot
closer to me than when we first met.
But our age gap can never be filled.
There will be a 15 year gap
between us forever.
The fact that
we can never fill it...
makes me scared somehow.
Oh, why are you scared?
I don't know.
Maybe I am not scared,
I just feel a little lonely.
In the coming 15 years in your life,
you will grow up and
your sense of values will change.
When you are about as old
as I am now,
will you still love me?
I have the same worries too,
because you're also going to change.
I am too old to change.
That's not the case.
Sorry for bringing this up.
Look at the setting sun!
It's gorgeous!
Come on, let's go outside.
"Marriage registration form
Shota Tezuka, Nana Hibino"
I'm glad that we bought it.
You said it the second time today.
About what we were saying
just now...
I want to grow to become
a more reliable person.
So I'm going to grow
and I'm going to change.
And I think you are still going to
grow and change too.
But even if we both change
and become someone
different from who we are now,
I will still fall in love with you.
Don't worry.
We'll change many times,
we'll like each other
after we have changed,
and we will fall in love
with each other again and again.
So don't get worried and let's go to
register our marriage.
And...
Yes?
What will we have for supper?
I'll make something.
That's right.
We have to buy some groceries.
I'll go with you.
It's okay, you went to buy lunch.
Keep training
your internal oblique muscle.
Oh? You remember it now?
Wait, where is my coat?
Your coat is probably there.
- There?
- No... Wait. Is it there?
- Did I put it there?
- No, it's fine.
What?
Oh, hello.
- The manager said that, right?
- Yes.
But I'm not bothered by it.
Glad to hear that.
He also said that to me
when I first moved here,
that many childless couples
keep cats.
Oh, it's only me and my husband too.
I see.
Well, I think the manager
doesn't think before he speaks.
True.
That's why I thought I shouldn't let
everything he says hurt my feelings.
Every time someone says
something awful to me,
I say something nice
to somebody twice.
I am practising this,
so that I can make
the kindness in the world...
Well, increase little by little.
Is this weird?
No, I think your idea is wonderful.
Thank you.
Go straight ahead
and you'll see a supermarket.
Turn left at the second corner?
- Yes!
- Okay.
You can ask me anything
if you need help.
I am the chairlady, after all.
Thank you.
By the way, what is your first name?
It's Nana.
Nana, right?
You can call me Sanae-chan.
Oh, let me call you Sanae.
- Let's be good friends, then.
- Sure.
- See you.
"Chiunque Kuramae"
"Person in charge of cleaning:
Room 401, Kinoshita. Thank you."
"Room 401, Akane Kinoshita"
This.
What is this about?
I didn't attend the residents'
association meeting this month.
"Room 204, Jun Nishimura"
Sora.
Where's your mummy?
Working as usual?
But I saw her just now.
She went to work again.
Yeah?
It's dark now, go home.
Okay.
“Room 201 , Ryo Kakinuma, Airi Seno"
"Room 203, Cuong"
"Room 203, Iqbal"
That's right... Yes.
That's right.
Then the opposite direction.
Not like that!
The opposite! Don't you get it?
"Room 402, Masashi Enomoto"
Opposite? Which way?
Right or left? What?
- The opposite.
- The opposite?
Watch out! Look backwards!
What? Opposite...
Thanks for supper.
- It was delicious.
- Thank you.
But did you eat enough?
You don't have to force yourself
to limit your sugar intake.
I'm not forcing myself.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'm a fitness trainer,
so I keep myself fit to
gain my clients' trust.
And I just want to lose weight.
I see.
You'll get fat
if you sleep right after you eat.
What's the matter?
Keys.
What keys are they?
What? They aren't mine.
Maybe it's the manager's?
He came inside this afternoon.
- I'll go and return them, then.
- Now?
Yeah. I didn't see him,
so I'll go and say hello too.
"Manager's office"
Ground floor.
Excuse me, I am Room 302's Tezuka.
Are you here?
He wasn't there. Maybe he has left?
I found his contact details.
Maybe we can give it back tomorrow?
But wouldn't he be
worrying about them?
Are they the keys of his office?
The door was open, I wanted to
lock it, but none of them fits.
Maybe they're his home's keys?
But this looks like a car
or a motorcycle key.
Anyway, let's call him.
Nana, should you speak first?
No.
I don't really know
how to talk to him.
Why?
I can't really explain it,
but the other residents
have trouble dealing with him too.
To be honest, everyone hates him.
He doesn't answer.
Can you hear it?
What? He left his mobile here too?
He did?
It's outside?
I can't open it!
"Our property manager"
"Your Turn to Kill"
Was he murdered by one of you?
None of us wrote the manager, right?
If someone killed for you, you have
to kill for someone. It's the rule.
I know the answer.
The real culprit is...
"The drama is fiction"