An murder-swap game that was played without me realising it
- My loved one was taken away...
- Nana-chan
Even after I decided to revenge...
My wife was killed.
I want you to profile the criminal.
All disturbing events happened...
A lot of people die in that apartment...
Because of a murder-swap game.
What do you mean?
I can't keep up with that!
- Did you see Soichi?
- No...
The child is missing.
Soichi is not an ordinary child.
♪ ~ We are the children of science
♪ ~ It's time for everyone today ~
What…!
I was worried that
Someone may be killed again.
What? I was doing an experiment.
What?
What did you just say!?
Hey! Hey…!
Sora!
Mom!
Good….
Here please.
Thank you...
Detective, this boy.
- Take him!
- Yes.
Well...
Excuse me.
Is there anyone who was close to Sawa Kuroshima?
Eh... yes.
Yes...
By the way, the last time you met Ms. Kuroshima...
What happened?
That... yes, actually...
How is Ms. Kuroshima?
Fortunately, she was able to avoid collision with the train.
She was hit hard on the head by the impact of the fall.
The situation is unpredictable.
Huh...
Who is the culprit?
Excuse me, but it's an ongoing investigation.
- What?
- Oh no...
We checked the security camera,
but there are several people
We didn't know who pushed it.
- That video...
- Can you show me that?
As is expected...
Are you a friend?
Do you have any idea?
Hayakawa...
I was suddenly called by Professor Hayakawa.
Professor Hayakawa...?
Ms. Kuroshima wrote Hayakawa name in the game.
I see….
Excuse me, the Student Affairs Office of the University is here.
Ah, We're going now.
I have something to confirm.
- This is bad timing.
- Timing?
There's a rumor that you might be in a disciplinary meeting.
- Huh?
- Masashi Enomoto
started talking about your past bribery.
In addition, incidents around the condo are continuing.
It's because you didn't report about the game.
Your conviction is terrible and you could be dismissed.
Yes. Well, it might be better for you to deliver rignment letter
before your career is damaged.
Think carefully.
Well, you don't have time to think about it.
Well, I make my decision quickly.
What is it?
Oh...
The detectives were calling.
Thank you.
Would you like some coffee?
Aren't you tired?
I'm here, so you'd better go home.
Doyan, Are you okay?
I'm... totally...
But you already got me one?
Huh...?
You must be worried.
I can only worry now.
- I'm worried as much as I can.
- Yes.
Sometimes I worry, sometimes people worry about me.
It's possible because I'm alive.
- So my wife...
- Yes.
- She is out of danger.
- Ah... is that so...
And Soichi, was imprisoned in a juvenile classification home
The charge is as expected.
Attempted murder.
But he is still my beloved son.
I have to tell you,
As for Soichi's interrogation...
Each animal
has a different way of opening its pupils when it dies.
And what would that be like for a human?
I want to see it
And when I heard that,
How should I look?
I don't blame myself for him turning out like this.
You said he used to be handcuffed only when going to the bathroom.
Yeah.
According to Soichi's statement,
he went out of the room
and broke into Fujii's room...
♪ ~ We are the children of science
♪ ~ 1234
Was there a threat video?
Yamagiwa was my classmate at university.
I hated him since the old days
If you send them together,
It will be effective.
Good! Let's do it.
Takeshi Fujii.
Are you familiar with this?
Wow...
Technology nowadays is great.
Right?
I wanted to do eveything to help my mom.
Are you sure?
Then...
There's nothing I can say now...
Don't you have anything else?
Umm...
Was it...?
Doyan Doyan.
Well...
- Let's go home.
- No, but...
Her parents are here, and we will bother them.
- Huh?
- I'm pretty sure.
The third person in the room that day...
I make decision quickly
- That detective.
- Wait a minute.
In other words,
do you mean the partner of the Enomoto couple?
Yeah first
there were three people in that room...
- Nana-chan
- Shota...!
In the end, there was only that couple.
When Kuroshima was discovered in room 303...
Are you okay?
I heard that no one was around.
Did he betray and run away?
If Enomoto and his wife are not talking to the police.
There is a possibility that they are still in cahoot.
It's better not to rush and ask.
Yes.
I'll make sure he's cornered.
So, as Masashi Enomoto stated
Did you leak the date of the illegal casino raid and receive money?
Yes.
As a condition of silence
You deliberately neglected to report
on the murder-swap game
to cause confusion about the investigation.
If I get caught
I'll tell all about what you did two years ago.
Therefore, I'll take responsibility
- Resignment...
- Don't jump to conclusions, Idiot!
However, as Mr. Enomoto says.
I will admit an assault.
Assault?
We only heard about the bribery from Enomoto.
Huh?
Were you doing anything else?!
- Hey Kamiya!
- Ah….
Because of the bribery story
I had a fight with Enomoto in the park.
Hey! What were you doing!
I was witnessed by the resident
That's true. You're idiot!
Huh...
What will happen?
Maybe disciplinary dismissal.
- You asked for it.
- I know.
Sorry for the inconvenience!
You might be contempt for me
But I donn't hate Mr. Mizuki.
I don't hate?
It's subtlely rude!
Thank you very much for your help.
OK! If you're sorry,
I'll do what I can.
- Whatever you do now...
- No. No.
This is the case where many people were killed.
If you can solve it.
There is chance that you will be able to
receive only suspension as punishment.
But from now, I'm under suspension.
So! I solved it
I'll make it all your credit...
Expect it.
So Sora was discharged
from the hospital.
I'm not worried about his physical condition,
but I'm still worried about his mental state.
- The analysis of Soichi was right.
- Yeah.
However, what AI did during this period was
just looking for people who were
more likely to commit pleasure killings.
Soichi had an alibi when Nana was killed...
Nothing has been solved.
What to do next?
First, the database of past crimes has increased.
Please look at the analysis result based on that.
After all, the killings of Nana,
Akaike couple, and Mr. Ukita
The possibility of the same culprit is high.
If you try to narrow down the criteria for each item.
The reliability will decreased.
But in case of same culprit
Even if you add Kayo Kojima to the victim's data
The reliability does not change.
- In other words...
- The culprit who killed Nana-san
is very likely to kill these five peaple.
I don't know the purpose….
As a result, the culprit is...
Still uncertain.
Don't run out of control.
- Mr. Nishimura, this.
- Yes, I will take it.
1400 yen...
This is a private receipt, right?
No, it's magic when I drew a poster.
Then please bring that magic.
What we bought with the budget of the residents' association
It belongs to the residents' association.
Ah!
- Do you have receipt?
- Mr. Nishimura...
- Me?
- Me too
- I need to talk to Mr. Tezuka.
- Can I do it later?
- Not good.
- Hey! Are you going to run away?
- No, I'm going to get that magic...
- This person is really strange!
When the manager died
- Where were you?
- Do not ignore!
I was watching TV in the room.
Just in front of the manager room...
I heard a small sound that the metal rubs.
I had the opportunity to
hear the same sound later.
What were
you doing in the manager room at that time?
Oh... There was something I lent to the manager.
I went to remind him but he was out.
What did you lend?
A mahjong mat.
After a while, it was returned as new.
Is Nishimura here?
- Yes
- Please accept this as a token of apology.
What did you mean by apology?
I heard that he made a hole
with a cigarette...
I think he bought a new one.
Wasn't it?
Oh, please get it.
Oh, yes.
Hey!
Well...
By the way, Mr. Nishimura
Since when did you know about
the murder-swap game?
- Are you still talking about this?
- This is the last question.
Didn't we go to the restaurant together?
I heard you played a dangerous game
at the residents' meeting.
Eh?
Isn't it a promise to not talk about that?
What were you doing there?
I was told by Ms. Kinoshita later,
so I asked at that time.
I'm sure I explained... But...
First of all, we aren't told anything.
- Hey?
- Huh? Yeah...
I will tell you if you
return my work materials.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, if you have a receipt,
you can brought it here.
- Oh yes yes.
- Oh, I forgot.
- I missed my budget...
- I'll get it.
All right.
Mr. Kamiya.
- Can you take it off for a minute?
- Yes.
What?
One thing I want you to answer honestly.
You have heard about Soichi-kun?
Until this time,
even Soichi is not doing anything
- There is a possibility of guilty...
- I will answer.
What about the Akaike couple's incident?
There was no plate on the cake left on the spot.
Didn't she eat it?
What are your thoughts?
I ate...
- Be honest.
- Really.
At that time, Nana-san was watching the cake
I also noticed it right away.
Culprit was trying to make the case
that's the game-related murder.
While everyone was taking care of Grandma...
I contacted the police!
Why do you do that?
I mean, if the police noticed...
There was a possibility
that your sin would be found out.
Thank you very much.
Only one more.
After all whose name did you write?
Is it Mr. Tokoshima...
the property manager?
Yes….
Mr. Kamiya, This is bad!
I heard you're under suspension?
Mr. Mizuki, There is new
information from Sanae Enomoto.
No... No...
I'm helping you because I'm counting on you.
Let me summarize the numbers.
It is a little red.
- I want to make up for it from the reserve.
- Yeah, more important than that.
One of you did it again, didn't you?
On the railway!
What does this mean!? It's scary!
Let's talk about anything you know!
If so, please tell the police.
- Don't distract me. Are you a killer?
- What?
Weren't we looking for Sora together?
- That's right.
- Then...
The culprit is...
Mr. Tezuka, right?
- Huh?
- Eh?
Because “I will kill all the residents of this condominium.
- Haa!?
Everyone.
Is this a massacre?
Will you keep killing until the last one?
Did you really say that?
- I said that.
- Oh...
Why did you only said that to Ms. Ono?
Why are you so enthusiastic about the incident?
- That's right!
- Isn't too much...
- just for curiosity?
- That's all for the checkout...
- Well, sorry it's for the work.
- Eh?
- Ha?
- As I thought you're a reporter!
It's wrong.
I mean, you guys didn't know me?
- I don't know.
- Do you know?
- I don't know...
- I'm still not famous enough.
What is it?
“Entertainer who tried to live in
a place that incident happened”
My name is The Southern Cross Minami!
Ha?
One week has passed since I lived
in a property a 15-minute walk from Sakai Station.
From the first day, it gradually thickened.
Here is an example.
Look at this!
It's the grudge of the person who died in this room.
Wasn't it true?
Do you shoot this kind of video in this apartment?
Well I don't feel good.
But it didn't sell until this year.
I'm not talented at the time.
In this kind of niche
I have to do something extreme.
What are you talking about?
You!
Ah! It hurts... Oh...!
No matter how much you keep going.
It can't be helped!
I'll make fun of it, so help me!
Try it!
- Hey...!
- Stop it!
- Calm down!
- Hey!
Let's calm down.
Can you say the same thing if Kuroshima died!
If It can be solved by violent, I'll do…
Don't be meaningless.
We can't solve this without the cooperation
of the residents.
I'm sorry.
There is something I want to show you.
Okay.
- It's finished.
- What did you do?
I installed the app I made.
This is for Tezuka who
tends to take extreme actions
Think of it as an amulet.
Amulet?
Originally developed for elderly people
who lost their spouse.
- Eh... what?
- So
This app allows you to talk with Nana.
Well, For now,
It can speak only simple things.
By talking back and forth,
It will become closer to the person.
Doyan...
When anger cannot be suppressed
When you became hopelessly lonely.
Talk to it.
I'm happy, but...
That makes me laugh
Well... If you feel like it.
Nana-chan.
What's wrong? Shota-kun.
Where are you?
Come home early.
Yup.
What do you want to eat?
I want to meet...
Me too.
Sorry.
Nana-chan...
I said I'd protect you...
See to it that the culprit is lured and act on his own.
I was stopped by Nana-chan...
That was exactly what Nana says.
There's something I can't solve...
with just love.
I want to meet you.
Me too.
I want to meet...
Don't cry.
These are the reasons for Kamiya's suspension.
He will probably be dismissed
You guys don't act like idiots.
Yes.
- Then Mizuki! Progress report.
- Yes.
With the assumption that the game was played.
I've confirmed the alibi of the residents.
There was no change.
Sawa Kuroshima, who is hospitalized,
has an alibi in every incident.
Is it true that Sanae Enomoto wrote
the name of Hiroshi Tokoshima?
Yes, however at the estimated time of death of Tokoshima
The couple had an alibi.
Is it possible that his son Soichi Enomoto killed Tokoshima?
- I don't know
- But...
He is now proudly testifying about his crime.
If he killed Tokoshima, I think he would confessed.
If it was a game, the person who drew the paper might have killed him.
I'm calling many times.
Mr. Kamiya
Please call me back...
Yes
Oh, Mr. Nikaido,
I'm sorry you had to come every day.
No.
You're so kind coming every day.
I'll take your kind offer.
- Oh yes!
- I'll keep an eye on Sawacho properly.
Honestly... I can't believe she have friends in Tokyo.
I will contact you if something happens.
Thank you.
I'm here, so Ms. Ono...
I was able to be alone with Nikaido.
Two people alone...
Oh yeah, Would you like to eat this?
I made these wafers myself.
I'm sorry.
I can't eat what people made.
I'll eat it myself!
Do you often have such medical accidents?
Sometimes... but it is possible.
Potassium chloride takes about 2 hours to drop the drip.
If you do it for a short time, it will cause heart failure.
Hey...
Please ask me anything.
I usually only talk to my coworkers or patients.
It's fun to talk to a healthy amateur person.
Yes.
I don't know anyone, but please don't.
I've lived 10 years in blood and sand.
My face must have changed
- Yes, it's nice!
- No! Not at all!
- Huh?
- Is it okay? Your role is
A benefactor who helped this child 10 years ago.
But you're ashamed of yourself with
the past that killed people.
If she found out that a benefactor whom she has been searching for 10 years
Was a gangster,
she'll be shocked.
I leave without revealing my circumstances.
I'm leaving!
That's totally different!
Then if Mr. Tamiya does it...
I've lived 10 years in blood and sand.
My face must have changed.
You have clear eyes.
Why do you kill people?
It's human slaughter! Drifter...
Are you saying my eyes are clear?
What a funny girl...
- Thanks for your work ~
- Thanks for your work
I'll bother you ~
Of course you already know,
Kono was my subordinate.
You met him at the bank just before he died, didn't you?
Yes, I warned him about the game.
Do you doubt me?
If I was going to do something.
I wouldn't meet him at the old office.
But there were troubles at the funeral.
Ah… Wait!
Innocence!! I'm clear!!
It's like you
That's because there were many people who had the same shallow doubts as you
I have no doubt.
Because you were the person who put the surveillance camera.
To solve the incident.
It didn't help though.
By the way... Oh, excuse me.
Yes, Mizuki.
Yes….
- It's about Mr. Takafumi Kono...
- Yes.
It took a long time to analyze
the video of the security camera.
There were several people who are especially suspicious.
They were all about 170 cm tall.
It's 178.54.
You're surprisingly tall.
That's all.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Excuse me! Excuse me….
Yes, only the legs have been discovered.
I'm sorry to ask you something strange.
Some fingerprints of strangers were found in the room.
The police found some of them.
But at that time, there was a trouble at home.
That….
You also lost your wife, right?
Yes.
Did you love your wife?
Did you let your wife know how much you love her?
I'm...
confident.
Huh... That's good.
I couldn't tell at all.
But we didn't look in different directions.
There is a little distance, but we went in the same direction.
We were running side by side.
There's always someone somewhere in sight.
It's an excuse.
I was cheating on her.
Yes, thank you.
“AI Nana-chan”.
It was a machine, but it was not just a machine.
You should express your feelings properly.
Yes?
Doyan may be not good at express your feelings.
But it's still love that overflows.
- Eh?
- Umm...
Doyan feel like your love is acting on your own.
You can't stop yourself from trying to move.
What are you talking about?
It's when
Kuroshima woke up.
But... Who is this?
I'm sorry, you've called me many times.
Yeah.
Then tomorrow night.
Excuse me!
Ah... Good morning.
That's suddenly...
My husband didn't come back.
Eh?
Ah, it's okay here.
Don't forget to get in touch when you go out.
Yes.
Fu ~.
Angelina ~!
Angelina!
Angelina...!
Angelina! I'm back…!
Ah... It's been a long time.
Nice to meet you,
My name is Yoshihiko Hakamada.
I've heard it helps to get back memory
If you live in the same environment as before,
Are you familiar with that work?
I'm a doctor.
And here is Kuzumi's room?
Ah...
Hey Hakamada!
Yes.
Did you do it?
Huh?
Isn't it pretending to be memory loss?
Mr. Kuzumi.
- Um... I'm Hakamada.
- No, no.
You just said,
“I'm back” or “Long time no see”.
I was listening.
Aha I don't understand,
Could you go through the office?
Kuzumi is lying!
Kuzumi is a murderer!
Hey Fujii!
Ahh! Look.
Give me a break...
Why do you notice it so soon?
Don't worry.
Actually, I did it too.
- I guess so.
- Oh...
It's better to speak honestly and cooperate.
I even beat the police.
- Oh, how could you?
- It's that….
Doyan doesn't get irritated because you like Kuroshima-chan
It's great to meet such people
Nikaido...?
Grandma This is Chiunque Kuramae.
The apartment where the grandma lived.
Do you remember anything?
I'll introduce people who live here.
101 is Kuzumi.
102 is Kayo Kojima.
She had an English class in her room.
- 103 is...
- As always, You're not good at talking.
Misato.
I'm sorry.
And I don't know what to do with it.
I'm thirsty.
- Oh, would you like something to drink?
- I will drink.
I'm saying I'm thirsty.
Do you need to ask again?
If you ask, would you like something to drink?
You don't know how to use particles.
Oh and then I want to have tea.
Yes, I will buy it.
Wait!
I will pay by myself.
You asked me to borrow you.
You can't do that.
Yes. I'm going.
Please rest for a while.
Thank you very much.
But it was really relieved!
Don't worry, don't worry.
Yeah, let's take a photo together.
Before
Doyan feel like your love is acting on your own.
See, Sawa, laugh, laugh.
Eh now?
Mr. Nikaido, would you like to take a picture together?
I love you!
Even if you don't talk about anything, just being there is fun...
eh?
Ah….
What I wrote on paper was
Kayo Kojima
Good job.
Ah ~!
Ahh! Ah ah ah...!
Orangutan time.
Orangutan time!
Grandma was not participating in the game.
There is a high possibility that
this paper was drawn by Misato.
Mrs. Kojima was killed
after Misato died.
In other words,
Misato did not kill Mrs. Kojima.
Mr. Ukita.
Nana-chan.
Akaike couple.
There is a murderer who killed
these five people, including Mrs. Kojima.
What do you think, Nana-chan?
I think it's bullseye.
What is it?
Don't tell you're going to cancel.
On the contrary, can we meet earlier than planned?
I think I know who killed your wife.
I wanted to let you know as soon as possible.
I will wait for you at planned location.
Can I trust him?
Shota-kun, Believe in yourself.
Mr. Kamiya
Ah ~~~‼