"Everyone must have someone
they want to kill."
l think this is what started it.
We wrote the names of the people
we want to kill
and showed each other secretly.
Right after that...
The name l wrote
was Yutaro Yamagiwa.
I had no idea
that he'd really be killed.
I wrote Misato Akaike.
I wrote Yoshihiko Hakamada
on the piece of paper.
The name l wrote on the piece
of paper was Mrs Kayo Kojima.
People are murdered one after the next.
The man whose name l wrote also...
l don't want to die
when she still hates me.
We should tell the police.
I found out a certain fact
about the game.
But please keep it a secret
from Mr Enomoto.
Mr Enomoto didn't participate
in the game,
if he was doing something...
He did it for Sanae.
It is true that l lied.
We also do what we do out of love.
And...
l wrote the name of my subordinate,
his name is Takafumi Kono.
The man whose name is on
the piece of paper l drew also...
Don't really attack me.
Mr Kono!
Okay, that's all.
Thanks for your cooperation.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Mr Kamiya.
- Yes?
Please solve this case
as quickly as you can.
Of course.
Excuse me.
- What about me?
- Don't know.
I feel so hurt!
The man didn't kill Kono, did he?
Even so, too many people
around him died.
I'll hurry to check the CCTVs
in the area.
Shota!
l've just finished, too.
Nana!
I said nothing about the game
just in case.
But is that all right?
"Takafumi Kono"
lt's supposed to be the name l drew.
But someone else killed him.
If it's in that order,
the one that would threaten me
to kill him should be Mr Kuzumi,
but he is hospitalised
and unconscious.
This isn't a murder-swap anymore,
right?
If so, was Mr Kono's murder
a coincidence?
Like, the murderer disguised it
as a murder-swap?
People besides us who could find out
about Mr Kono were...
Mr Tamiya himself,
Sanae,
and Kuroshima.
I don't want to suspect anyone.
Well, let's say, l'm the murderer.
To kill Mr Kono right after
l find out about him
would be too obvious, so l wouldn't.
Does Mr Tamiya know
about Mr Kono's death?
I think he's been informed.
lt's on the news, too.
Until Mr Tamiya says anything to us,
l think we should feign ignorance.
We have no idea
who did this and why,
maybe we should be more careful.
Let's not tell Sanae
and Kuroshima either.
The victim was a bank worker
Mr Takafumi Kono, 26 years old,
who worked at Aoi Bank's
Sumida branch,
which is 200 metres away from here.
Mr Kono was sent to hospital,
but bled to death afterwards...
"Your Turn to Kill"
"Episode 9"
Also...
Thanks.
I think we should move away.
But...
Let's save moving
as the last resort.
At that time,
l thought l should stay
and stop the game,
but in the end, many people died,
and l couldn't protect
Mr Hosokawa and Mr Kono.
So...
l...
What do you want to do?
I only want to protect you.
Okay.
Maybe it seems like l'm running away
and it's irresponsible...
That's not true.
I also hope that nobody
will be harmed,
but if l can only protect
one person, l'll protect you.
And the other reason that l think
we should move away
is the piece of paper Miss Kinoshita
showed me the other day.
I think you'll be killed.
What? Someone wants to kill
both of us?
No, this...
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You got the wrong idea.
l wasn't sure at that time,
but it probably was...
l saw it on the news.
His funeral...
Okay, then. Bye.
It really was Mr Kono?
Wait!
I wrote the name of my subordinate,
his name is Takafumi Kono.
Evidence. l've got evidence!
Good evening.
The trick is to push
the attacker's wrist to the side.
I see.
Push his arm to one side and...
Mummy, amazing!
- Let's move on.
- Please give me a break!
It's okay if l'm murdered?
Of course not! But if someone
attacks you, just shout.
If you're attacked,
go behind the attacker.
Don't fight with him.
Call the police.
And l think you should run--
Mummy, amazing!
Kuroshima?
Sanae.
Are you coming home from school?
Yes, l took too many days off,
so l had to go to school.
Oh, or you won't be able
to graduate.
If Miss Ono knows,
she'll probably say that if l go
to school at a time like this,
l must be the murderer.
I just thought maybe
you were the murderer.
I am on my way
to the convenient store, too,
"Having a late night snack
at a time like this?
Are you the murderer?"
She'll probably say that.
Lately, l've been thinking
that even smiling is inappropriate.
I'm going to suffocate.
Indeed.
- See you.
- Do be careful.
It was supposed to be
my turn to kill Mr Kono
if the game went in that order.
But someone else killed him.
I see.
So l think it is not a murder-swap
anymore now.
All right.
I will investigate this myself, too.
Excuse me. Would you talk
to other detectives about this, too?
Regarding this, l think
l talked to you the other day.
I concluded that investigating this
on my own
is the shortcut to solving the case.
This meeting between you and me,
keep it a secret from Mr Enomoto.
You did, but...
Excuse me.
Why do you think
that investigating the part
about the murder-swap on your own
is the shortcut to solving this?
I am sorry, but l can't tell you
about my investigation.
Did Sanae do something?
Who is Sanae?
The wife of Community Safety
Division's Mr Enomoto.
You know that, right?
I didn't know Mrs Enomoto's name.
But she lives in the condo
of the case you're investigating.
How can you not know?
It should be written in detail
in the data,
but l didn't memorise all of it.
So, what did Mrs Enomoto do?
Well...
l am investigating a murder case.
Don't poke your noses into it
out of curiosity.
That's not why...
lf it ruins the investigation,
then l've done futile.
I don't think you want that
to happen.
Something isn't right with this.
But keeping the murder-swap a secret
from other people
won't be beneficial to him.
But he still investigates this
on his own,
is it because he is covering it up
for Sanae?
Cover up?
Like, the detectives
are on the same side
and they hide anything scandalous
for their friend.
Then, Mr Kamiya doesn't have
to do this on his own, does he?
Or on the contrary,
to prevent the whole organisation
from hiding it,
maybe he is investigating it
on his own?
If that's case,
we shouldn't get in his way.
But in either case...
ln either case, it still means
that Sanae killed someone.
Gosh, l really hate this.
I hope what we deduced was wrong.
I see.
"Car model: Rivelty lV
Tyre: 225-37R18"
lt really is disused?
"Car disused"
Nothing.
Thanks.
Hello, l'm Kamiya. Yes.
It's about that.
Yes.
Hello!
Somebody complained about you
quite a long time ago,
but you didn't hear it
because there was no caretaker,
so l'll tell you now.
It's too late now,
but it was from Akaike.
Right. He doesn't speak.
Will you hurry up?
You have a great voice
when you speak.
"An offensive odour
comes from Room 501,
there is noise like a bird
being strangled,
and noise like someone purring,
and it's noisy."
What the heck?
Did you bring a woman home?
I'm jealous. You have the looks
that let you stay silent.
"Takafumi Kono's Funeral"
Please accept
my deepest condolences.
Thank you.
"Reception"
Mr Tamiya.
Actually...
l should leave?
Well, l don't mind,
but some people suspect you.
Are you saying that l killed Kono?
Nobody says that so directly.
I worried about Kono so much
that l even warned him!
That's exactly why.
What?
I give up.
- Mr Tamiya again?
- Exactly.
Calling me was bad enough,
he finally came here himself.
He went, "Danger is really
approaching, do be careful!"
lt was horrible.
I gave up and just listened,
then he started to lecture me.
I told him,
"Your calibre is low as a person,
so you don't have enough wisdom
to listen to my advice."
So it seems.
But why does it make me
the murderer?
It has been bothering him
after all...
So this...
Oh, Kono, your name tag.
He has been telling everybody
that the killer you hired
was after him, so he hid his name.
Excuse me...
"Condolence Money: Junichiro Tamiya"
Excuse me!
I am innocent!
Just until we find our next flat.
What? Don't do that!
Everyone still thinks
that the murder-swap is going on.
Just by showing them
that we're looking for the murderer
can be a deterrence.
But we don't know
what Mr Kono's murderer is thinking
That person could think
you are a nuisance...
and come after you.
That's convenient. l'll be the bait
and lure the murderer out.
But it's risky!
I'll be all right. Nana, make sure
that you lock the door chain. Yeah?
Has there been any change?
Well, nothing happened so far.
Do you know anything about
the Yoshimura on the piece of paper?
How do l know?
Many people's surname is Yoshimura.
Yes, indeed.
I guess,
the only clue is the person didn't
use any honorific before Yoshimura?
The person must've been reluctant
to participate
if they didn't try to let you know
the name.
So if in the future--
What's the matter?
I am sorry!
I just wanted to see the result
of my training.
For my children, too,
l can't afford to get killed.
No need to worry about me.
The threats have stopped.
I see.
You did fulfil your duty.
What are you implying?
We know clearly the name you wrote
and the name you drew,
what l want to know is
if you threatened anyone,
like you were threatened yourself.
I apologise about the knife.
"Your turn to kill"
l didn't.
Will you...
What?
Tell your lies more skilfully?
You try to distract me
by shouting at me.
Has it ever gone well?
What's your point?
If your threat was successful,
then it's the police's job,
and l won't say anything.
But if you're still threatening
someone, please stop.
That's all.
I think Xinyi wrote "Masao Tanaka,"
l'm not wrong, am l?
But l don't know what name you got.
If it's in that order,
l think it should be Mrs Akaike.
Xinyi doesn't know Japanese.
But we talked at the diner.
Right? You said,
"Would you please wait?" to me.
It was in your dream.
How can it be a dream?
In Vietnam,
we call this "beating the tiger's
back with watercress."
l don't get what you mean at all.
Please leave.
But she...
Just leave.
- I...
- Leave.
- Was it okay?
- Yeah.
I only talked to them.
But Miss Ono wasn't home.
She's the one l want to talk to
the most.
Miss Ono!
Oh, you can't.
If you have that massage too often,
it will make you tired instead.
So l won't give you one today.
No, it isn't about that.
lt's about the paper.
You wouldn't tell me no matter what
when l asked you the other day.
Because l was terrified.
If l say something l shouldn't,
maybe someone will kill me.
I know,
but we'll find out many things
at once if you tell us.
Then...
Please hug me.
Pardon?
If l feel safe,
maybe l can tell you.
So l--
All right, now...
Miss Ono.
Will you tell us now?
The look on her face is terrifying.
No, it's not.
Would you tell us, please?
I'm scared.
No.
I can't tell you.
Sorry.
What? You--
The girl is funny, huh?
Nana, are you angry?
No.
I just thought that Miss Ono
always locks her door chain.
But after so many murders,
she must be careful.
But it was since the first time
we met.
I am Ono.
But she's a lady and she is living
alone, maybe it's normal.
But, indeed, l've just been
to many people's flats,
you can see the visitor
on the monitor,
so everybody unlocked the door chain
when they opened the door.
Has Orangutan Time begun?
Someone else
always locks the door chain, too.
Who?
Sanae.
Could there be something that she
doesn't want other people to see?
You can't run away
by saying nothing.
You attacked this man, didn't you?
There is a witness, too.
"She beat him with a baseball bat
37 times."
The witness should've helped the man
instead of counting.
Your boyfriend told us everything.
Your lie is so obvious.
He looks weak, but he has some guts.
How would he talk?
I tried to get him to tell me
who killed Mr Ukita.
But he didn't know anything
because he didn't kill Ukita.
No, l'm sorry.
Is this the same baseball bat
you used to kill Yoshihiko Hakamada?
No, you got it wrong.
We went to steal oranges
from an orchard that night,
so we couldn't tell you.
What about the night
that Mr and Mrs Akaike was killed?
That night...
We beat up the wrong person.
What are you talking about?
Airi wanted to kill her father
who abandoned her and her mother,
so we went to Yamanashi
to beat him up.
But we realised
that we got the wrong guy.
What?
Then, we found out that this guy
is her father.
So we asked Mr Ukita to come with us
to arrange the hospital
and help to hush him up.
I can't let them ask me
what l did that night.
That happened on the night
that the Akaike couple were killed.
So Airi did not kill anyone.
Please believe me.
No disturbing case happened
after that.
When we have found the place
we'll move to,
our neighbours have returned
to our residents' meeting.
What?
So they have also heard
about the game.
I can't believe it, though.
And it's okay. lt started by chance.
A number of people died, like, their
deaths were related to the game,
and we were shocked. Right?
It's a coincidence
that we don't want.
Well, whatever caused their deaths,
they actually died,
so l'd like to talk about
the security.
You mean...
My company has developed an app...
The neighbours
are surprisingly calm.
Especially to the people
who don't know Takafumi Kono's death
and the fact that Mr Kuzumi
wrote Yoshihiko Hakamada's name,
the last murder stopped
at Mr Ukita's.
Even regarding that...
At the end of the day,
the guy was a gangster.
Maybe he had trouble with someone.
I thought the game was the cause.
If you mention that,
Mr Kuzumi's accident, too...
lt can't be just a coincidence
if he died.
I heard that the man with him
passed away.
You know a lot.
Read some newspaper.
And then,
the Kojima couple and the Akaike
couple were on bad terms,
so the couples killed each other.
What about the last caretaker?
He committed suicide to begin with.
Oh, if that's the case, actually,
the game has nothing to do
with anything that happened.
Oh, that's true!
If you play such a negative game,
you'll be pulled
by a negative magnetic field.
It makes you think about everything
that happens to you in a bad way.
This often happens.
Yes, that's right.
The magnetic field was bad.
- So, chairlady.
- Yes?
I would like to declare
that the game is over now.
All right?
Well...
What does everyone think?
You are all here?
I found something left by the last
caretaker that says "apology gift."
- Apology?
- Yes.
Who is it for?
"To Nishimura"
ls Nishimura here?
Yes.
The apology gift is for you.
Thanks.
Wait.
It's over, right?
Excuse me.
Wait--
See you later.
See you.
- Mrs Tezuka.
- Yes?
Please go without me.
Is it all right to declare
that the game is over?
As l had seen this piece of paper,
l couldn't just sit and do nothing.
Thank you.
I want to help you,
so will you tell me
what you're hiding?
Pardon?
There's something
that you didn't tell us, right?
Why do you think so?
If you ask me back why l think so,
that means you really have a secret.
That's why l asked.
I didn't participate in the game,
so there's no conflict of interest.
Can you trust me?
But l have no secret.
Can we exchange secrets, then?
I have some very important
information about this game.
It's about the chairlady.
Sanae?
Do you want to know?
You do, don't you?
If you tell me yours first.
I am sorry,
but l can't trust you yet.
But this is to protect myself,
so l will make a deal with you
without trusting you.
If the information is trivial,
l will only say something
that is as trivial, too.
As the person
responsible for cleaning,
when l checked how the rubbish
was sorted,
l found this by chance.
"Chairlady, no money is deposited.
Why? l'll show them the photo!"
I found this in the caretaker's
rubbish bag.
I found two similar notes,
maybe he wrote them wrong.
Maybe there's some kind of trouble
between the caretaker
and the chairlady.
"Chairlady, no money is deposited.
Why? l'll show them the photo!"
Okay.
Now, it is your turn.
Please tell me what you are hiding.
The piece of paper.
The one with "Room 302" written.
It was used when we voted to decide
who'd be in charge of cleaning.
What?
I remembered.
The caretaker read it out.
"Room 302's lady, one vote,"
he said.
This piece of paper has nothing
to do with the murder-swap.
That was nasty.
You are the nasty one.
Why?
You showed me the piece of paper
to make me scared
and you tried to get information
out of me.
You started to be in charge
of cleaning
since the day after the caretaker
passed away,
so when did you open
his rubbish bag?
Have you been opening
the neighbours' rubbish bags
before you became in charge
of cleaning?
I won't tell anyone.
See you.
That's all for today.
"Chiunque Kuramae"
Orangutan Time.
At that time,
Sanae called us.
It took us several minutes
to arrive.
The window was open,
but this is the 5th floor.
The murderer tried to avoid
people's eyes when they ran away,
so they chose the stairs
instead of the lift.
If the murderer was a resident,
they would run back to their flat,
but if they ran away
from the condo,
this should be about
how empty the street was.
If they run towards that direction,
they have to go past
the convenience store.
When they were running away,
they got worried
and stopped.
They looked back.
"Club Carpark"
They smoked a cigarette
when they were running away.
Of course not.
In that case...
That's right.
Changing their outfit
to cause confusion
in eyewitness information
is the usual method.
That means...
The toilet?
Sanae's husband-- Wait!
Hey, what are you doing?
Sanae's husband, you--
What?
- What...
- Well...
You're right where l want you.
I got drunk.
But you've been fighting, right?
Kamiya, sorry for making you
walk me home.
I can go home myself now.
- I haven't finished--
- Now!
He will walk me home.
Yes?
Please.
All right.
Sorry, but please walk him home.
Sure.
I'll contact you again.
What?
- Wait.
- The acid is coming up.
- Are you okay?
- l'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I don't smell alcohol on you at all.
Gosh.
- Sorry about this.
- lt's okay.
Why do you investigate alone?
I can't tell you.
He didn't tell Sanae's husband?
Mr Enomoto didn't participate
in the game,
- if he did something...
- lt was for Sanae.
Did Sanae do something?
Who is Sanae?
Maybe he investigates it on his own
to prevent
the whole organisation
from hiding it.
I can go home myself now.
Thank you.
- Thanks.
- lt's okay.
Well then, good night.
Good night.
Maybe there's something she doesn't
want other people to see?
Oh, good evening!
Hey!
What...
What the heck?
Well, your steps weren't steady,
so l got worried.
The way you worry is rude.
I'm sorry.
What's the point of apologising
to me?
Well, l did apologise to Sanae
and her husband.
Why did you peek into their flat?
I just thought that
they were hiding something.
Even so, they can't possibly put it
in the centre of their flat.
You never know.
If you put a corpse in a suitcase,
it's quite obvious, right?
Whose dead body?
Mrs Kojima?
Don't say something so scary!
Anyway, don't do anything
you shouldn't.
But l do this for you.
If this is for me,
then you should stop.
But...
lf anything happens to you,
if you are killed because of me,
how am l going to live?
I don't know!
That jerk.
Do you think he realised?
I'm sorry.
I have to do something
about that guy.
Calm down, l won't die.
Because l love you.
How can l die and leave the person
l love so much behind?
But love can't solve everything.
- It can.
- lt can't.
I love you very much, too.
I love you so much,
but l can't solve the problem
with both my ex and the game.
I am so, so sorry.
It's all because
l don't love you enough.
Impossible.
I'll feel hurt
if there's another reason.
How can it be your fault?
lt's all my--
l want you to blame me
for everything.
But you already love me so much,
it's like l'm asking for more.
I want you to ask me
to love you even more.
How can l say that
after you kiss me?
You don't have to
because l understand.
So good! lt's delicious!
The fried chicken with tartar sauce
is so good!
- How many times will you say that?
- l haven't said enough!
So good!
I heard that people say nothing
if it is really delicious.
You scare me. Say something.
But you just told me to say nothing.
I was joking.
To check whether it's the chicken
or the sauce that is delicious,
make fried pork with tartar sauce
next time.
Sure. What about fried beef
and tartar sauce?
That too.
So good!
It's so good!
Thank you for the supper!
Thanks.
- Okay, next.
- Next?
The next urge
after the one for food.
Oh, let me have a break first.
No.
- Oops.
- But l'm tired!
- Don't run away!
- No!
Come on!
Oh, man!
Come on, Nana!
Open the door.
Give up and let me make love to you.
Nana.
I hit the bull's eye.
Nothing. Why?
I decided to give up.
Hey! Dive!
- Boom!
- You're heavy!
See you later.
Take care.
You too, Nana.
- Bye.
- Once more.
- See you.
I am really sorry.
Excuse me?
Shota? What's the matter?
Shota!
Please open the door!
All the flats' layout
should be the same.
Shota! Open the door!
Kuroshima?
Shota...
Wait a second.
Thank you for your message,
l'm so happy!
Just wait a second.
Wait, Sanae!
No!
Oh, shit.
"Your Turn to Kill"
"Preview"
"Chapter One, last episode"
lmprisoned.
I'll help you.
Run away with me.
What's in the box?
"What is in the box?"
Sanae!
"Who will be killed?"
l'll kill Shota and myself!
Shota!