"Everyone must have someone
they want to kill."
l think this is what started it.
We wrote the name of the person
we want to kill half-jokingly,
"Asao Hosokawa"
and secretly showed each other.
Right after that...
The name l wrote was
Yutaro Yamagiwa.
People are murdered
one after next...
"Masao Tanaka"
They said he got a note that says,
"lt is your turn to kill!"
People are cornered...
The name l wrote
on my piece of paper
was Misato Akaike.
I heard you played a dangerous
game at the residents' meeting.
You knew?
I think we should tell the police
about the game.
But still...
Maybe we would all be treated
as a murderer for a while.
I did nothing, so l don't want to be
treated as an accomplice!
We didn't talk to the police...
l wrote on the ballot paper that
l wanted to kill Yoshihiko Hakamada.
And one more person died.
"Yoshihiko Hakamada"
"Episode 6"
Don't panic, loser.
Sorry.
Also,
that isn't the only problem.
Thank you.
Big Bro.
You startled me...
What's the matter?
I saw you.
You went to meet Nana, right?
Calm down.
Anyway, when did you know her?
You hit on her?
But you're married, right?
Yeah...
Well, Nana is pretty,
so l can understand why
you want to make a move on her.
But you shouldn't.
Nana is my wife!
Oh, is she?
Well, l am happy that
my wife is popular,
but l had no idea that you...
l think we do get along, right?
We even have the same taste
in women! The same!
Your wife is popular,
doesn't it worry you?
One worries because
he hasn't had enough training.
It's a different matter.
No, it's image training.
"If my beloved wife has an affair."
That's the image training l do.
In the end, my plan is to love
Nana more than anyone else.
It's the only one l have.
What the heck?
Even if you're serious about
pursuing Nana,
l'll just give her even more love
than you do.
We worked together for a while,
then we met again after a long time.
I had no idea
that she was your wife.
What? "l had no idea"?
What?
It should be,
"l had no idea, sorry," right?
Sorry.
Okay, we're friends again.
We'll give you the latest update
on the case.
In 1991, when Mr Yoshihiko Hakamada
was 18 years old,
he won the Junon Super Boy Contest
Grand Prix Award...
When l was slim,
people said l looked quite like him.
I think l've seen him somewhere.
Hey, it's Yoshihiko Hakamada!
You don't know him?
That's not what l mean.
Look, it's him!
"101 Yuzuru Kuzumi"
He looks like him...
Wait, it's that condo again?
Well, we'll concentrate on our case.
"Murder of Kuramae Condo's Couple"
What's your current recommendation?
"Recommendation"?
This guy, l think.
I still can't verify his alibi
on the night
Mr and Mrs Akaike were killed.
"Room 203, Xinyi Lin,
student from China"
"Your Turn to Kill"
lt isn't your fault, Mr Kuzumi.
lt's obviously my fault.
It's because l wrote
Yoshihiko Hakamada.
I kept wishing him dead,
but l actually think that
he's a very good actor.
I think he was a good actor.
Who drew your ballot paper?
Yoshihiko Hakamada was a good actor!
Mr Kuzumi.
I'm sorry.
Are you threatened by anyone?
What?
LIke when Mr Fujii was threatened.
No, l haven't received any notes.
Moreover, l don't know the man
whose name was on my paper,
so how can l kill him?
Will you show me
the piece of paper again?
Sure.
It's "Asao Hosokawa", l presume?
Yes, the first name is Asao.
Yes?
I wrote the name.
What?
So, please, don't kill him.
If anyone threatens you,
please talk to me.
Mr Kuzumi?
All of these aren't a trap you set,
right? Or are they?
Suddenly, people started dying
the day you moved here.
The property manager died
on the very same day you came.
I am home!
I'm home...
Oh? Mr Kuzumi? What's the matter?
You hit on her?
What?
No, we're talking about the game.
Oh... The murder-swap.
They obviously are going to
make a deal with someone.
What did they carry here?
Someone is here.
What is going on?
"Asao Hosokawa"
Wait a minute.
I am this man's trainer!
He told me.
Big Bro will be shocked
if he's killed for hitting on you.
Hit on me?
That's how you knew him, right?
No?
- I...
- Wait... l'll guess.
Orangutan Time.
Nana, you're actually...
Married.
To him.
What?
I am sorry.
Sorry, l don't get it at all.
Who is married to whom?
You've asked me to
register our marriage many times,
but l still haven't, right?
Because l can't.
I'm still married to him
on the marriage records.
Should l leave you two alone?
No! Please stay here.
I... I'm a bit upset
if no one else is here.
Wait, but...
May l hold your hand?
Go on.
I think l told you
that l was divorced,
and that my ex-husband is Mr Hosokawa.
He's the managing director
of my previous design company
and he was a nice man.
But many things happened
after we got married,
- so we decided to get divorced.
- Many things?
Sorry, may l finish this first?
Yeah... Go ahead.
There was one thing that
l could never forgive him for...
ls it many or just one?
Sorry... I'm listening.
We decided to get divorced,
but he said
he didn't want to see me,
and asked me to post him
the divorce form.
So l did what he asked
and let him submit the form.
Then, when l went to
renew my driver's licence,
l found out that
the form wasn't submitted.
Did you tell Big Bro?
I told him over and over again,
but he made up excuses every time
and avoided the topic.
Shota, after you proposed to me,
l told him that
l wanted to marry someone.
He accepted it at the time,
but he still didn't submit the form.
Of course,
it was partly my fault too.
After l started working freelance,
l still took jobs from his company.
So when l think
about our future life,
l just couldn't insist.
Ouch! lt hurts.
I am sorry!
l know they are all excuses.
Yes!
- It's a bull's eye!
- Yes?
It's been a while since l hit
the bull's eye at Orangutan Time!
What is it?
I was just going to say it.
Your ex-husband is actually Big Bro,
and you wrote his name!
Yes! l guessed it right.
Shota...
Sorry.
Shota, don't apologise.
You've been worrying about
something so serious,
but l had absolutely no idea.
I'll kneel.
I hurt my semitendinosus a bit
during training today,
so l will just bow.
I am sorry.
I am really sorry.
- So, Mr Kuzumi.
- Yes?
Please don't kill this man
by mistake!
Nana had loved him so much
that she was married to him once.
I won't kill him, so may l go now?
"lt is your turn to kill"
lt has come already?
"Obey the rules properly"
l met him the other day
because l didn't know
who drew my piece of paper.
I just wanted to see if he was
attacked or harassed in any way.
I understand now.
So we're all good.
Anyway, is anything else
worrying you?
You might as well
tell me everything now.
"Room 302's occupant"
l think you might be killed.
Telling him more might
turn my worries into reality,
so l couldn't say it.
It's fine.
I see.
Let's start from doing what we can.
Is there anyone you can talk to?
Excuse me.
Oh, detectives.
What's the matter today?
We'd like to talk to her.
Me?
Actually, Miss Seno's fingerprints
were left in the late Akaikes' flat.
Well, we have done some digging.
You brought the old lady home
when she fell from her wheelchair?
Yes.
So, where were kind Miss Seno
and the two gentlemen on that night?
The three of us went for...
- a car trip.
- Dinner.
Oh? Which one?
We took a drive and had dinner.
I see. Okay, then.
"Kojima Kids English Class"
Mr Ukita.
Should we worry about the police?
I'll take care of this.
Sorry for making you do this for us.
I don't do this for you two,
it's just for Airi.
No, it isn't even for Airi either.
It's for the promise l made
to her late mother.
I won't let Airi have
a criminal record.
And you should
pull yourself together.
You'll marry her, right?
Yes. l am sorry.
When will you be back next time?
Tell me!
You haven't been back for so long,
and you'll just leave now?
You told me to leave
in the first place.
Right?
What are you doing?
You're crazy.
What... Hey!
Trying to kill me?
I want children!
What? Whose?
Between us!
It's too late to ask me.
Let's start over again.
You know that isn't the problem,
don't you?
We can go back!
If we have children, we can go back
to the happy days...
You're out of your mind.
- I'll race you.
- No.
- Why?
- Because you run faster than me.
All right, then.
l'll start two seconds later.
Two seconds?
Fumi, Kazu.
I made Bavarois. Let's have it.
I am already full.
Then, Kazu, let's have it.
- Ouch!
- Come with me.
It hurts! Let go of me!
Mummy!
Come with me!
Hey, what are you doing?
No!
Stay here.
You...
Why?
Why am l always the lonely one?
Why are you all here so late?
We want to talk about the game.
Let's talk somewhere else.
What do you do that for?
If we all know what name each person
wrote and who drew it,
then maybe we can prevent
more murders from happening.
Although I'm not convinced that
none of you want to tell the police,
l can understand.
If anyone dies because of the game,
it's possible that everyone
participated is just as guilty.
But doesn't it make you feel guilty
if you don't do anything?
I know what you mean,
but there's no way to find out what
the caretaker and Mrs Akaike wrote.
Yes, you are right, but...
We think that it isn't
totally useless.
I didn't even tell my wife
about the game.
I am sorry.
It's fine.
We hope you would convince the other
residents for us if possible.
You mean everyone here
agrees on that?
Yes.
I refuse.
Please. lf you say it, they will...
All these years,
l've been meddlesome...
during the residents' meetings.
But l won't be anymore.
I want to use my time...
for my dream.
What should we do?
I think we can only create
an opportunity to ask them again.
Yeah, let's do that.
I wonder what happened to Mr Tamiya.
He is like a different person.
We've made no progress at all.
What should we do?
Nana, who do you think will be
next to get killed
in the murder-swap?
If there really is
a murder-swap going on,
and it actually goes in that order,
the person whose name you wrote
gets killed,
then you get threatened,
and forced to kill the next target.
And this is the result.
That means Mr Ukita
killed Yoshihiko Hakamada?
"Ukita kills Yoshihiko Hakamada"
l don't know.
I'm not confident at all.
The news said that
he was attacked by several people...
But Mr Ukita has two underlings.
But you see, if Mrs Akaike was
killed by the Chinese girl, it's...
Sorry, let's stop this.
Most of these are groundless.
I believe what you deduced.
I think there are other things
that we should do.
That's right, Big Bro.
If he's killed,
you could be arrested too.
Please don't kill this man
by mistake!
I think we can trust Mr Kuzumi.
Anyway, you'll see him at the gym,
won't you?
What will you do?
I'll try to talk to him calmly.
Shota! Shota!
Sorry, I'm in a hurry.
Today, l made...
- Talk if you can keep up with me.
- Okay.
- Do you drink protein shake daily?
- Yes.
I made this protein shake myself!
Thanks.
The milk is additive-free and--
l am happy, but you've been
giving me too many things,
so can this be the last one?
Yes?
You see, l don't know what
thank-you gift to give girls,
and l shouldn't take too much.
That's what Nana...
That's what my wife said.
Thank you for this. See you.
Is that so?
Big Bro!
You lied about hitting on her!
You said l hit on her yourself.
Please break up with her!
Mr Tezuka!
Ouch!
You've trained me very hard.
Listen, l am Nana's legal husband
and she is having
an affair with you.
You even bought a flat
and live together,
now you can't make up any excuse.
If l sue you, you'll pay me
a large sum of alimony,
and Nana will lose the job
that earns her money.
You are nasty!
I've checked how much you earn too.
You will both be ruined.
I will still call you Big Bro.
Big Bro--
Well, we are brothers in a sense.
You'll punch me?
Punch me and get fired!
Just so you know,
l love everything about Nana.
I love Nana now and l will continue
to love her in the future,
and that includes the time that
spans her whole life.
In other words,
l even love the days that
Nana was living with you too.
What are you talking about?
When l say l love Nana,
l also mean that l love you too.
You'll break me.
Ow...
So l will protect you.
What?
If you feel that someone wants to
kill you, tell me at once.
Why would anyone want to kill me?
I told you about the game, right?
Nana wrote your name.
My name?
But l will protect you.
I feel guilty
every time l watch the news.
It isn't your fault, Mr Kuzumi.
lt's a coincidence.
I want to think it is too!
Oh, darn!
"Names Revelation Meeting"
Nobody comes.
I guess they really don't want to
tell others the names they wrote.
Well, we have been
keeping ours a secret too.
Why don't we tell each other now?
I will go first, then.
I wrote...
"My first boyfriend."
Your first boyfriend? Why?
He had seen
my most embarrassing moments,
so l wanted him to die before
anyone finds out about my past.
It is nothing serious!
On the train station platform...
l forced him to kiss me...
Well, l didn't write an actual name,
so l don't think he'll be killed.
Indeed.
By the way,
the ballot paper l drew says,
"People who don't give up
their seats on the train."
lt sounds like Mr Tamiya.
Yeah, he doesn't accept
anything wrong.
Sounds like
what Mr Tamiya would write.
I wrote the name of the professor
of my university tutor group.
His name is Hayakawa
and we're on very bad terms.
I'm now in my third year,
but he already said
he would certainly make me repeat
no matter what thesis l write.
How mean of him!
But l wrote "Professor",
it's obvious that l wrote it.
Xinyi is a student too.
But Xinyi probably wrote the owner
of the Bhutanese diner.
Yeah.
And l think l told you the name on
the piece of paper l drew,
it was Oda Nobunaga.
Who wrote the name as a joke?
But isn't the answer to this
quite clear?
It's someone who hates Nobunaga.
Nobody does.
Among the residents,
there could be offspring of
lmagawa Yoshimoto or Takeda Shingen.
I don't know much
about Japanese history.
- Yes?
- Yes.
What about you, Nana?
The piece of paper l drew says,
"Takafumi Kono", in Hiragana.
- You don't know him?
- No.
I don't know him either.
And the name l wrote was...
Asao Hosokawa.
And l drew the piece of paper.
Who is that person?
He is...
lt's someone l knew at my work.
Yes.
The reason that Nana wants
my acquaintance to die...
Well, it's a secret,
but it's just a side of her
that you haven't seen before.
This is Black Nana.
Yes.
Ms Kitagawa.
Hello.
l think it's time to
tell Mr Ukita everything.
It's still early.
I wouldn't tell him if l could.
But l think the police has realised.
What?
- So what?
- So Mr Ukita...
You do know what matters most now,
don't you?
Yes.
I'm off to work.
I understand why the other people
don't want to come,
it's possible that we'd be
in the same room
with whoever murdered
Mr and Mrs Akaike.
Are you not afraid, Ms Kitagawa?
I...
l came here for my son.
I fear that it could even harm Sora
at this rate.
Well, among those who participated
in the game,
there shouldn't be anyone
who would harm Sora.
What do you mean?
The name l wrote
on the ballot paper...
was Mrs Kayo Kojima.
"Kayo Kojima"
l didn't want to say that l wrote
the name of our neighbour,
but l think you all know that
she isn't in her right mind, right?
Yasu said he was afraid
to be on his own, so l...
This woman called Sora "Yasu"!
She gave him another name and
calls him that! This isn't right!
It's my fault that
l can't look after Sora well,
but l didn't want to kill her!
I'm regretting this.
I understand. l did the same thing.
Please, tell me what is going on.
We don't know that too.
By the way, what is written on
the piece of paper you drew?
Well...
l'll say this first.
I was...
a bit taken aback.
Taken aback?
Nothing is written.
Yes, the piece of paper is blank.
But I'm glad that it is blank!
Although l wasn't serious,
l still shouldn't have written
the name of someone l want to kill!
Mrs lshizaki also said that
she wrote her own name.
You wrote a name easily and
there's something wrong with you!
It makes me think that
I'm a horrible person,
and it makes me sad.
Oh? You are still here?
Sorry, l applied for a day off
next Thursday to go golfing,
so l have to work.
Go golfing on a weekday?
Well-off, aren't you?
I'm not well-off, that's why l go
on a weekday, because it's cheap.
I see.
- Have a good evening.
Darn...
l forgot them there.
I don't want to go.
"Email from Toshiaki. No subject"
"Will you send my golf clubs
to my office by post?"
- What is it?
- Well...
l'm just wondering what you think
about Airi and l getting married.
I'm happy, of course.
Besides the fact that
you'll be her husband.
I'm just joking.
Well, we aren't related by blood,
but l feel like I'm a dad
about to marry off his daughter.
I know.
What is it?
Well, actually...
What's the matter?
Why didn't you attend
the residents' meeting?
What?
You asked us to
look for the murderer ourselves.
Well...
I'm sorry. But l've already...
You told us the name you wrote
and the one on the piece of paper.
Hey, you didn't tell them, did you?
Hey, it isn't something
that you can tell a random person!
Sorry.
I'll tell you the name l wrote.
It was Yoshihiko Hakamada.
What? So...
Yes.
Gosh, what is going on now?
I have joined them
to figure that out.
So we're doing that, right?
Yes.
We're looking for the person
who drew the paper
with "Kayo Kojima" written.
Room 102's?
And the person who has Room 104's
Mrs lshizaki's piece of paper too.
Hang on a second.
If you want my help,
l can't do so now.
The police suspect me.
Because l have no alibi...
on the night that
Mr and Mrs Akaike were killed.
Of course l didn't kill them.
But there's a reason that
l can't tell them where l was.
Let's start from the breakup scene
at the pub.
But l haven't memorised
the lines of that scene.
Will someone remind her
if she's at a loss for words?
You want a prompter? l'll do it.
But you're new. Can you do it?
Let's begin and not waste any time.
Huh?
Ready, start!
I think neither of us is at fault.
We each have our own view
on what is right,
they just aren't compatible.
If that's also what you think...
l want to break up with a smile.
- No!
- "No."
"l don't want to! lf we'll break up
with a smile..."
- Wait...
- Yes?
What are you doing?
She didn't say her line,
so l prompted her.
You just delayed a beat, right?
Yes, l did.
I am sorry.
I didn't expect you
to delay a beat here.
If you don't mind, would you tell me
how you plan to act?
He said he wanted to break up
and l was hurt...
But looking at the development
of the whole story,
the girl totally expected
what the guy would say
when she is here, right?
So instead of being hurt
by what he says,
she would prevent him from saying...
- Please say the line.
- Yes?
The last line.
What?
- Start here.
- Okay.
If that's also what you think,
l want to--
No!
I think you should say it here.
"I don't want to. lf we'll break up
with a smile,
l would be a lot happier if we hate
each other to the core!"
Then cue the music.
It's a suggestion.
lt isn't absolute.
There's no correct answer in acting.
Let's do this again.
Please let me learn from you.
Okay!
Oh, I'm sorry. Please go ahead.
You're poking your nose
into trouble like this, Ukita?
Please. This is for a girl
l love like my own daughter.
I know where he is,
but won't you be in trouble
if the police sees you two meeting?
It was years ago. l'll be fine.
Tell absolutely no one
that l told you where he is.
Sure.
"Brothel Paradise"
"Parking ticket"
Darn!
I should've parked it
at the carpark.
"It is your turn to kill"
"lt is your turn to kill"
Good afternoon.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
- Sorry about the other day.
- Don't worry about it.
I do want to help you,
but l am extremely busy.
Sure. l understand.
And one more thing.
Yes?
I have information
that will help you,
that l refrained from telling you.
Yes?
It's about Mr Kuzumi.
I had bumped into him once
at the lift...
l thought it was fishy,
so l checked afterwards.
It had been opened and closed
over and over again.
Mr Kuzumi probably did this.
You'd better not trust him too much.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
- It's okay.
- lt's okay.
I didn't expect...
lt is messy, isn't it?
Yeah...
l've been busy going to school
and work.
But you have financial support,
right?
Or you can't rent this flat
on your own.
Well, my parents own this flat.
- You made me jealous!
- We said it together.
- Yeah.
Well, l've made a summary of
Nana's notes here.
This is...
l do maths in university,
sometimes l can't write
all the calculations in my notebook.
Wow...
Our main topic today...
is this.
"Game participants,
name written, name drawn"
"Murderer? Victims"
"Residents not participating"
Amazing.
I somehow feel that some people
don't like what we're doing,
so l think we'd better
talk here from now on.
You are right.
Somehow, l feel that
we can solve the problem.
"Game participants 101: Kuzumi"
- Excuse me, Mr Kojima.
- What's the matter?
I forgot to tell you
that you have a parcel.
Oh.
It's bulky and heavy,
so it's at the distribution centre.
It's fine. That's just my golf bag.
"But your wife sent it here."
"Idiot, l don't want to see her,
that's why l made her send it here."
When l look at this,
everyone seems suspicious.
Even people who didn't participate
in the game.
Indeed. Like Room 501's Mr Sano.
He lives right next to Mrs Akaike.
But he's been the same as always,
even after the murder.
He always goes up the stairs
to the fifth floor.
Yes. lsn't he scary?
Is Mrs Kojima all right?
I'm starting to get worried.
"Staff entrance"
"Sender: Kayo Kojima"
Mr Kojima, you must be using
some fine quality clubs.
- Yeah. You want to see?
- Of course.
Mrs lshizaki too.
Mrs lshizaki isn't on her own,
so I'm not worried yet.
Yeah... Mrs Kojima's husband
hasn't been going home.
This will surprise
a knowledgeable golf fan.
But that happened to Mrs Akaike when
all three of them were together.
Somehow I'm getting worried now.
Should we go see Mrs Kojima?
Look!
Do you know how awesome they are?
"Your Turn to Kill"
Who drew my piece of paper?
We should tell the police.
The people who threaten us
should be different,
but the handwriting is the same.
"Getting close to the truth"
l think someone is lying.
She was killed.
You need a motive!
Nana... l hit the bull's eye!