We wrote the name of the person
we want to kill half-jokingly
and showed each other secretly.
Then, one after another...
People whose name were written
were killed...
Ukita?
Even the man whose name l wrote...
And the man whose name
is on the piece of paper l drew...
Mr Kono!
During the hard times,
the time l spent with my love
gave me emotional support.
Make fried pork with tartar sauce
next time.
- See you.
- Take care.
I thought my happiness...
l am really sorry.
Will last forever.
Forever...
Shota...
Kuroshima?
No!
I hoped it would last forever.
Forever.
"TRY UP Gym"
Hello?
He left this morning as usual.
He didn't come to work?
Please leave your message
after the tone.
Shota? Your gym called.
Are you okay?
Call me at once
when you get my message.
Where should l look for him?
Did Sanae do something?
Either way, it means
Sanae killed someone.
Why did you peek inside?
I thought
they were hiding something.
Yes?
Nana?
Oh? He has gone missing?
You must be worried.
How long has he been missing?
I did apologise to
Sanae and her husband.
He hasn't been home
since last night.
Have you seen him, Sanae?
I am sorry, but l haven't.
Hang on, l'll help you look for him.
Thanks for waiting.
Let's go.
- I'm sorry.
- lt's okay.
"Your Turn to Kill"
"Episode 10"
Thanks.
Thank you for keeping quiet.
Kuroshima, l'll...
Ow...
l can't reach it.
Thanks.
He...
l think he is Sanae's son.
What?
They have a son?
Do you remember that
there was once before...
Daddy.
I didn't find it strange
at that time,
but when l think about it,
calling him "daddy"...
Even so...
why do they hide him?
Rather than "hiding,"
it's more like confinement.
Let's escape together.
What should we call you?
Please tell us your name.
I just think maybe
someone will come to rescue us.
This room is probably soundproof.
Am l noisy?
I am sorry.
Has Shota ever
ditched work before?
No.
I hope he isn't involved
in anything scary.
- A torch?
- Yes.
I was on my way
to the convenience store.
I thought
it should be Sanae's flat,
so l counted from
the ground floor to check.
Kuroshima, please come in!
Then, right after
l entered the flat...
Oh? l thought it'd make people
pass out right away.
Sanae!
Does the boy have anything to do
with the murder-swap?
I have no idea.
Can you call anyone here?
How did he go out to the balcony?
You are Sanae's son, right?
This isn't all right.
l promise, l'll save you.
Let's escape together.
Please...
Please don't blame my mum.
- Well...
- Yes?
Looking for him like this
won't get us anywhere,
so let's go back for now
and talk about what we'll do.
Sure. Okay.
My place is messy, so
if possible, let's go to yours--
lsn't it better to ask for
the police's help?
My mum isn't a bad person.
We know. Sanae is nice.
She just worries about me too much.
I was bullied for a while
in the past.
Soichi, going to
cram school again?
Good boy. We'll help you,
so that you won't be late.
- One, two...
- Stop it!
Ow...
This has happened too many times.
How long do we have to endure this?
All right.
Let's do what you said.
"Three years ago"
For some reason, l was put in
a carton box when we moved here.
Are you okay?
We're almost there.
At that time,
l realised that there was
something wrong with mum.
But it was too late.
You must be exhausted!
This is your new room, Sou.
Mum?
Why are you doing this?
Mum! Let me out!
She told me to always stay
where she can see me.
Sorry, l find that
somewhat unbelievable.
"Sumida Police Station"
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
It's okay.
Handle this quickly.
She is very worried.
I will.
Let's go, then.
Yes?
"Community Safety Division"
My dad...
He told me to be patient
until it calms down.
Calms down?
Until mum's heart is calm.
What do you mean?
It wasn't just me,
mum was frequently bullied by
the other children's mothers too.
Dad said her heart caught a cold.
Sorry that we have to talk here.
I can do this at the police station.
First, is there any reason
that might cause him to go missing?
Is the Community Safety Division
the right division
to talk to about this?
Of course, you request for a search
of missing person at our division.
However, we cannot intervene
if it is a civil case.
To sum up, if he left home
because you had a fight,
then the police...
The two of them
can't possibly have a fight.
I know.
But at this stage,
we can't determine whether it is
of a criminal nature or not.
Yes.
Even if you ask for a search,
the request might not be accepted.
Even if it is, the police
won't conduct a proper search.
What should l do?
First, you will talk to me
and l'll talk to my superior.
This is the application form.
We'll talk while you fill it in.
I'm sorry that my husband
was in work mode.
He seemed cold-hearted, didn't he?
It's okay, he's just doing his job.
People say that
his eyes are lifeless,
but l think he looks like
the Buddha...
Well, l will see you later.
Why? The station is over there.
Yeah, l want to go to his gym,
so l'll take the train.
And you, Sanae?
Well... l think l'll go shopping
and go home.
- Thank you.
- No worries.
Mr Enomoto,
l thought you'd gone home.
Don't ask stupid questions.
I just ran some errands.
"Request for Search of
Missing Person: Shota Tezuka"
Thank you.
Where would they hide
their spare key?
There isn't any.
Nana?
I thought you were going to the gym?
Are you okay? You can talk to me
if you're still worried.
I'm okay when l see you.
Don't be a stranger.
I am counting on you.
- Sou, l'm home.
- Welcome home.
Excuse me.
Are you talking to me?
Yes.
Have you seen my husband?
Do you mean physically,
or in my mind?
Pardon?
If you mean physically,
my eyes see you currently,
so l don't see Shota.
But l always look at Shota fondly
in my mind.
Okay. Thank you.
Wait.
You look tired.
- I'll massage your ear lobes.
- No, thanks.
I am sorry.
It feels good though.
See you.
Shota and l walk to
the train station every morning,
but he didn't today.
Has Shota gone missing?
No, he will be back soon.
You will be alone at home
for a while, won't you?
I said, he'll soon...
Welcome.
Sorry, l am late.
I've been wondering. ls it a play?
5,000 yen including
the ticket for the first play.
Yes?
You didn't have to sell it yourself.
We want an audience.
Mr Tamiya, you can make up for
any loss with your pocket money.
Drama is an art that only exists
if the creators and the audience
share the same period of time.
You can't spend time like that
watching a film or reading a book.
The audience enjoy the finished work
of the creators--
l've learned a lot from you.
See you.
But my beer hasn't come.
Well... no.
Is it about Kono?
Mr Kono!
Regarding that,
l do feel a bit guilty about it.
I can guess who the murderer was.
What?
I'm going to make
the murderer pay for that.
"Shota"
Your call cannot be answered right
now, please leave a message...
- What's the matter?
- l'm sorry.
My husband has gone missing
since this morning.
What?
He didn't go to work either.
Is this related to the game?
I don't know.
l submitted a request for a search.
But l'm still worried,
so l'm calling you.
Who did you give it to?
Community Safety Division's
Mr Enomoto.
So...
Yes?
But there is something
l'm worried about.
It's okay even if it's late,
so can we meet?
"Automatic number-plate recognition
matching report
Vehicle (TKA370 O 40-23)"
"For lsehara"
All right.
I have to do something
in your neighbourhood too.
I'll come to you.
Thank you.
"For lsehara at 23:21
TKA307 O 4023"
Everyone still thinks
the murder-swap is going on.
Just showing them that
l'm looking for the murderer
can act as a deterrent.
If Shota found out something that
let him to identify the murderer,
and that got him into trouble,
then the likely suspects
are Mr Fujii and...
"Sanae"
Maybe there's some kind of trouble
between the caretaker
and the chairlady.
"Chairlady, no money is deposited.
Why? l'll show them the photo!"
"First boyfriend"
"The caretaker?"
The person who wrote the caretaker
was probably...
"Murderer A, threatens?
The person who wrote caretaker"
The person who killed
Yutaro Yamagiwa.
"Where is Dr Yamagiwa's head?"
"Still Unsolved,
Dr Yamagiwa's Murder"
"After he was murdered,
his body was moved to a mountain
in lsehara, Kanagawa Prefecture."
The murderer couldn't have
transported the body by taxi.
Sanae?
Backing a car is difficult
until you get used to it.
Sanae's car...
Excuse me.
l am really sorry, but...
would you let me see
what is in that box?
You know there have been
murders, right?
I'm not suspecting you, but...
Sorry, and thank you.
Good evening.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Have you seen the car here?
The chairlady's?
She used to practise
how to back in her car.
Yes. Have you seen her car lately?
I will go buy something else.
Speaking of which, she's been using
her bicycle for a while ago.
Thank you.
But we can't get rid of
so many people.
Then...
Should we just let the two of them
live in the room?
Well, Soichi needs some friends
as well.
- Yes!
- Don't nod!
It's difficult to kill them both
at once, so let's do it one by one.
Don't say such scary stuff.
But it is scary!
It is scary, but we're doing this
for Sou!
Let's divide the work.
I'll kill Kuroshima, and you--
l have to kill too?
You should share some of
the household chores with me.
Fine, from now on,
l'll do the cleaning and laundry,
so you'll kill them both.
What?
What the heck?
We've never had a conversation like
this since we've first met!
Pull yourself together.
What's the matter?
We can't do this alone.
Where are you now?
I understand that
you want to protect your mum,
but if you do,
let's leave all the more.
Or the matter will get
even more serious!
Will you look for something
that can untie and uncuff me?
What should l tell her?
What... What's the matter?
Mr Fujii...
You've been threatened since
Yutaro Yamagiwa was killed, right?
What? Yes...
ls it possible that Sanae did that?
The chairlady? Why do you ask?
I think Sanae wrote
the Caretaker's name
So she was threatened,
and killed Yutaro Yamagiwa.
Really?
To verify, l need to know
who you'd threatened.
I want some clue.
Hello, Mr Atsushi Fujii,
it is your turn to kill!
Darn, l deleted it.
Wait, l kept the threatening notes.
No, l think l threw them away.
Please look for them!
l'll compare the handwriting.
No, l threw them away.
So l'm sorry, please leave.
Good night.
"It is your turn to kill"
She might find out what l did too.
Anyway...
when will she stop prying into this?
Anything will do.
But l don't think
they'd put any tool here
to prevent him from escaping.
What is in that box?
I was told not to open it.
Will you open it and look inside?
What is it?
I don't really know.
What...
No!
Please leave your message
after the tone.
Mr Kamiya, have you finished work?
I'm expecting your call.
How long has it been here?
I don't remember clearly,
but it was more than a month ago.
I see.
Will my mum be arrested?
Yes, she will.
Tell me, why do you think your mum
might be arrested, but not your dad?
The other day...
Why did you do that?
I didn't know what to do either...
lf you didn't know what to do,
you should've talked to me!
But at this rate, Sou will...
Your voice...
Your voice.
After that, l heard the two of them
went out in the middle of the night.
Then, after a while...
Do not open this, okay?
I'm sorry, Sou.
So you did what they said?
I had a feeling that
something bad was inside,
so l didn't want to know.
"New message from Kamiya"
"l have to handle something urgent,
so l cannot come."
"lncoming call: Nana Tezuka"
Excuse me, Mr Kamiya.
Where are you now?
I am very sorry,
but my matter is urgent too.
Over here.
Gosh!
Blindfold them!
Well, we'll do that anyway.
I won't do that.
I've explained myself clearly.
Why did you come if you won't do it?
You said you'd expose my secret,
so l had to!
Yes, if l am arrested,
l'll tell them everything you did
two years ago.
A detective gave information to
a suspect he was investigating,
and took 500,000 yen.
It was 1.5 million. l wouldn't take
the risk for so little!
The amount doesn't matter.
Be quiet.
I'll only be punished and dismissed
even if they know,
but when you first threatened me,
you told me to get rid of all data
about the game, so l said yes.
Now you're asking too much!
You've been hiding something from me
since the beginning.
The two of you
killed Yutaro Yamagiwa.
"TKA370 O 40-23"
l figured it out using the N System.
I used the data of your car,
so l found it first...
but Kanagawa's prefectural police
will realise it soon.
There is an empty flat
on the third floor.
Just move them there one by one--
l said...
We'll be in trouble
if they find blood here.
We'll be in trouble anyway!
I need three people,
including someone to keep watch.
If you do just that,
no matter what happens later,
l won't say anything.
I'll give you three minutes.
Think what the best option is.
This is the only way.
Hey.
I make my decisions quickly.
Don't ask anything.
You're asking too much.
Sorry that we have to talk here.
I can do this at the police station.
I just thought
she was hiding something.
Hurry up!
The key...
"Master key"
Why have you gotten this?
What?
Nana?
Shota?
Shota!
Nana! Please, uncuff me.
This is bad. Kuroshima...
Why? ls she here?
They took her somewhere.
Who is he?
Sanae!
- Wait...
- Hurry up!
All right...
Run!
Nana!
Call someone here!
Someone, please!
Help us! Help!
Help!
How should l shut you up?
Yutaro Yamagiwa was in my car's boot
at that time,
so you are my accomplice!
Right? Will you shut up now?
Got a problem?
I am really sorry.
I do this for my son!
Who cares, this isn't right!
You won't understand,
because you aren't a mother!
It doesn't matter who l sacrifice,
l have to protect those l love!
Catch her!
- What's going on?
- Come with us.
Thank you. Wait here.
Wait...
Apologising won't help!
No...
ldiot! Don't do it here!
Kamiya, help us! Kami--
That jerk!
- Don't come here!
- What?
- Help!
- Sorry, it got just out of control.
Gosh, Mrs Enomoto!
But you're the police!
What happened?
I said, it's a blender!
What you use to make smoothie!
She's using it... Just come now!
- Nana!
- Shota!
Sanae, let's give up.
Don't worry, Masashi!
I'll take care of this!
What?
Now, listen to me!
Look carefully
at the blender's blades!
What?
Concentrate!
When the blender stops,
you will forget
what you are seeing now!
What are you talking about?
That's enough...
Please!
Forget what you see!
Look carefully at this!
I beg you!
- Sanae!
- Don't come here!
If you come any closer,
l'll kill Nana, and then myself!
Sanae...
What's going on?
Don't do this.
Who is that?
Sou!
Soichi!
Mum, l'll jump off here
if you don't stop!
What? "Mum"?
His mother?
Get off there. lt's dangerous!
Let the lady go, then!
- Nana!
- Shota...
Soichi, get off there!
Shota!
- Soichi!
- Shota!
Sou! Sou...
Sou!
You haven't forgotten
what you promised, right?
Well...
Fried pork with tartar sauce.
Shota!
Nana?
Excuse me, l'm Sumida Police
Station's Mizuki.
What?
You mean every day...
Mrs Tezuka stays here so long,
l worried that she'd get ill.
Wow... l miss her so much!
About Sanae Enomoto...
You can't ask him that yet.
But...
Ask him after the doctor approves.
Please leave for now.
Come on!
"Housewife Attempted Murder
with A Hand Blender..."
"Doctor Yamagiwa's head found!"
"Suspect, Sanae Enomoto is arrested
for attempted murder,
but she remains silent
about Doctor Yamagiwa's murder."
"The boy who fell
only has minor injuries
and has been discharged
from the hospital.
He is staying at a children's home."
Mr Tezuka, l'll come in now.
"Tokyo Metropolitan Police Hospital"
Oh, you're right where l want you.
Mr Tezuka?
You shouldn't walk yet!
I want to call back home.
May l borrow 10 yen?
Mrs Tezuka called us. She will come
when she finishes work.
Now return to your room.
Okay.
Sorry.
I'll just take my wallet
and be back at once.
I might keep you waiting here
for a bit. See you later.
My key...
Shota, are you okay?
And are you okay?
They only tied me up.
You've been discharged already?
I sneaked out of there.
I want to see Nana as soon as l can.
You must miss her.
But not only that.
I want to propose to her again
as soon as l can.
I think Nana will be happy.
- Don't tell her. lt's a surprise.
- Okay.
Please record the memorable moment
for the both of us.
Yes?
Now, after hundreds of years,
l am going to see Nana again!
Oh? lt isn't locked.
After so many things happened...
Nana is too careless!
Please come in...
Be quiet.
She isn't in her office.
She'll shout at me later.
Let's go.
Oh?
Not here.
We really are going to surprise her
by waking her up!
Here l go.
Good morning, Nana!
Why?
Nana!
"Your Turn to Kill"
The condo is cursed!
All mysteries will be shown
next time!
And...
The murderer will die in pieces!
We're destined to be together!
I love you! l really love you!
I am sorry!
It is a special episode.
I love you!