Everyone must have someone
they want to kill.
l think this is what started it.
We wrote the name of the person
we want to kill half-jokingly
and secretly showed each other.
Right after that...
When we still couldn't believe it,
some people have killed someone,
the person who had someone killed
for them kills someone else...
Perhaps.
You wrote the diner's owner's name?
I didn't think he would be killed.
Your wife didn't tell you?
It's the murder-swap game.
Your husband is here.
What is the "murder-swap game"?
Then, again...
Mrs Akaike!
I'll call the police!
Old Mrs Akaike!
(Oh, my Julia!)
Mrs Akaike!
Misato Akaike
- Thank you.
The entrance's door was unlocked?
Yes.
The window was opened too.
Only the four of us
entered the flat.
Shota, are you okay?
Yeah, l am okay.
But there's blood on your foot...
lt isn't my blood.
What happened?
Good evening, sir.
Good evening, sir...
Drive the people outside away!
Yes, sir.
- Go now!
- Yes, sir!
How many people died?
Two. Look directly at them.
But l am scared!
Are you okay?
I guess not.
Why don't we move away from here?
Okay. Well, we have a mortgage,
so it's a bit hard,
but if we rent out the flat,
we can get some money,
but under this situation...
What will happen to the person
l wrote on my piece of paper later?
I can't search anything
if we move away.
Let's save moving away as
our last resort.
Why?
Because l mentioned money again?
Sorry, but we'll be okay.
I think we should move away
even if it'll be tough.
I'm scared, but the police will come
to investigate this for a while,
so maybe l feel safest here.
What? But l am scared!
Don't cry.
Nana, go to bed with me.
Sorry, l'll send
a business email first.
At a time like this?
I'll send an email to ask
if they can extend the deadline.
Xinyi wrote Masao Tanaka?
Misato Akaike
Did Xinyi kill Misato?
Nana, have you finished?
Your Turn to Kill
Episode 5
We presume that the weapon is an 8
to 15 centimetres long knife,
but we have not found it so far.
Did the old lady in the flat
say anything after that?
No, she kept mumbling something,
but she didn't answer
any of our questions.
Are any of the residents suspicious?
The people whose whereabouts
we can't locate at the EOD are...
201's Keisuke Ukita,
Ryo Kakinuma,
Airi Seno.
203's...
Sorry.
203's Xinyi Lin,
204's Jun Nishimura,
301's Mikiha Ono
and the flat next door,
501's Go Sano.
Why are the photos like that?
They were taken secretly
during the interview.
They all look like killers to me.
Also, we lifted fingerprints
other than the victims' in the flat.
They are 201's Airi Seno,
202's Sawa Kuroshima,
203's Iqbal Bin Dato,
302's Nana Tezuka,
404's Yuki Etou.
We found these people's
fingerprints.
The one who left fingerprints
in the flat
and has no alibi is...
This girl?
- I'm counting on you!
- Yes, sir...
Hey, take this with you.
What? lt's salt again?
The residential tower is cursed!
Indeed.
The property manager killed himself
last month,
a diner exploded and the owner died,
the waitress...
and a regular customer live there.
On top of that, the customer found
the body of the murder victims.
Hey, speaking of which, why didn't
you report these just now?
Do you remember Mr Enomoto?
- Mr Kamiya.
- Yes?
Good evening.
Enomoto lives there too. And?
He indirectly put pressure on me.
Enomoto?
Hey.
He seems to want to be promoted
one rank up from lnspector,
so he cares about his reputation.
Whether he can be a Superintendent,
the boss's appraisal matters.
So about what happened
at the residential tower...
Nowadays, you never know
what will be against your favour.
Well, l don't need to hide anything,
but don't you think
you don't need
to make connections between
everything and make a fuss?
What?
Just because he happens to live
in the condo that a murder happened?
It won't affect his promotion!
That's what l said too, but...
Well, this isn't important,
but the Deputy Chief
is waiting for my promotion.
If officers of his faction
are at the best possible positions,
it's easier for him to work too.
At a time like this,
if my chance of being promoted
is lost because of you guys,
what will the Deputy Chief think?
In that case, do as Enomoto wishes.
What?
Idiot! lf you get dragged
into an organisation's trouble,
it'll be even scarier than a curse.
Alibi not verified
Room 203, Xinyi Lin
Smoking is not allowed
inside the building.
Smoking isn't allowed
outside the building too!
Are you serious?
Yes.
I think we should tell the police
about the game.
l think it's important information
for catching the murderer this time.
You relate it with the game again?
Actually,
there was a birthday cake
at Mrs Akaike's flat,
and "Misato Akaike" was written
on the chocolate plaque.
Usually it should say
"Happy birthday, someone," right?
But it was only the name,
Misato Akaike.
What? You say that Mrs Akaike
was killed in the game
based on that?
That's all?
Not based on that, but...
lt's the same as saying that someone
among us killed Mr and Mrs Akaike.
That's not what l mean.
What do you mean, then?
Actually...
l also think that it's better
if we tell the police,
but...
what about the inducement of murder
we talked about the other day?
I don't know very well either.
I didn't do anything,
so l don't want to be seen
as the murderer's accomplice.
Mrs lshizaki,
didn't you say you wrote your name
on the piece of paper?
Make sure you don't kill me
by mistake.
Yes, so?
Instead of worrying
about being killed,
you worry more about being seen
as an accomplice?
What's your point?
I just thought you were the murderer
for a bit.
What? You...
Sorry, l am late.
Are you all right?
Why do you ask?
Mrs Tamiya
said you weren't feeling well.
I am all right. What's the topic?
Mrs Tezuka suggests that we should
tell the police about the game.
I'll let you make the decision.
We can't reach a conclusion
on our own,
so we would like your opinion.
Yes?
I have looked it up,
and l don't think we'll be arrested.
Really?
But all of us could be treated
as murderers for a while.
- That would be awful.
- But...
We'll be in trouble
if gossip magazines sniff anything.
They'll say this is a condo full
of murder suspects and cause a stir.
I think you're exaggerating it.
Murderers' condo
lf they add an exclamation mark
and a question mark,
they can write
almost anything they want.
It's over if they do this.
Even if we're found innocent
at the end,
it'll stay on the internet forever.
Mrs lshizaki,
your children's classmates will call
your kids "murderer's children."
Our properties' value
will drop rapidly too.
It's like our whole residential
tower is a stigmatised property.
Fujii got most desperate
and he's suspicious.
Don't make fun of me!
Fine.
How can you be so calm?
We are all terrified!
Are you calm
because you're the murderer?
What do you mean?
This isn't right.
- Miss Ono.
- Please calm down.
- Mrs lshizaki too.
- What do you mean?
- You said l was the murderer!
- l didn't.
You did!
Among these three people?
Did they come to buy
a birthday cake?
I don't remember their faces.
Did you keep the receipt?
We did, just a moment, please.
Well...
You are scared because Mrs Tezuka
wants to report us to the police.
"Report"?
You guys are fishy because
you are afraid of the police.
Let's calm down.
You see, someone knocked his hand on
the desk and injured himself before.
Yes, l did.
Sorry for causing you trouble.
It's totally healed now.
I'm not young anymore,
I'm ashamed of what l did...
l am sorry.
Yes?
I was joking.
What joke?
You don't get it, old man.
Mr Tamiya's seriousness isn't funny
at all,
but it makes me happy to see it
after a long while.
In the end,
what are we going to do?
I have been living here for years,
so l know that none of us
is a murderer.
But Mrs Tezuka just moved here,
so l think she just
doesn't understand that.
Please don't blame her.
The murderer wasn't caught
on camera, Mr Tamiya?
You put many in the building.
I haven't been recording lately.
What were you trying to do, then?
I feel ashamed of myself.
Everyone, l am sorry.
First of all,
were Mr and Mrs Akaike murdered?
They could be having a fight
and it turned ugly.
Relating it to the game
based on the chocolate plaque
is unreasonable.
I think the couple
didn't have a fight.
Right?
Let the police investigate this.
If it's just a hunch,
it's pointless if our mere guesses
make things awkward between us.
Then we have to tell them
about the game.
Then we need everyone's consent.
Someone joined the game,
but is absent today.
You mean Ms Kitagawa?
I'm home.
Sora?
Sora, l am home.
If there's a possibility
that all of us will be suspected,
we have to get
Mrs Kitagawa consent too.
Let's make the decision later, then.
We'll decide later.
Are you not scared?
I carelessly wrote the name
of someone l know.
Frankly, it's a long story
and l hate the person.
But when l think that they might be
killed, I'm absolutely terrified.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
It was horrible, wasn't it?
Oh, l watched that.
lt was interesting.
What did you watch?
The musical movie you recommended.
I recommended a few.
Which one was it?
If a film l watch is interesting,
l forget its title.
The thought that the film
is interesting occupies my mind...
What the heck?
Well then, let's vote.
Is that okay?
I think it's the only way.
Okay.
- Then...
- lt was just once.
A murder just happened by chance.
If you want to make all residents
here suspects, then raise your hand.
- The way you say it...
- Raise your hand.
We have decided
that we won't tell the police?
Sorry, l second that.
Me too.
You take her side
because you know the result.
Tell me if you have
any other recommendations.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Okay...
Have a good evening.
- Nana.
- Yes?
I am sorry,
l couldn't raise my hand right away.
It's okay.
I am sorry too.
Don't worry about it.
Maybe l just worry too much.
Who do you think you are?
What the heck is going on?
It's none of your business.
How dare you!
Calm down.
Sora, you'll go now?
Leave Sora alone!
Calm down and talk--
l am very calm!
Hands off him!
- Shut up!
- Hey...
And don't step on me!
Sorry about the fuss.
It's okay, but...
Why do you act calm?
You are scaring Sora.
Don't touch Sora!
Stop!
Don't touch him!
You...
This woman kidnapped Sora!
Sora and Mrs Kojima
often spend time together.
I had played with him too.
Sora told me that our neighbours
have been taking care of him,
but something is wrong
with this woman!
A murder just happened, Yasu said
that he was scared, so l...
See?
She called Sora "Yasu."
She gave him another name
and calls him that.
This isn't right!
I just said the wrong name...
Who do you use Sora to replace?
Ms Kitagawa, l think it's enough...
Sora, take this off.
What are you doing?
That woman made Sora wear this!
She forced Sora
to go to the barber with her
and changed Sora's hairstyle
the other day!
Darn!
Let's go home.
Excuse me.
Sora, let's go home.
Your wife didn't tell you?
It's the murder-swap game.
Orangutan Time...
How was the residents' meeting?
Nothing special.
It's Nana's habit
to cross her fingers when she lies.
Why did they have
an urgent residents' meeting?
Well...
Not only did Nana not tell me
about the game,
but she even lied to me.
If the property manager,
the owner of the Bhutanese diner,
Mr and Mrs Akaike...
were murdered as part of the game...
Wait, she is worrying so much
on her own!
I feel so bad for Nana!
However...
lt's kind to let her worry.
Very often, it's better to just let
the person solve the problem.
What Big Bro said
was reasonable as well.
But when will
the residents' meeting end?
Murderers' condo
Excuse me.
Yes?
Is the residents' meeting over?
I think it isn't held today.
Manager's office
She isn't here.
Sorry for making you hide.
It's okay.
And...
l thought a bit
about telling everyone.
I think l will tell you whose name
l wrote on my piece of paper.
Yes?
Actually...
l wrote "Misato Akaike."
Misato Akaike
The person
who drew my piece of paper
really carried out the murder.
They even killed her husband.
If you had said it
during the meeting,
maybe they would agree
to tell the police too.
But if we talk to the police now,
l'll be the most likely the suspect.
Moreover, if they ask
what l did that night,
l'd be in trouble.
But you didn't kill them,
did you, Mr Ukita?
Of course l didn't kill them.
But l'll be suspected
because of my current job too.
Is that so...
Why did you want someone to kill
Mrs Akaike in the first place?
It didn't occur to me
that she would actually be killed.
You said the other day
that Mrs Akaike kept ignoring you.
Well, the woman looks down on people
more stupid than her.
She didn't seem as someone
who's like that to me.
You know the young couple
who live at my place?
Airi told me...
You can't even send a postcard back?
I am sorry.
I thought l had put a stamp on it.
You didn't cross out the "to"
under the recipient.
If the recipient had received this,
you would've embarrassed me.
I am very sorry.
The education you received
was different from mine and Goro's
and l know that,
but l thought you would catch up
if you had spent decades with us.
Yes, l am sorry.
I am glad that you have no children.
The genes of idiots end here.
That's what the old woman does
when she's alone with you?
If she does that again,
just punch her.
Pardon?
Well, you shouldn't use violence...
Sorry.
Could you be talking to me?
Of course l am.
I think you got the wrong idea.
I don't worry about it so much
that l need a working girl's advice.
What do you mean?
Look at your outfit,
the words you say,
isn't it obvious?
You jumbo woman!
She kept ignoring me during
residents' meetings after that.
She didn't seem as someone
who's like that to me...
People often say, "Do unto others as
you would have them do unto you,"
but it's fancy talk.
There are many people...
who do what other people did to them
to those weaker than they are.
In the world, the weaker you are,
the more awful things happen to you.
But even so, l didn't wish her dead.
But the person who drew the ballot
paper that says "Misato Akaike"...
really killed Mrs Akaike.
I want the murderer to be arrested,
but l don't want to be
dragged into trouble.
Well...
We don't have to talk
about the game,
the police will naturally search
for the murderer.
In addition...
We are going to do what we can
and search for the murderer.
Please.
Search for the murderer.
Residents of the residential tower
who have no alibi
are these four people.
The Bhutanese diner's waitress,
and he who has connections
with gangs.
Keisuke Ukita
Ukita has been arrested for fraud
many times.
He's a smooth talker
and lies without batting an eye.
What? Are you still worrying
about the cake?
Yes.
We verified that Misato Akaike
bought it herself, right?
But the cake's chocolate plaque
is the problem.
There wasn't one.
The shop clerk said
they didn't forget to put it there.
Maybe it was eaten.
Maybe if someone killed for you,
it becomes your turn to kill.
Did Xinyi kill Misato?
Xinyi?
It's Tezuka.
- Is this okay?
- Yes.
The stairway is right there.
- Please wait a second.
- Okay.
Is this okay?
- Yes, okay.
- Good.
We'll go down the stairs.
Slowly, please.
- Be careful near the corners.
- Okay.
Sanae.
Someone is moving?
I think he is old Mrs Akaike's
relative.
The old lady will enter
an elderly home with caring service.
Well, l guess she wouldn't want
to return to the flat.
- I'll put it here.
- Thank you...
lt's Mr Etou.
I didn't know he was friends
with the Akaike family.
Mrs Akaike, why don't you try it?
I'm sure that you'll look good!
- It is amazing!
- Really?
It really suits you!
Nana.
Will you be available
on the next holiday?
Let's have a break from this
and have lunch together.
You can invite your husband.
English for Beginners
Recruiting theatre group members
You're lying in bed again.
I thought you had gotten
a bit better.
I'm not lying here.
I'm training my muscles.
What is it this time?
I'll stop worrying about it.
From now on, l'll do what l want.
You should do so too.
What happened?
Don't think about what happened.
Think about what will happen.
No. Think about what will happen
because of my own actions.
That's the important thing, right?
Don't ask me to agree with you
so forcefully. l don't know.
I will do it!
Touo University Hospital
Now Trend
Account: Good Doctor
Log in
Good Doctor
Yutaro Yamagiwa
is the medical industry's disgrace
l can't feel sorry enough
for Yutaro Yamagiwa's patients
lf you have no motive,
you won't even be suspected, right?
When Yutaro Yamagiwa was a student,
he was just a loser.
Delete account
Are you sure that you want
to delete the account?
Yes
Murderer...
Murderer
What the heck?
Sorry, he suddenly said he wanted
to go somewhere first.
Don't worry about it.
Welcome.
Look, he's here.
I... l'm meeting with someone.
- Please come with me.
- Okay.
Sorry, l am late.
You...
Excuse me, this table isn't big
enough for all of you.
We won't dine here.
I see.
Sorry.
How can we help you?
I said l was going to meet you,
then they...
We want to ask why you deny us
from attending
the residents' meeting.
It's our fault
that we didn't attend it,
but not attending and not allowed
to attend are different matters.
Do we have to talk here?
I don't want someone to use violence
on me in a locked basement room.
Violence?
Just say what you want and let's go.
I heard that...
you played a dangerous game
at the residents' meeting.
- What?
- Yes?
You promised not to say it!
Sorry, l break promises.
You knew?
- Well...
- What is going on?
Will you explain to us?
In the end, they just hate us.
Telling them that we know
about the game is enough for today.
First of all,
nobody told us anything.
- Right?
- Yes?
What is it?
Nothing.
Hello.
Hay fever?
This is really delicious, isn't it?
Yes, it is very delicious.
How long are you going
to keep quiet?
I don't know what and how
l should tell you now.
I see.
That's true.
It's okay. Tell me when you can.
I'm sorry.
Actually...
l have a present for you, Nana.
Look!
Exchange diary.
If there is something that you want
to tell me but don't know how,
you can write on it from now on.
Sorry, l made you worry.
I hid it from you
and it was my fault.
It's okay. lt's totally okay.
And I'm sorry that...
Yes?
I am too old to exchange diary
with someone.
I see...
l'll use it myself, then.
Can l continue?
When did you find out?
Ono told me a while ago.
Shota, are you okay?
I was wondering how much
the other people knew,
so l asked Miss Kinoshita.
Then it became something serious.
I didn't want to make you worry.
If l had told you,
you'd do everything to deduce it
and probe into this.
It had never occurred to me
that someone would actually die.
Anyway, l thought l didn't have
to tell you at first,
but before l realised it,
the matter became so serious
that l didn't know how to tell you.
Don't talk so much.
Yes?
You only have to tell me
to trust you and l will.
I trusted you
even before you told me.
I'm sorry.
But in return,
l'll trust you
even if you lie to me.
I trust everything you say.
Because to me,
everything you say is true.
That's how much
I'm prepared to trust you.
I'm not hiding anything.
Trust me.
Okay. l trust you.
All right...
Then...
Let's do it!
Let's do what?
Well, we're married, but there was
a secret between us for a while,
so now, we should hide nothing
from each other
and reveal our bare selves
to each other.
It's the shortcut to making up.
Reveal our bare selves?
Let's make love
and make each other feel good.
But Shota...
Missed call
At such a late hour...
l'll go for a jog,
then go straight to work. Shota.
Sorry about yesterday.
Are you not worried about yourself?
Why do you ask out of the blue?
If l tell you this,
you'll probably accuse me
of opening people's bin bags.
But l think this is too serious
to worry about that.
Room 302's occupant
l think you'll probably be killed.
Hello?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Sorry.
I would like to ask you something.
What is it?
Do you know the actor,
Yoshihiko Hakamada?
The Hakamada?
Yes...
This Hakamada.
Hakamada has a new girlfriend,
a dental hygienist
Of course l know him.
The one who sang the song.
That song was 20 years ago.
How do you remember it?
I often sing it at karaoke.
You are weird.
What about him?
People say
that l look a lot like him.
Indeed, Mr Kuzumi,
you do look like him.
Because of that I wrote down that...
The person l want to kill
is Yoshihiko Hakamada.
What...
Mr Hakamada, it's the extra script.
Okay.
It's embarrassing,
but people often say l look like him
since a long time ago.
As insults.
Like "Yoshihiko in the morning
after he got drunk and had ramen."
Lately, they call me Reward Card.
Also, if l say no to someone who
asks for an autograph in the street,
they tut at me.
So when l go out,
l always wear these.
Anyway, that's the only reason.
I wished Hakamada would die,
so l wrote his name.
Where is the toilet?
We are using one in someone's home
that's 10 minutes down the mountain.
I'll drive you.
It's fine. l'll find somewhere.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Don't make the hem dirty.
- All right.
So you came to tell me?
I feel horrible that our neighbours
get suspicious about everything.
So l frankly told you what l wrote,
and l want to retire from the game.
None of our neighbours...
will go to kill Yoshihiko Hakamada,
right?
What?
Wait!
That was the name l wrote,
and this is the name l drew.
But l don't know this man.
Thank you.
Asao Hosokawa
You actually keep coming,
Mr Hosokawa.
Yeah, l think l get along
with my gym trainer.
Your Turn to Kill
A new threat!
ls anyone threatening you?
You'd better not trust that person.
"Their daily life is falling apart"
Why is my life a misery?
Punch me and get fired.
This is nasty!
What is going on?
The whole thing
isn't a trap you set, or is it?