We really are going to surprise her
by waking her up.
Good morning, Nana!
Nana!
Detectives.
I am sorry to hear about your wife.
Mr Tezuka, today...
About my wife, right?
I will do anything to help.
Why don't you come up?
- Yes.
- No. We're here for something else.
We'll visit you again.
I see.
Please call me if anything happens.
Thank you.
Mr Mizuki, you said we would come
to talk to Shota Tezuka.
I feel sorry for him!
He just came home
from his wife's funeral!
Not legally married, though.
Don't talk about them like that.
Shota Tezuka has found
too many murder victims.
When you said he was suspicious,
l thought you were right,
which was unusual.
I just lost the motivation.
The man seems nice, doesn't he?
Detectives don't judge a book
by its cover.
Let's go back
and check everything again by
assuming that Shota Tezuka
was the culprit in the cases.
Okay.
Let's smile together
and we'll overcome everything.
Yeah. Thank you.
Say that you want a coffee maker
that costs 5,800 yen!
Why?
I want to share everything
in our home with you.
Make fried pork with tartar sauce
next time.
What about fried beef?
That too.
So good!
I miss you so much!
"Your Turn to Kill Special"
The match is over if you give up.
"The account is locked"
Orangutan Time.
Starts now.
"Password incorrect"
Her birthday...
The day that we started dating.
"Password incorrect"
The day we first met.
"Strange Tale of Panorama lsland"
"23rd June, 2018"
23rd June, rainy.
I met a weird boy today.
"23rd June, 2018"
"Strange Tale of Panorama lsland"
Oh, Panorama!
The novel is amazing!
The culprit was shot up
with the fireworks
and died in pieces in mid-air
at the end!
Yes?
I said, the culprit was shot--
Please don't tell me.
Don't tell me how it'll end.
l'm reading the book.
I am sorry.
But it's okay!
It's super good even if you know
how it will end,
just look forward to it.
See you.
I thought, "What's wrong with him?"
But we met again 30 minutes later.
Our gym's trainer
is wearing the sample.
- Should l ask his opinion?
- Yes, please.
- Tezuka.
- Yes?
Oh, what a coincidence!
Indeed.
I am Nana Hibino, nice to meet you.
I'm Shota Tezuka,
nice to meet you too.
Tezuka, what do you think
about the tracksuit?
Why?
Did you design this?
Yes. l would like to hear
what you think.
Sure!
It's very easy to move in this,
and it looks cool.
Like this black part here is black.
Glad to hear that.
So...
Good!
The boy was really weird.
I don't really know why,
but he liked me.
Like l can see him
wagging his tail vigorously.
He said he would lend me
the mystery books he recommends,
so we agreed to meet next week.
I am a little excited.
My tail?
30th June, sunny.
It's over 30 degrees outside
and hot,
like the rainy season never came.
The weird boy came
pretty much later than promised.
Sorry l'm late.
- Did you bring that from home?
- Yes.
It must be heavy!
Not at all.
I lied. lt's so heavy that it took
me longer than l thought. l'm sorry!
You didn't take a taxi?
I thought l should train myself.
Please have a look!
These are the mystery books
l recommend most!
Ta-da!
"Detective Conan"
Why? Could you have...
read them already?
No, l'm just a bit surprised.
I assumed they were novels.
I want to talk about them soon,
so please read them all today!
No, that's impossible.
You can, Miss Hibino!
What?
How far have you gotten?
Oh, l see.
Has the murderer
made his appearance?
Please don't tell me!
Okay.
So...
Let's focus on reading.
Say nothing about the stories
until we've both finished reading.
Okay!
"Murderer?"
Don't write on it!
I am sorry!
Is there more in the later chapters?
No.
You're lying!
Sorry. l'll check now
and erase them.
But you can't erase this.
I'm such an idiot!
I am sorry...
Tezuka always says
the most important point right away.
I don't know if we share
the same hobby or not.
He's like a cute little brother,
or a pet that
needs to be looked after.
I had such a good laugh today.
I don't remember the last time
l laughed so hard.
On the day that Shota Tezuka
moved to the condo,
the caretaker, Tokoshima, fell from
the condo's roof and died.
But it was suicide.
There was no trace of struggle
on the roof,
and the fingerprints and footprints
showed that he climbed the railing.
He had a disease too, right?
Yes, the medical report at his home
says he had a brain tumour.
Tokoshima's friend said he
complained that he would die soon.
Then this is a suicide,
without a doubt.
However,
he was tied up by a power cord
and hung outside Room 302,
and Tezuka witnessed that.
What's your point?
Maybe Tezuka could've saved him
if he wanted to.
Hey.
If you want to twist the story,
make it better.
Why do you want to make Mr Tezuka
a murderer so much?
If l am arrested,
l will tell them everything
about what you did two years ago.
I make my decisions quickly.
10th July, sunny.
Something unexpected happened.
Miss Hibino!
I love you! Please be my girlfriend!
I am sorry.
Why?
I'm the one to ask why!
You surprised me!
You shouldn't tease
someone older than you.
How can l be teasing you?
I love you.
But l'm 15 years older than you.
l've been divorced once too.
That doesn't matter.
I am serious.
Sorry.
I see...
Well, it is too sudden, isn't it?
When something occupies my mind,
l get ahead of myself.
But...
Maybe you will change your mind?
To be honest, l was happy.
But he is cheerful, honest,
young and shining.
So l thought
l was not good enough for him.
Then...
Do me a favour.
Yes! Sure...
Will you continue to be
my mystery story companion?
Yes! Yes!
I think for us, this is
the best relationship we can have.
18th July, he called me out
to the same place.
Miss Hibino!
I really love you!
Please be my girlfriend!
I am sorry!
25th July.
Would you consider being
my girlfriend?
I am sorry!
1st August.
Miss Hibino!
I love you!
8th August.
Hey, just give up
and be my girlfriend.
Sorry, forget what l said.
l'm so sorry!
14th August.
Please...
Please!
26th August.
Nana.
I really love you!
Please be my girlfriend.
I can't.
You deserve a girl younger
and better, Tezuka. Okay?
But the girl...
She isn't you,
so l refuse.
Why?
I don't understand why
you do so many things for me.
There are many reasons,
but it's because l fell in love
with you when we first met.
Is that even possible?
Your mind didn't just
trick you temporarily?
A person is at the mercy
of this part and this part,
so l had considered
that possibility too.
But now...
l don't just want to read "Conan"
with you,
l want to read the last chapter
of "Conan" with you.
That's what l think...
That means...
l love you, doesn't it?
Sorry, l can't.
Don't say you can't!
The match is over if you give up.
You were in the basketball club?
I was.
I was too!
But l was the manager.
This is fate, isn't it?
I fell in love with you right away,
and we're destined to be together!
We have to be a couple!
Don't be absurd.
It isn't absurd!
Gosh, all right!
Yes!
The 31st time of Tezuka's
unstoppable attempts...
Sorry.
I finally said yes.
Yes!
I will never meet another man
who loves me so much again.
I had this feeling.
This time, l have to properly ask
my ex to submit the divorce form.
I asked Asao about the divorce form,
but he avoided
talking about it again.
He hinted indirectly that
he would terminate our contract.
I shouldn't compromise
when he plays dirty.
Nana...
She has been worrying about it
since that day?
Okay, next. We'll talk about
Dr Yamagiwa's murder.
Okay.
According to the actress whom
the victim Yamagiwa dated,
on 5th April at around 10:00 pm,
when she was on her way
to Jonanjima in Ota City,
where she usually met Yamagiwa,
Yamagiwa texted her and said
he wanted to meet somewhere else,
and she couldn't
get hold of him since.
Sanae Enomoto probably
followed Yamagiwa from the hospital
Yes, and she killed Yamagiwa there,
put him into her car and got away.
I did some digging
and found the car was disused.
The actress didn't call the police
because it was scandalous,
and there was no CCTV
near the crime scene.
The local police and Kanagawa's
prefectural police were at a loss,
then the attempted murder happened.
Run!
Sanae Enomoto still said nothing?
She's silent about the murder
and disposal of the corpse.
She's an ordinary housewife
and isn't a patient,
why does she hate a doctor
who appears on TV so much,
that she had to kill him?
Grudge for no reason?
Actually, the Doctor Fujii
who lives on the same floor
had been friends with Yamagiwa
since college.
It's more reasonable
if this guy killed him.
But even if Fujii has a motive,
he couldn't have asked
a weak housewife to kill for him.
9th September, sunny.
I came up with a plan to stop Shota
from telling me how stories end.
Which film should we watch?
Which one do you like?
I'll watch anything.
Choose one you like.
In that case...
This one?
l've been wanting to watch it.
This? The taxi driver is a serial
murderer and you'll be so surprised!
Okay.
I'll go home today.
Nana, l'm so sorry...
Goodbye.
No. l am really, really sorry.
You don't have to forgive me,
but at least say "see you" instead.
Okay.
- Shota.
- Yes.
When you want to tell me
how it ends, ask me a question.
Ask me, "Do you know how it'll go?"
Then...
"Next Conan's Hint!"
"The taxi driver
is a serial killer!"
You said it.
Sorry.
Okay, let's call it
"Orangutan Time."
Orangutan?
- You don't know?
- No.
Orangutan Time starts now.
What does the orangutan
in "Orangutan Time" refer to?
All right...
Next Conan's Hint!
Read
"The Murders in the Rue Morgue."
Okay.
20th September, rainy.
Orangutan Time!
Who do you think the murderer is?
All right...
l think it's the niece
of the butcher's wife.
She's the most unlikely suspect!
3rd October, sunny.
Nana...
- Orangutan Time.
- Why? About what?
It can be anything,
let me play Orangutan.
What are you talking about?
You want me to make you guess?
Yes, l think l'm addicted
to Orangutan Time.
But that wasn't why l invented it.
Okay, then...
32, 85, 13, 41.
What is it?
A cipher.
32, 85, 13, 41.
What does the sequence mean?
All right,
l'll decrypt it right away.
32, 85, 13, 41...
- A clue!
- Yes, please.
I am 51, 51.
- "I am?"
- Yes!
51, 51... Come...
Maybe Shota was still a little boy.
No! Hang on. 51... Come... What?
10th October, cloudy.
By the way, Shota,
your birthday is on the 19th.
Wow! You remember?
You're so dramatic.
What do you want for birthday?
Orangutan Time!
What do l want for my 34th birthday?
- Running shoes!
- No.
- Dumbbell?
Protein!
Your guesses aren't accurate today.
- Give up?
- Hang on.
- You have 10 more seconds!
- Wait!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0!
Oops, time's up!
The correct answer is...
Marry you.
What l want is your future.
Please marry me.
Sorry...
l'm very happy...
but l can't.
Why?
Yeah.
Why, indeed.
All right! Orangutan Time.
I promise, l'll solve the mystery
and propose properly to you again.
I'm so sorry.
Nana?
Wait... Nana, what's wrong?
Actually, l was very happy.
But my ex still wouldn't submit
the divorce form.
I cannot waste Shota's time anymore.
11th October, rainy.
"I enjoyed our time together.
Thank you."
"Nana!"
"Nana..."
Are you okay, Mr Tezuka?
I don't even know where Nana lives.
What...
Mr Tezuka?
This is no good.
I shouldn't do this.
I am Shota Tezuka,
the man who never gives up.
I want to give up.
The explosion at the Bhutanese diner
isn't related
to the series of murders!
The gas pipe was cut
somewhere unnatural,
but the fire was too vigorous to
judge if it was cut intentionally.
The waitress and a regular customer
live in that condo,
it's near, so it's reasonable.
Tezuka doesn't have
much connection with this,
can we rule out the possibility
of him having committed this?
Okay, next.
Well then...
The murder of the condo's residents,
Misato and Goro Akaike.
The case is full of mystery.
No footprint on the balcony,
the murderer could only go in
and escape from the entrance.
The intercom only recorded the four
people who found the bodies.
It's possible that the record
was deleted.
In the flat, fingerprints
of many residents were found.
It was terrifying.
The murderer only let the old lady
live. lt doesn't make sense.
Judging from the blood stain,
Misato Akaike's throat was cut
from behind when she was standing.
If she bled so much,
no wonder the candles on the cake
went out.
The murderer sat her on the chair
after they killed her
and lit the candles again.
Why did they do that?
It's terrifying if l understand
what a bloodthirsty killer thinks.
For example,
it's the opposite of birthday,
they celebrated their death?
You see, the plaque on the cake
was missing,
and the photos show that
the victims were smiling.
You have no emotion, do you?
19th October, cloudy.
Today is Shota's birthday...
and he texted me.
Orangutan Time!
Solve the puzzle
and go to a certain place!
It's the birthday present for me.
Spare some time for me today!
The clue is,
51, 51, 55, 65, 04, 25, 13.
I had no idea that Shota decrypted
my cipher the other day.
It's the pager's text input.
65,
04,
25,
13.
The destination was my...
"Numazu Minami Private High School"
high school.
Shota...
Go onto the stage.
Please.
I will shoot the ball
into the basket in one go,
give me my birthday present
if l can do it.
I wasn't good
at shooting a three-pointer.
But...
l swear, l will win this match!
But this isn't a match.
Shota, this is an important decision
in your life.
Why, of all people,
did you have to choose me,
an unworthy divorced woman
who's 15 years older?
You aren't unworthy!
Because it's you.
Nana, you often say that
you are unworthy,
but l love you for everything
you think is unworthy!
You are Nana, 15 years older
and divorced once, that's why...
l love you.
And l...
l love you more than
anyone else in the world!
That's all!
Concentrate!
Concentrate, Shota Tezuka!
I have to marry Nana
and we'll be happy
for the rest of our lives!
Okay!
It doesn't count.
Yes?
You stepped on the three-point line
when you shot it,
so l don't accept that
it was a three-pointer.
It was a regular shot.
Did l miss the basket
when l shot a regular shot?
That's not the point!
Do it again.
The match is over if you give up,
isn't it?
Yes.
I am Shota Tezuka,
the man who never gives up!
I didn't see it!
- You didn't see it, right?
- No, l didn't.
Have a break.
No, l'm okay.
Next time...
No, l mean,
l will succeed in one go.
One shot.
You flared your elbows out
more than when you first started.
You did this just now.
You're kidding!
I'll close my arms.
Can l try once?
You can, but it isn't easy.
What if it goes into the basket?
Hang on! No!
I guess l can't do it.
Whoa! Oh, no! Nana, hold on to me!
"Marry me"
l didn't shoot the ball
into the basket,
but you'll marry me, right?
I...
l'll love you forever!
Even when you become
a lovely old lady
and l become a feeble old man,
and we can't dribble
or shoot a ball,
l still want to be with you.
Please marry me.
Yes.
Yes!
I want to be with him forever.
That's what l thought too.
"I want to be with him forever.
That's what l thought too."
Nana, can l ask for
my birthday present next year now?
Sure. What do you want?
I want to see you
in a wedding dress!
No! l won't wear it.
I want to see it!
What?
"Marry me"
They started falling like dominoes.
Yes.
The severed right leg of
Room 102's Kayo Kojima
was put in a golf bag
and sent to her husband.
Room 201's Keisuke Ukita was
strangled to death in a reuse shop.
Room 101's Yuzuru Kuzumi
fell in an accident
with Asao Hosokawa,
legal husband of
Room 302's Nana Tezuka,
and is now unconscious.
A man in his 20s
sent Kayo Kojima's golf bag.
It's possible that Tezuka
was thought to be in his 20s,
but the man who sent it
was 170 centimetres tall,
so it wasn't him.
You won't say Shota Tezuka
could have half crouched?
He carried the golf bag to send it
and walked like this?
Of course he wouldn't have.
You made fun of me?
When Ukita was killed,
Tezuka was at work,
so Tezuka couldn't have killed him.
He was the most suspicious
in Asao Hosokawa's case.
He was the man whom Tezuka
has the clearest reason to kill.
Impossible!
He fell with Kuzumi in an accident.
Tezuka could've manipulated Kuzumi.
You won't have trust issues
with people?
On top of that,
he witnessed the condo's resident,
Junichiro Tamiya's former colleague,
Takafumi Kono's murder afterwards.
It was just by chance!
"Do you find so many Pad Thai
by chance?"
That's what you said.
That's why we're checking
the facts again now.
Is that how l speak?
I'll pay attention.
And then...
Someone poisoned Nana Tezuka
and murdered her.
Nana!
Shota Tezuka was hospitalised,
staying at the hospital
is the best way to make up an alibi.
He could pretend that he couldn't
move and sneak out late at night,
then kill his beloved wife.
Jerk, are you really
a flesh and blood human?
Just look at this.
My hunch as a detective tells me
that he isn't the murderer.
There's no physical evidence,
we only found circumstantial
evidence to make a tableau.
Saying Shota is the mastermind
behind the series of murders is...
impossible!
Let's have supper.
Even as a game,
there's something wrong with this.
20th January, cloudy.
Because of Shota's earnest request,
we had hot pot for supper.
Oh?
We've eaten all the meatballs?
Where are they?
Shota, you've only been
eating meatballs,
so they're all gone.
I won't give up.
There should be one hidden.
I'll give you mine.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Great!
So good!
There are odd folks
who don't like hot pot,
but l don't get it at all.
Because hot pot is warm, delicious,
enjoyable, nutritious,
and makes you happy.
Isn't it the best?
But l didn't understand
why people like hot pot.
What?
Sorry.
It's okay,
because l understand it today.
Nana!
Our wedding rings are made!
It's my 49th birthday.
I thought
it wasn't worth celebrating,
but Shota went all out
to celebrate it for me,
so l'm happy.
We bought a flat.
It shows my determination.
I will definitely get him
to submit the divorce form.
Shota said something wonderful
to me.
"We'll change many times
and we'll like each other
after we have changed
and we will fall in love
again and again."
Even if we both change
and become someone different
from who we are now,
l will still fall in love with you.
We'll change many times
and we'll like each other
after we have changed,
and we will fall in love
with each other again and again.
"We will fall in love
again and again"
"You have a new email"
"Open"
"Joli Chapel: Booking Confirmed"
This is...
"Mrs Nana Tezuka,
another booking has cancelled,
so your booking is accepted."
"On 19th October, 2019"
Can l ask for
my birthday present next year now?
Sure. What do you want?
I want to see you
in a wedding dress!
No! l won't wear it.
"Groom: Mr Shota Tezuka
Bride: Mrs Nana Tezuka"
Nana in a wedding dress...
l wish l could see it.
"To Shota"
What?
"Dear Shota,
l'm sure that
when you are reading this,
l'm not there with you.
I wish l could be with you for
longer, until l am 100 years old.
As you said the other day,
l wish we could grow old together.
We're going to change,
and we'll like each other
after we have changed,
and fall in love with each other
again and again.
If there is a next life,
l want to meet you again
and fall in love with you.
This time,
l won't lie to you
or hide anything from you,
and l want to be your wife for real.
Nana...
l don't say this often,
because l'm too shy,
but l love everything about you.
Like, you frolic like a puppy,
work hard seriously
as a trainer at the gym,
you become friends
with our neighbours right away,
and your habit of scratching
your right chest when you lie.
You thought l didn't know, did you?
"You thought l didn't know,
did you?"
Nana...
lt isn't her?
Shota, you scratch your right chest
every time you lie.
"Warning"
What is going on?
"Oh, you realised? That's what
l expect from a man who loves Nana.
So l have a present for you!
Please accept it"
What?
Now, choose one.
Nana...
Will you choose the elephant
or the giraffe?
Giraffe.
I see.
It's your last moment,
so please smile.
There's something you want
to say to your husband, right?
Excuse me,
please look at the camera.
Shota...
l...
"Your Turn to Kill"
Let's not mention the murders again.
Nothing has been solved!
I've brought the new resident here.
I study artificial intelligence.
Please profile the murderer.
I'm excited.
I take back what l said.
I'm totally prepared
to take revenge.