"Everyone must have someone
they want to kill."
l think this is what started it.
We wrote the names
of the people we want to kill
and showed each other secretly.
Right after that...
The name l wrote
was Yutaro Yamagiwa.
People are murdered
one after another...
The name l wrote on my piece of
paper was Misato Akaike.
I wrote Yoshihiko Hakamada.
The name l wrote on the piece
of paper was Mrs. Kayo Kojima.
We should tell the police.
I won't be arrested, will l?
Make sure
you don't tell other detectives.
I won't kill just because
l got a threatening note.
Who did this?
I'm suspecting someone.
I'll try to get an answer myself.
People are cornered, but still...
Ukita?
And the man whose name l wrote...
l've been doing lift maintenance
for 20 years!
l guess this is it.
I will die.
"I really loved you,
but the way l loved you was wrong."
"l'm sorry..."
Darn...
l don't want to die
when she still hates me.
Ouch...
Sorry, Jessie.
It isn't your fault.
- Yes?
- Sorry for coming so early.
Please come to the police station
with us.
Shota...
He's dead.
What?
He...
He died.
What?
"Tokyo Metropolitan Police Hospital"
We did our best to save him.
Don't worry about me...
it's okay to cry...
Hey, bring her with us now.
But that's her husband...
The woman could've killed him.
Sorry, but it's time to go.
Okay.
- Nana...
- l'll be okay.
A horrible wife
who requested someone
to kill the husband she divorced.
"Murder-swap, please!
Kill him for me
and l'll kill for you in return."
"Murder-swap, please!"
"Your Turn to Kill"
"Room 102, Kayo Kojima murdered
Room 201, Keisuke Ukita murdered
Victims fell down the lift
in Hikifune Warehouse
Reinvestigation
on property manager's suicide"
"Series of murders
at Kuramae's condo"
They are cursed.
All right, where should we begin?
Maybe from whether we should
investigate it with Kuzumi's case?
Is his job related
to the crime scene in any way?
Sir, Kuzumi works
at a lift maintenance company,
he was responsible for the
maintenance of the lift there.
He could tamper with it
if he wanted to?
The security camera was broken,
so we don't know the details.
However, Kuzumi's toolbox
was left at the crime scene.
By the way,
Kuzumi's subordinate said
that he was pretty obsessed
with lifts.
Obsessed with lifts!
He regularly fiddles with the lift
in the condo he lives in for fun.
Dear me...
He'd make the lift silent
when it arrives
and says that
"Angelina became modest."
What? He names the lifts?
I guess he didn't have any friends.
For now, we can't verify whether
it was intentional or an accident.
In that case,
we have to start with her.
"Suspect, Nana Tezuka"
ls Mr. Hosokawa her brother
or her husband?
He's still married
with Nana, legally.
I called him Big Bro
without knowing that.
Someone wrote on a forum
to ask for someone to kill Big Bro,
so the police suspects
that Nana wrote it.
And Nana is still in custody today?
Someone murdered another person
and put Nana through this.
You borrowed someone's smartphone,
wrote you want a murder-swap,
and put Mr. Hosokawa's photo
on the forum.
I told you, l--
A week after the first message
was written,
Mr. Hosokawa himself
called the police,
and without a doubt,
you are the murderer.
However, that evening,
Mr. Hosokawa was involved in a fall
with your friend, Yuzuru Kuzumi,
and died there.
I did not write that message.
Did Yuzuru Kuzumi read this message?
I don't know.
I already told you yesterday.
You've been separated for years
but he didn't agree
to get a divorce,
so you wanted to murder him...
l've answered this question
many times as well!
We were taught to ask
the same questions again and again.
Why is that?
Tell her why.
Because if you are lying,
we'll gradually see a hole in it
if we ask over and over again.
Is that the reason?
And? Have you found any hole
in what l've told you?
We haven't.
- Then...
- Come on!
Do you know how many people
who lived in your condo died?
Let us investigate it thoroughly.
But it's the game...
That's how tricky the case is,
make sure you don't tell
another detective.
I'm here because l want to help.
I did nothing suspicious...
Sir!
You scared me!
l died for two seconds!
- Sorry, sir, but...
- What is it?
Is there any connection
between Mr. Kuzumi's accident
and Mr. Ukita's death?
By the way, who among these
three people wrote Mr. Ukita's name?
Three people?
Well...
lf Mr. Ukita was killed...
that means among Mr. Tamiya,
Miss Ono and the caretaker,
one of them
wrote Mr. Ukita's name, right?
Yes, you're right.
Who do you think it is?
"301, Ono"
"Caretaker, Tokoshima"
Mr. Tokoshima?
Why?
Among the three,
Mr. Tokoshima wasn't really
on good terms with Mr. Ukita.
- I see.
- No matter who wrote it,
the people who could've drawn
Mr. Ukita's piece of paper were...
Mr. Tamiya, Xinyi, Miss Ono,
Mrs. Akaike and the caretaker.
There are five people.
But Mrs. Akaike and the caretaker
are dead,
so the people who could've killed
Mr. Ukita are...
Mr. Tamiya...
Xinyi...
and Miss Ono.
l...
Miss Ono.
Sorry for saying something
l shouldn't the other day.
When someone dumps me like this,
l'm scary.
It isn't enough as an apology,
but this is a massage oil
made with natural ingredients.
It's good for your skin
and it makes you calm too.
Oh, but you see...
l won't give you this.
If l give it to you,
you will turn a cold shoulder
to me again.
No, Miss Ono--
So l'll apply it on you now.
What? Why?
No, thank you!
- Don't bother...
- Don't move.
Wait...
What?
He gave it to you?
The caretaker made it himself.
Were you and Mr. Tokoshima
close friends?
We hadn't really spoken.
What about Mr. Ukita?
Why do you ask?
Well, because...
You suspect everything
when you're tired.
No, that's not what l mean.
Pressing on the acupressure points
makes your body and mind relax.
- Hey, are you sure?
- Yes, sir.
We found the owner of the smartphone
used to write the forum's request,
a man spoke to her
when she was jogging...
He cried and said it was urgent,
so l lent it to him.
The characteristics of the man...
He looked exactly like the man...
You see,
the man who just passed away...
Oh, Yoshihiko Hakamada!
- What?
- The description of his outfit
also matched Kuzumi's clothes.
So Kuzumi borrowed a phone
and wrote the request to kill
Mr. Hosokawa on the forum?
Why?
We don't know his motive.
I guess it's quicker
to wait for Kuzumi to wake up.
"Sumida Police Station"
Excuse me.
I guess you've already realised.
I did not tell anyone
about the murder-swap.
What?
You're investigating it alone?
Yes. l...
lf you investigated properly,
Mr. Ukita...
and Mr. Hosokawa didn't have to die!
I'll talk to other detectives.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
This is because...
there's a problem.
- Problem?
- Yes.
I hope didn't say anything
you shouldn't.
Will you give me a break?
Were you tailing me?
I'm here just by chance.
This coincidence might happen again.
I didn't tell her anything.
Then l won't say anything either.
Ouch...
lt hurts...
How are you?
Have you gotten used
to life in hell?
Why did he go to hell?
He could've gone to heaven.
Don't drink during the day.
Heaven, huh?
He was nice to us,
but in other people's eyes,
he was evil.
That's true.
What is this?
Mr. Ukita loved it.
I know, but bring him a fresh one.
Idiot!
Mr. Ukita loved one that's soft
after being put in the fridge
overnight.
Who killed him?
"Penguin Moving Company"
This is none of your business,
Mrs. lshizaki.
It is my business.
Why?
Because l want to run away too!
What?
Well...
Ms. Kitagawa is going to move away!
What do you say?
What can l?
She wants to run away alone!
We're all accomplices!
Excuse me, what should we do?
- Please carry this outside.
- Sure.
You can't!
- You...
- Wait!
- Cut it out!
- l won't let you escape!
Hey! What are you doing?
It's your fault!
Who got the piece of paper
with my name on it?
What are you doing?
I'm going to be killed!
And it's her fault!
If you're so worried,
why don't you move away too?
Shut up!
I bought my flat!
We have to pay the mortgage
for 20 more years!
Sell it, then!
How can l sell it?
lt's a murderers' condo!
- So this is the rumoured...
- What?
See? There's rumour going around
about it!
Sora.
I think Sora fell from his scooter.
What?
Are you okay?
Sora?
Please wait for a moment.
Sure...
l'm sorry.
- Thank you.
- No worries.
Sora, come.
What happened?
It doesn't matter.
When is this going to stop?
As we told you the other day,
the detective, Mr. Kamiya--
ls that guy doing his job
properly?
He won't tell us
the results of the investigation,
maybe the police will suddenly catch
the murderer tonight.
Yes, maybe, but...
Anyway, let's calm down, okay?
I'm home.
Thanks for having me.
See you.
Nana!
I'm home.
I would've gone to pick you up
if you had told me.
Sorry, l was tired.
Then you should've called
all the more.
What's the matter?
I need the energy
to ask for help too.
I was too tired
to ask for your help.
Don't say that...
What have you been doing?
What did you do at Miss Ono's flat?
Sorry... l was asking what name
Miss Ono wrote and drew...
Sorry,
please don't talk about that now.
I'll go and lie down.
Sorry, l have to go alone.
Don't worry about it, his relatives
will probably be present.
Are you okay?
Your eyes are swollen.
See you later.
If this is for Nana,
l'll do anything.
It's none of your business!
But it's what you saved
for your retirement...
Hello. l would like to talk
about the name you wrote and drew.
Go back inside.
- I haven't finished--
- l said, go back inside!
Are you doing what you did before?
When will you stop nagging me
about my last job?
You're the one who...
Drama is just a hobby, okay?
lt isn't your job--
- Sorry about that.
- lt's okay.
How can l help you?
- The name you wrote--
- l don't want to say it.
Why?
Because l've just found
my life's purpose, that is, drama.
I don't want anything else
to take up my time. See you.
Please don't go yet!
Please tell me.
Knowing all the names is the answer
to solving the problem.
Don't you think?
I think it will let you concentrate
on your life's purpose too.
I don't get
why you assume this pose.
This pose is tougher than kneeling,
and it shows how serious l am.
Please help me!
People will laugh at you.
Please.
Do be careful.
You're just like who l used to be.
What?
You have more passion than other
people, but you go in the wrong way.
You'll only
bring other people trouble.
It's fine if you only cause trouble,
but they'll ridicule you
as a workaholic,
spread rumours about you,
and eventually, you'll be cornered
and have to retire early...
l digressed.
Could you have written the name
of a former colleague?
Please tell me!
It was my subordinate.
I wrote the name of a man
called Takafumi Kono.
On the paper l drew,
the name written was Takafumi Kono,
in Hiragana.
I taught him
with all the experience l had.
I was proud of this subordinate.
Thank you for telling me.
Also, on the piece of paper l drew,
it says, "Someone who can't
sort rubbish properly."
Thank you.
I won't laugh at you.
Good luck with your search
for the murderer.
"Manager's office"
Excuse me.
Room 304's Ms. Kitagawa...
They moved away yesterday.
I see.
Do you know where they moved to?
I didn't ask.
Of course.
But l can tell you
where she works.
There you go.
It's a secret.
I'll now reply to messages from our
listeners. lt's Sumika Kitagawa's...
Oh, it's Grooving Jam
hosted by Ms. Kitagawa, right?
How do you know
such a local radio station?
Why do you know, then?
I looked up data of everyone here.
Ms. Kinoshita, you use
your real name at work too, right?
No, that isn't me.
- Oh, and...
- Yes?
You didn't wipe the earphone
before you put it in your ear.
It makes me fall in love with you.
The matter has gotten too serious.
We should keep a low profile.
I'll apologise for the knife.
"It is your turn to kill"
l'll also forgive you for hacking
into my computer at the hospital.
What are you talking about?
India is an lT superpower now,
isn't it?
I am Bangladeshi.
The one who is familiar with lT
is the illegal immigrant here?
You really made all the threats?
What? You want to punch me?
Do it, then.
Don't actually punch me!
l'll call the police!
You punched in a way
different from Japanese.
Both of us will be in trouble
with the police.
In that case...
tell me who it was.
What?
Was it Mr. and Mrs. Akaike?
Or was it Yoshihiko Hakamada?
Who was it?
Tell me.
What was revealed about this case?
The murder was committed
by several people.
It must've come to a dead end.
Yutaro Yamagiwa's head
still hasn't been found.
I'm not in charge,
but my stomach hurts.
Reports about two cases
caused a stir,
that's why nobody pays attention
to ours and it helps a lot.
If someone is arrested...
people will pay attention to it.
And they will come out at once.
Prepare yourself. We can't afford
to arrest the wrong person.
But we haven't made any progress
on the cases of Mr. and Mrs. Akaike
and Kayo Kojima,
who is only a leg now.
We'll be in trouble at this rate.
I got a report from the forensics
about Ukita's death.
What is it?
They found something interesting
about the footprint
left at the crime scene.
Sorry for asking you
to gather on a holiday.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay, this is better
than being alone at home.
Yes, it makes me feel safer.
Something is bothering me.
It's unusual for people to write
a name of someone they want to kill,
did you do it as a prank?
No. Only a few people
actually wanted to do it.
Everyone else was reluctant.
I probably stopped talking
halfway through.
Someone might complain
if we didn't write a name,
there was an awful tension
in the air.
I see.
In the midst of it, isn't it weird
that a piece of paper was blank?
If someone did this,
someone might demand to know
who didn't write a name down.
Why didn't Ms. Kitagawa say
that the piece of paper was blank
and someone cheated at that time?
Indeed.
Now l'm curious after you said this.
Isn't this curious?
Yes, indeed.
Usually, footprints aren't left
at a place like this.
Maybe when the murderer strangled
Ukita with a piece of wire...
they stepped on it!
So this is the murderer's...
- How long is it?
- 26.5 centimetres.
It's an average shoe size for men.
If it's a woman, she is quite tall.
But that alone won't tell us much.
You want to say Ms. Kitagawa lied
just based on that?
Kuroshima said the other day
that it was possible
that some people among us lied.
Yes, but l didn't mean Ms. Kitagawa.
She could've prepared
the blank paper afterwards,
it also prevented her
from digging her own grave
by saying a false name
and being asked in detail.
But it's just a thought, right?
Well, some people didn't give
a specific name as well,
and l suspect all of them.
You mean...
"People who
don't give up their seat..."
"402, Enomoto"
And Oda Nobunaga as well.
And "Someone who can't
sort rubbish properly."
l asked Mr. Tamiya.
The name he wrote
was Takafumi Kono.
- Is it...
- Yes.
And on the piece of paper he drew,
it says, "Someone who can't
sort rubbish properly."
ln other words,
Ms. Kitagawa, Mr. Tamiya,
Kuroshima and l lied.
Is that what you mean?
Yes, this is possible.
Wait!
I'll talk about this
from a different angle.
For now, people whom we don't know
what name they wrote are...
Miss Ono and the caretaker.
The names that we don't know
were drawn by whom
were Mr. Ukita and the caretaker.
In other words...
The names written by Miss Ono
and the caretaker
were either Mr. Ukita
or the caretaker.
Correct.
But l think it's unlikely
for the caretaker
to write his own name,
so Miss Ono wrote the caretaker
and the caretaker wrote Mr. Ukita.
In that case,
now we have filled
the "name written" column.
Nobody wrote what was written on
the pieces of paper you two drew.
What is going on?
Wait, you see...
Ms. Kitagawa and Mr. Tamiya too...
So l want to ask
the two of you first.
I know you have alibis of when
murders happened in our condo,
but in Mr. Ukita's case...
What did you do on that day?
Don't suddenly
treat us like suspects.
I'm sorry.
But when l was organising the facts,
l found that it is also
a possibility.
It's just a possibility,
but Ukita could've been involved
in the gangsters' fight.
But the gang that Ukita belonged to
didn't function as an organisation.
I've checked people whom Ukita knew.
He used to steal produce
from farms and orchards
and put them on black market,
then he'd gain the margin
of the sale.
It was quite cheap as a thug's job.
He hasn't been paying
his flat's rent either.
What bothers me
is Mr. and Mrs. Akaike's murder.
Why?
They didn't live in luxury,
but they were pretty rich.
Also, Ukita had no alibi on the
night the Akaike couple were killed.
Ukita and the other two killed
Mr. and Mrs. Akaike for money,
they had a fight when dividing
the money and Ukita was killed?
If that's the case,
the people who killed Ukita...
were these two?
I think one of the four people here
killed Mr. Ukita.
"Enomoto, Kuroshima,
Tamiya, Kitagawa"
This mostly hit the bull's eye.
Wait, Shota.
What about Mrs. lshizaki?
The name, Yoshimura,
which Mrs. lshizaki said she drew,
wasn't written by anyone.
But Mrs. lshizaki wrote her own name
and she's scared
that she'll be killed,
so l don't think she lied.
That means...
Yes, somebody lied
about what name they wrote as well.
If Mrs. lshizaki wrote her own name,
then the caretaker
could have written himself too.
Who would use an honorific
when writing their own name?
It is a possibility.
It's rude to suspect the ladies
when we aren't exactly sure.
Well, l threw away
the piece of paper,
so l don't know how to prove
that l didn't lie.
But the names written
by the caretaker and Mrs. Akaike
are only a deduction, right?
Exactly.
Look, we don't know the names here
for sure too.
Yes, about Miss Ono.
I made a desperate effort to ask,
but she didn't tell me.
See? There are too many holes
in the deduction, right?
Is that so?
I thought l hit the bull's eye...
l'm sorry/ l'll deduce this again.
If everything will be solved
in the end,
l don't mind being suspected at all.
Okay. l might suspect
the two of you again...
because l want to protect Nana.
Okay.
Frankly, l get overwhelmed easily,
and l think there will be times
that l can only see Nana,
so l'm really sorry,
please forgive me.
I'm so sorry!
Sanae and Kuroshima
must be secretly angry with me.
Of course, l know you are too.
I think they are angry
and l think they're hurt
because you suspected them.
Sorry.
However...
l don't know if l should speak
for Sanae too.
Why?
I couldn't say it
because l was afraid to.
The detective told me
something unusual.
What? You couldn't say anything back
after he said that much?
What should l have said back?
It is true that l lied.
Don't say you lied.
That wasn't a lie.
No.
What we also do, we do out of love!
If they find out
the various things about us...
it'll make our family seem
like we haven't got as much love
as that couple.
It's frustrating!
But that's...
Am l wrong?
You are right!
It happened
when he was in middle school.
So l said l'd go talk
to another detective...
- Problem?
- Yes.
I can't tell you the details,
but l found out a certain fact
about the game.
However, l concluded
that investigating the case alone
is the shortcut
to solving the problem.
What do you mean?
This meeting between you and me...
keep it a secret from Mr. Enomoto.
He keeps it a secret
from Sanae's husband too?
But we talked to them together.
He just repeated
that he couldn't tell me
more about the investigation.
He found a clue,
but couldn't tell Mr. Enomoto...
That's what l've been thinking too.
Mr. Enomoto was in the caretaker's
office at that time, right?
He didn't participate in the game.
If he was doing something...
He did it for Sanae.
I don't want to think that, but...
l think we should check out Sanae
as well.
Hang on.
I'm scared.
Just let the police
take care of the rest.
But we can't count on them!
Shota.
Fine.
You promise?
Mr. Tamiya.
Could it be here?
"TK Queen"
Very fine, isn't it?
Well...
But this place is closed, isn't it?
Of course!
I thought you were going to treat us
to lunch.
I'll treat you to something,
but it isn't food.
It's this lounge!
You mean...
We'll rent it
as our drama group's practise room.
Look, although it's small,
there is a stage.
We can even perform a short play.
My seniors,
you are all pretty talented,
if you have a place
where you can concentrate,
you can go a step further.
Oh, this is difficult.
We aren't a professional drama group
and we only do what we enjoy
when we aren't working, right?
You can aim to be pro now.
The direction we go
should be a group decision.
I'm running out of time!
What do you mean?
Anyway, l will pay
the whole sum of money.
Are we happy with that?
I'm home!
Nana!
You're late! You should've called.
l was worried.
Sorry. But l found the bank
where Mr. Tamiya worked!
Yes?
I tried to ask Mrs. Tamiya casually.
You said we would
let the police do their job.
But l meant Sanae's part.
Let's go.
No, l think we shouldn't.
Why?
We should see
what Takafumi Kono is like.
What will you do after that?
Tell him what's going on
and tell him to be careful.
What can you tell him
about the situation?
I...
But l want to protect him.
I don't want what happened
to Big Bro happen to him.
Anyway, let's just meet him.
Let's go.
Thank you very much for talking
to us about getting a loan.
Let's begin...
- Well...
- Please ask anything.
Sorry for being rude, but would you
let Mr. Kono be in charge of this?
Mr. Kono?
Yes, Mr. Kono helped my friend
on getting a loan,
we heard that he was very helpful.
I'm very sorry, but nobody
in our branch is called Kono.
If he was transferred
to another branch,
and we have to check
all the bank's branches...
Orangutan Time.
Pardon?
There was something different
about the man just now.
What is it? l give up. Tell me.
He's the only one
who's not wearing a name tag.
Please ask me anything.
Oh, did he forget to?
Excuse me,
is Mr. Takafumi Kono here today?
- Kono?
- Yes.
Let me see... Oh, he's over there.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Should l call him here?
No. Thanks a lot.
That's too much!
l can't finish it within today!
- It's easy for you.
- Will you do it for me?
- Good luck.
- All right.
Excuse me.
Mr. Kono, l presume?
Wow... Seriously?
You're so annoying.
Are you going to attack me here?
The security guard is over there.
I think you've got the wrong idea.
We're Mr. Tamiya's...
That man told me.
What is it? l will be killed?
Be careful when l go home at night?
He even gave me a book
on self-defence. lt's annoying.
We won't attack you.
lt's the opposite.
Yes, we want to see
that you're safe--
l don't care at all.
I have nothing to do with that guy
in the first place.
But Mr. Tamiya said you were
a subordinate he was proud of.
I do the exact opposite
of what he does.
He is too serious,
too honest, and too hard-working.
What is wrong with that?
Despite that,
his performance was only average.
It was too inefficient.
Inefficient?
Anyway,
don't drag me into your troubles.
Mr. Tamiya said Kono
was a subordinate he was proud of,
but he wrote Kono's name.
l think l can understand why.
Somehow it's frustrating.
I won't laugh at you.
Good luck with your search
for the murderer.
But still, we should tell him
to be careful.
I'll go and say it.
Shota!
Sorry...
l'm sorry! Sorry.
Wait, where is he?
Mr. Kono, please listen to me.
Don't actually attack me.
Pardon?
Mr. Kono!
- Mr. Kono!
- Are you okay?
Call an ambulance.
We should call the police.
He must've done it.
Hey, he did it, didn't he?
"Your Turn to Kill"
l would like to declare
that the game is over.
Totally innocent!
There is something wrong.
That means Sanae killed him.
"What is Room 402's secret?"
l hope your suspicions are wrong.
No!