"Everyone must have someone
they want to kill."
l think this is what started it.
We wrote the names of
the people we want to kill,
and secretly showed each other.
Right after that...
The name l wrote was
Yutaro Yamagiwa.
People are murdered
one after next.
The name l wrote
on my piece of paper
was Misato Akaike.
I wrote "Yoshihiko Hakamada"
on the piece of paper.
Mr Fujii has been receiving
threatening notes.
People are cornered.
It's here already?
Even so, l think we should tell
the police about the game.
All of us might be treated
as murderers for a while.
I did nothing, so l don't want to be
treated as an accomplice!
We didn't talk to the police,
And another person...
The name l wrote
was Mrs Kayo Kojima.
On the other hand, l...
l'm married to him.
Divorce her!
Nana wrote your name.
My name?
Many things are happening.
We just got involved
and are tossed about by them.
What the heck?
Who are you?
Ghost? This flat's?
The murdered couple's?
Why don't you say something?
You scare me!
- Who are you?
- You suddenly spoke! Scary!
But l live here.
l'm the caretaker here.
Starting today.
"Kojima Kids' English Class"
Let's go.
Calm down, we're only going to
talk to you.
You totally suspect me.
Let us.
It's our job to suspect people.
What's the matter?
Another person was killed.
lf l say this now,
you might think that
l'm a horrible person,
but l don't think it's my fault.
No, it isn't.
At that time too,
l didn't want to do it at all,
but everyone said we would do it.
I understand.
It was the same for me, too.
Who drew my piece of paper?
I have no idea.
We should tell the police.
- But--
- Let's tell them.
Will l be treated as a suspect?
If they do, Sora--
lf you care about Sora,
you should rely
on the police more.
But...
Mrs Kitagawa can't make up her mind.
Nana, if it is to protect you,
l don't care
what the neighbours think.
Frankly, even if l have to
cause someone trouble,
l still want to protect Nana.
It isn't the point.
I don't think this is right,
but if it is to protect Nana,
l can ignore my reputation,
social rules and everything.
Isn't it how far you're prepared to
go to protect Sora?
Let's talk to the police.
Great! Let's go right now.
Look out.
"Your Turn to Kill"
Did Sanae tell you?
My wife has the same worry too,
that you'd be arrested
for inducing the commitment
- or assisting a murder.
- Yes.
You can count on him regarding that.
I'm CID's Kamiya,
you can tell me anything.
Is it okay to think that
l won't be arrested?
Yes, as long as l'm in charge.
But some officers might treat
all the residents here as suspects,
that's how tricky this case is.
Make sure you don't tell
another detective.
Okay, we won't tell anyone.
"Nishio Recycle"
Hey.
Ukita?
We agreed not to meet
for the rest of our lives.
I know.
What are you here for, then?
If you want the money
we stole together,
l had spent all of it
a long time ago.
Your daughter wants to meet you.
What daughter?
The daughter you had
with Naoko Seno.
What?
She is 21 now
and she is going to get married.
Her future husband wants her father
to attend the ceremony,
and asked me to look for you.
You came to see me just for that?
I see. But she's just a kid
whose name l don't even know.
I don't want to get caught now.
It's Airi.
It's Airi Seno.
She's a bit unruly,
but she's a very nice girl.
Please say yes.
"Asao Hosokawa"
Please don't kill this person
by mistake!
Nana loved him so much
that she got married to him.
"It is your turn to kill"
"Killing with a knife"
"Murder by Poison,
How to Hide A Dead Body"
"lt is your turn to kill"
Sanae's husband stepped in,
and we've reported the game
to the police.
We can let the police
handle the rest.
Mr Kuzumi?
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Why didn't you tell me?
You were too late to tell me
about the game.
It was because you said
if the police found out now,
it would affect your promotion.
Well, l got someone reliable
to help me with that.
The radio is noisy.
Someone reliable?
Well, anyway,
tell the other people to
let the police handle the rest.
The radio.
Why don't you turn it off yourself?
Please participate--
Come on, please!
You're so annoying.
I'll buy this too, okay?
I didn't know that you were so kind.
Why do you care about that kid?
After Naoko gave birth
to Airi,
she asked me to babysit Airi.
You grew fond of her
just because of that?
Shut up.
Fine. You don't have to attend
the ceremony,
but will you at least
go to see her once?
Please!
Come on!
All right.
Thank you.
You can probably meet your dad.
Despite his looks,
Mr Ukita is capable.
Will we really do that?
- It's too late to get scared.
- l'm not scared!
Listen, if you want to marry me,
find my stupid dad and kill him.
Don't forget that.
But do you hate a man
you've never met before so much?
I can say that mummy was killed
by that jerk.
She worked too hard on her own,
it ruined her health
and caused her death.
"Series of murder
at Kuramae's condo"
We have verified that the leg found
belonged to Kayo Kojima.
The flat wasn't broken into, right?
If there wasn't a burglary,
could the husband have killed her?
I doubt it.
To sum up, you went to a flat
that isn't your home?
Yes, it was a close...
colleague's home.
She is a lady l can talk to
about my private matters.
In other words,
you were at your lover's home.
- Have you been listening?
- Am l wrong?
No, you are not wrong.
Her husband was at his lover's home
at the victim's EOD.
Could the lover have planned
and murdered Kayo Kojima
with the husband?
We're checking the CCTVs
in the lover's neighbourhood.
Good. Also, the body's--
What's wrong?
It makes me scared
just to hear the word "body,"
let's call a body "pad thai"
from now on.
Mizuki, how long have you been
a detective?
Hang on.
What is pad thai?
Sorry, l am late.
Kamiya, tell him what pad thai is.
Something like Thai cuisine's
fried rice noodles.
Well done.
What are you talking about?
We're saying that only the leg of
the "pad thai" is found.
What?
Where have you been anyway?
I went to check
who posted the golf bag.
You've been acting on your own
lately.
- Did you find anything?
- Yes, sir.
The handwriting on the receipt
should be Kayo Kojima's,
but a young man
brought the bag there.
He talked to me
when l was delivering parcels.
He had the invoice,
so l took the order.
I think he was in his early 20s.
Is there a man in his early 20s
among the residents?
Yes, sir.
Room 201's Ryo Kakinuma,
and Room 404's Yuki Etou.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to be killed!
No, you won't. lt's just a game.
But now Mrs Kojima
has become just a leg!
It's because she had a fight
with her husband.
You mean her husband killed her?
I have no idea, but it has nothing
to do with the game.
I'm home.
Don't just act normal!
Mummy, is supper ready?
I'm not in the mood to cook!
Don't take it out on the children.
Mr Ukita.
You...
"lt is your turn to kill"
l see.
What about you?
"It is your turn to kill"
What should we do?
What do you mean?
Mr Fujii was threatened
and he really committed a murder.
That's what l think.
I won't do it just because of
this threatening note.
Okay.
But who did this?
Exactly!
The handwriting is the same?
They're the same, aren't they?
This is strange.
Why?
There is a murder-swap.
You wrote Misato Akaike,
and l wrote Yoshihiko Hakamada,
two people drew them respectively,
and they are threatening us,
saying that it's our turn now.
I see.
"Paper drawn by: A, B"
The people who threaten us
should be two different persons,
but the handwriting on them
is the same.
What should l do?
What should you do?
Don't do anything.
Okay.
What do you mean?
To sum up,
the people who we don't know
what they wrote
are Mr Tamiya,
Miss Ono,
and the caretaker, right?
- Yeah.
But the names that
we don't know written by whom...
"Yoshimura, Oda Nobunaga"
are this many.
The order is different,
but the names written and drawn
should match perfectly.
Isn't this strange?
Why are they so different?
I think some people lied.
What for?
Also, it's possible that someone
drew their own piece of paper.
We can't be sure that
all pieces of paper were swapped.
The probability is
around 37 percent.
But maybe the deduction
that it's a murder-swap
fails in the first place.
Here. lt says Mr Ukita
killed Mr Hakamada,
but the name Mr Ukita drew
was old Mrs Akaike.
That means Mr Ukita lied?
Even so, l don't think Mr Kuzumi
killed Mrs Kojima after that.
I wrote this.
What?
So please, don't kill him.
If you say that,
nobody seems to have killed her.
My Kuzumi probably did that.
You'd better not trust him too much.
Is there anything else?
No.
Let's say something more positive.
Mrs Kojima passed away and
Ms Kitagawa wrote her name, right?
Yeah.
But the piece of paper drawn by
Ms Kitagawa was blank.
I see.
There's nobody to kill.
No. lf it's a murder-swap,
it will stop here, right?
But actually,
the order doesn't matter, does it?
Why?
Because if the caretaker didn't
commit suicide and he was killed,
the murderer didn't kill him
because it was their turn,
they just killed him.
They weren't threatened,
but they still killed someone?
What kind of person is that?
Someone who hated the caretaker
very much from the start?
Was there anybody?
Ready, start!
Are you saying that
we will really break up for real?
Yeah.
- Excuse me, the bill, please!
- l haven't finished!
We have totally finished!
Waiter, your turn.
I'm a waiter.
I'm a waiter at a pub.
I am a waiter,
the head of part-time workers.
- Mr Tamiya?
- Excuse me, l'm concentrating.
But it's your turn--
Okay, l got the idea.
Just go and act.
What?
Go and act.
You're the director, so maybe l am
teaching a fish how to swim
but whatever an actor does,
he needs a motive.
I can't come out just because
it is written in the script,
or l'll be following it blindly.
You can also say that
l am the writer's slave.
Now, l need a motive
to make my appearance here.
And your motive is
the customer asked for the bill!
You just go along with the writer
and that's your interpretation,
but l interpret it in my own way!
Start from a bit earlier. Go!
- Excuse me, the bill, please!
- Certainly, sir.
- I'll really walk you home.
- What do you want?
I am your bodyguard.
Your beloved Nana wants me dead.
Yes. lt seems that you are
the most awful jerk.
Even so, l still don't think
it's okay if you die.
An awful jerk
has the right to live, too.
By the way, Nana said there was just
one thing that she couldn't forgive,
so she wanted a divorce.
Do you know what it is?
How would l know that?
Wait, you're so upset that you're
speaking in your native dialect.
Shut up!
Tell me, stupid Big Bro!
Stupid Bro!
Nothing serious happened
for a while after that.
However...
it also means that
the murderers haven't been caught.
Kazuo, what's the matter?
I wanted to play with Yohei.
Did you have another fight with him?
No.
Yohei's mum said if he went to
my home, he would be killed
and didn't let him come.
We all think that the murderers are
among our neighbours.
We've been doubting each other
every day.
It is sorted properly.
It's not fun.
Hey.
You live in Room 401, right?
You've been cleaning the place, does
it mean l don't have to do that?
Yeah.
Lately, there is no need
to clean it anyway.
Residents here
value public morality.
I doubt it.
To make people obey the rules,
fear is the best method, right?
Lately, people here try to avoid
being hated,
and they all behave themselves.
She's so...
cute.
- The three of us?
- Yes.
I think Big Bro has calmed down
quite a lot.
I think you two can talk properly.
I think he would agree
to get a divorce now.
Sorry, too many things happened and
l put what's important behind me.
It's fine. People died.
lt's totally fine to do that later.
I'm the type who didn't do
summer homework until the last day.
They're two different matters.
When l am with you,
l am having a summer vacation
that will never end.
That's how l feel.
So 31st August doesn't come for us.
We can put everything that isn't fun
behind us.
But if l don't
finish my homework first,
l'll keep thinking about it
and l can't enjoy my vacation.
I see.
Let's talk about it, then.
l'll ask Big Bro his schedule.
Nana, smile for me once.
Just force yourself to.
Smile for me.
What the heck?
When you smile, l smile.
When l smile, you smile.
Let's smile together
and overcome everything.
Thank you.
"JG Maintenance"
Would you like salty or sweet bread?
A sweet one, please.
Okay. l'll go buy it.
"It is your turn to kill"
Who is this?
Who drew my piece of paper?
"Yoshihiko Hakamada"
Who drew it?
I don't know!
Thanks for waiting.
Oh, thanks.
- What are these?
- Yes?
I haven't seen them.
What photos are these?
It's my parents' home.
Yes?
Hey, who gave you these?
I really don't know.
You are really annoying.
Don't come to the gym
if you hate it so much.
I thought you'd hate to see me!
Will you cut it out?
I know how you feel.
If in the very unlikely case that
Nana and l have to get divorced,
l'm going to complain too.
Just like you, stupid Big Bro.
Stop calling me that!
That's how good Nana is.
Let's go, Stupid Bro.
Don't make variations!
- "Stupid Bro" is good, right?
- No!
Isn't it better than Stupid Big Bro?
It isn't!
I can't do it!
Shota.
Is it okay if l walk home with you?
You don't sound okay with it.
I am just a bit tired.
Are you going to dump me?
What?
You grew tired and you'll dump me?
Hang on, l've never--
Don't say you had never thought
l was your girlfriend!
I'll say that. l am married.
You're awful.
You see, l'm truly in love
with Nana.
I am scary.
What?
If anybody dumps me like this...
l am scary.
Wait a minute, Miss Ono.
Wait, you...
What? You've got to be kidding!
Nana...
You startled me! Welcome home.
I hit the bull's eye!
Yes?
Do you remember what l deduced
about the caretaker's death?
It was...
Maybe they were in
a romantic relationship?
Then things got ugly.
You remember?
Yes, and?
Just now, l bumped into Miss Ono
on my way home.
We talked a bit,
she really is the type that would
commit a crime of passion!
Why do you think so?
Anyway, l think we should
dig further into this.
You'll see her, right?
You promised.
Tomorrow?
All right, then.
l'll bring her there.
See you.
Daddy! Daddy!
Airi.
I'm not your daddy,
call me Mr Ukita.
Why? l want a daddy, too.
Yeah? But...
Mr Ukita...
be my daddy.
I am not your daddy.
"Master key"
What?
It's gone.
"Manager's office"
What the heck?
Hey.
How have you been?
ls anybody threatening you?
They'll set your parent's home
on fire if you don't kill?
Darn! Who is this?
I'm thinking that
it's a certain person.
I had no idea
that it would get so serious,
but l was being careful
and l did a trick
when l wrote the name.
Because of that,
l have a rough idea about
who drew my piece of paper
with "Misato Akaike" on it.
Who is it, then?
Really?
I'll go and check that now.
I am a busy man too, so l'll get rid
of the trouble quickly.
- I'll go with you.
- No.
My guess might not be correct,
so l will go alone and try to
get the truth out of them.
All right, then.
Are you both nervous?
l guess you don't know what to say.
You don't look like me.
Are you really my daughter?
Naoko had been fooling around.
Hey!
Is it Naoko's fault
that you're so ill-mannered?
Or is it yours?
Wait! Sorry, l want to talk to her.
What are you talking about?
I know why you snapped,
but you should talk--
Sorry.
I made up my mind before l came.
Hey.
Die a hundred times, you jerk!
Hey!
Mr Ukita...
You...
l am sorry!
Why?
Airi wants revenge for her mother.
Forget it. l expected this.
- Call an ambulance!
- Okay!
I'm stabbed, the ambulance crew
will call the police.
I don't care!
You should care. Yeah?
I won't let you have
a criminal record.
I'll call an ambulance myself.
You two, just leave!
Let's do what he says.
Your father...
Sorry, l didn't realise that
you hated him so much,
that you'd want to kill him.
In that case...
it can be me, right?
Yes?
Think of me as your father.
Why out of the blue?
Because...
Call an ambulance
right after we leave!
Sure. So just go now!
I'll see you at the hospital.
Sure.
When l see you at the hospital...
l will call you daddy.
Sure.
Hey.
Ukita?
Have you left?
Why did he do this?
Is it you, Ukita?
Ukita?
Hey.
Hello? Police?
Someone died in my shop's toilet.
What? lt's...
someone l don't know.
This is ridiculous...
This is my fault.
It's because
l tried to kill that jerk.
It can be me, right?
Think of me as your father.
Since a long time ago,
l have always wanted you
to be my daddy.
Mr Ukita.
Be my daddy.
Daddy!
I don't really care,
but my company told me to check.
But we aren't.
It's pointless to tell me.
What happened?
Because of what happened
to Mr Ukita,
the company found out
that they're gangsters.
What happened to him?
Isn't it too late? We all know.
- Whose funeral did they attend?
- What?
Mr Ukita's, of course.
What?
He was killed.
I will go and check it now.
Good morning.
Why don't you work somewhere
outside our flat for now?
- But--
- Go to my gym.
Work at the break room.
Okay.
- Please take this.
- Okay.
I'll go to work.
Thank you.
- Sorry that we came uninvited.
- lt's okay.
I think Big Bro will come
in the afternoon.
Okay.
Feel free to relax here.
What is going on now?
Do you think that
everything is my fault?
Why?
Of course we don't.
But Mr Kuzumi said this to me, too.
He asked if all of these
were a trap that l had set.
Do you two--
We don't think it is.
Right?
I love how gentle you are
and the smile on your face
when you are with Shota.
No, l just...
You see, a while ago...
When someone says
something horrible to me,
l say something nice
to someone twice.
So because someone said
something horrible to you,
l said two nice things to you.
Okay. Thank you.
Excuse me,
did Mr Hosokawa come today?
I haven't seen him today.
He's usually here
before his personal training time.
Idiot, l'm at the warehouse already.
Don't apologise. You shouldn't make
your managing director do it.
The ladies said they felt safe
that we could stay together.
Okay, come every day, then.
But it'll be annoying
if we come every day.
Come every day.
Come eight days a week.
What are you talking about?
What's the matter?
Well, in the end,
Big Bro didn't come.
I felt a bit relieved, though.
Is he all right?
I have absolutely no idea
where it is.
The labels? l'm looking for it.
Just stop talking and come here!
Hello.
What's the matter?
I got a bit lost.
Our company rents the whole floor,
l think it should be another floor.
"Shota Tezuka"
What's the matter?
Hello?
He hung up.
Did you mistake me for someone?
Could it be Nana's
murder-swap or something?
You know?
Calm down and think!
Do you kill just for a game?
I'll be killed if l don't kill you!
Tell the police first!
I can't count on them!
They told the police,
but Mr Ukita was killed.
Mr Ukita?
Room 201's gorilla-like...
No.
Baboon-like guy!
I don't know him!
Can you solve any problem
by killing me?
You'll only become a murderer.
If there is no motive,
nobody will find out
that it's a murder-swap.
That's when unrelated people
commit murder for each other,
but you know Nana now, right?
The plan fails because of that.
You'll only be suspected and
arrested like the usual cases.
I made the suggestion.
I intended it to be a game,
of course.
I had no idea
that this would happen!
Calm down, okay?
What am l doing?
Gosh!
I have to go, then.
Why don't you run away
to your parents' home?
If l run away,
someone is going to harm my family.
I am sorry!
Please don't tell anyone.
Pardon?
Please...
Don't tell anyone about this.
Sure, l won't.
Don't come any closer.
- I won't do anything.
- Don't move!
Sorry.
It's fine.
Oh? You, well...
You look like Mr Hakamada?
Oh, yes.
That's my only characteristic.
It isn't a bad thing.
lt's the best to be common.
Yes.
But usually people
can't kill another person.
What?
I've been doing maintenance
for lifts for 20 years!
Yes?
Excuse me, l am
Sumida Police Station's Kamiya.
- You...
- Sorry for coming so early.
Please come to the police station
with us.
"Your Turn to Kill"
- You are the murderer?
- l had no idea.
She wants to run.
All of us are accomplices!
You are free to suspect me.
It's true that l lied.
"Who is the liar?"
Please.
I don't understand
why you do that pose.