A casual conversation
led to a nasty game of writing
the names of people we want to kill
and telling each other...
The name l wrote
was Yutaro Yamagiwa!
Two people could have been killed.
You said the rule is to kill someone
if a person killed for you.
There is no such rule.
Mr Fujii has been receiving
threatening notes.
Hello, Mr Atsushi Fujii.
It is your turn to kill!
Then, there is one more.
Who is this?
Number 214, Mr Tanaka.
Mr Masao Tanaka.
The Bhutanese diner's owner?
You are Mr Masao Tanaka?
Is this over now?
Or will more people die?
It was beyond my imagination.
Explosion in Bhutanese Diner.
One Dead Body Found.
Owner, Masao Tanaka
Did gas leak cause the explosion?
ls this Masao Tanaka
the patient from the other day?
Gosh! Will you not peek?
I was just checking whether you were
watching porn again or not.
It was infected with a virus
and you got into trouble.
Really?
Yes.
The diner's owner was a Japanese man
named Masao Tanaka.
That means...
You're not thinking that
it is your turn to kill, right?
Is it possible that
Mr Fujii killed him?
There indeed was a gas leak,
and it caused the explosion.
Thank goodness...
l don't know if l should say that,
but that means
it wasn't the game, right?
But the property manager,
Dr Yamagiwa and the diner owner
all had their names written
in the game.
Isn't it too unnatural?
I agree with him.
So l drew this.
Let's say, if the property manager
didn't kill himself
but was killed by
one of the residents,
it was the turn of the person who
wanted to kill him to go to kill.
Murderer B killed the property
manager and threatened Mr Fujii
Masao Tanaka
What do you mean?
Didn't Mr Fujii say the other day...
Someone killed the person
whom you want dead,
so you have to kill the person
on the ballot paper you drew,
or you will violate the rule.
But he was joking, right?
But in fact,
Mr Fujii wrote "Dr Yamagiwa"
and after Yamagiwa was killed,
someone threatened Mr Fujii and said
it was his turn to kill, right?
If that's the case,
the person who is Murderer B
could have been threatened
by Murderer A too.
Now it has really become
a murder-swap.
It is unbelievable,
but there are too many coincidences.
So, there were 13 people
at that time,
and we exchanged ballot paper.
If Mrs Tezuka is right,
that means 10 more people...
will possibly die?
It is your turn to kill
And you wrote the owner's name?
It didn't occur to me
that he'd really be killed.
And the person who killed someone
would send scary notes that say,
"lt is your turn to kill."
And it's this one?
- Let's call the police.
- l can't. l won't!
We can't tell the police!
Because l overstayed my visa?
It's not just you, Cuong.
For everyone's sake,
we can't let the police come near.
Wait a minute.
I get it that you wrote
the owner's name.
You drew a piece of paper too,
what was written on it?
Oh, it's that person?
- You know them?
- You see, a while ago...
Please do one last thing for me.
Just one step, please give me
the final support...
Actually...
Yes?
Sorry, something frightening
just occurred to me again.
What is it?
The person written on the paper
might not be someone close to us.
Indeed.
Someone would've been killed
somewhere a long time ago.
It'll never end if we think
in a negative way, so let's stop it.
Your Turn to Kill
Episode 4
Turn your socks inside-out
before putting them in the basket.
Are you listening?
Yes, great detective.
Stop calling me that.
About the explosion
at the Bhutanese diner...
Was it really an accident?
It was a gas explosion.
Then, did you notice
that people around us...
have been dying one after next?
All right,
what does this fact tell us?
Okay, it's Orangutan Time.
I have no idea.
I'll answer it!
It means that we have reached
the level of great detectives!
You see, murders happen
wherever a great detective goes,
so doesn't it make you feel
that we've become great detectives?
Are you having fun?
Does people close to you
dying one after next amuse you?
You've been feeling down,
so l thought maybe you would
relax a bit if l said that.
I shouldn't have cheered you up
like that.
Sorry.
It's okay. Thank you.
But you can cheer me up more by
turning your socks inside-out first.
I'll do it properly.
You said that the other day too.
This time l really will.
Don't your socks turn inside-out
naturally when you take them off?
Fine, l'll do it! You're annoying.
I say this because you didn't do it.
- The cat at the carpark...
- Don't sing Natsuiro...
when you're in the wrong.
Sorry.
Nine, and just one more.
Ten.
Okay, well done.
You can let go of it now.
Okay.
What's wrong?
I am feeling down.
Obviously.
My wife hasn't been herself lately,
like she is distant.
Even so, you shouldn't show it
when you're working.
But l could instruct
the last member cheerfully.
Well, it's okay to
show your weakness in front of me.
I am sorry.
So, how has your wife been acting?
Tell me.
You'll be surprised when l tell you.
Okay.
First, something shocking
has been happening around
our residential tower.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. We're even now.
It is 1:10 pm now,
you're listening to Fan Fan J-Pop,
an old J-Pop song programme.
I am your host, Sumika Kitagawa.
You are really close.
Hello.
Misato.
Yes?
It's a good thing for you.
That you can take care of me.
It makes you look like a good wife
to other people.
You're worth nothing if you
don't have to take care of me.
You're just a big woman.
Thank you.
Your habit from working as a barmaid
shows when you thank me.
Thank you!
If you don't use your head,
the nutrients go to your body.
Sora.
Where is your mum?
She isn't home yet?
Have you had supper?
Do you want to have it with me?
No, thank you.
Let's have supper.
lt's here.
Isn't this where the
property manager jumped?
- It is.
- l'll get some salt!
We don't have enough time.
We do!
Yes, l went to the diner
regularly, but...
Has anything strange
happened lately?
We asked the waitress,
but she said she didn't remember.
Oh.
The girl can't speak Japanese
at all, so it was difficult.
"At all," you said?
Why?
That reminds me, when he came to
our hospital the other day,
he said the diner's stove was broken
and he was at a loss what to do.
When l went there after that,
l did smell gas.
I see.
By the way,
do you live here alone?
Yes, l am single.
Thank you. Let's go.
Sorry to bother you on your day off.
What are you doing? Let's go!
It's the office used by
the caretaker who jumped off here.
I know! Heaven will punish you!
The waitress who worked at
the exploded diner lives here too.
The regular customer just now
lives here too.
It's totally cursed here.
Let's run away now.
The flat just now was creepy too.
Come on.
- I forgot one person.
- What?
He lives here too.
Enomoto?
He's the head of
Community Safety Division, right?
Let's leave through the front.
I don't want to be involved
in their trouble.
Don't just say yes, seriously.
Detectives?
My husband pretended
he didn't realise they were here,
but they stood in front of
the manager's office.
That means he really
didn't commit suicide?
I don't know.
What do you think?
The police might as well
just solve the case.
Why did your husband
pretend he didn't see them?
The police officers are sticklers
when it comes to jurisdiction.
Oh? There are only a few of us?
- You're right where we want you.
- Why?
Were you involved in the explosion
the other day in any way?
Wait...
I'm not Mr Tamiya, but the fear and
suspicion is trying.
- Let's ask him openly.
- But...
You blamed me when
the property manager died too.
That was what l thought too.
How nasty of you.
So, were you?
Well...
as the diner's regular customer,
l only provided information
to the police,
and I'm innocent.
I see.
I am sorry.
I have no motive to kill
the diner owner to begin with.
If l have no motive, nobody will
even suspect me. Am l right?
Motive...
That's right.
You have no motive.
Exactly. None at all.
Okay, l won't ask anymore.
Please don't mention it
to me either.
Hello.
Sorry, we're late.
Let's have a seat.
All right, let's start our meeting.
Haven't we had a residents' meeting
the other day?
We've been having urgent ones,
but this is our regular meeting.
It's unusual that
Mr Tamiya isn't present.
He set up security cameras himself,
is that all right?
What?
It's still fine if there had been
incidents like burglaries...
He said he wanted to
make this a better place.
I asked him what he was doing.
He said he wanted to
make this place better.
He said he has aged
and wanted to make the world better
for the young people,
and it was a part of
the activities for that.
This is great.
Could Mr Tamiya have killed him?
Why?
Who did he kill?
Oh, l don't know who,
but maybe he used the cameras to
keep an eye out for the police.
Saying that he killed someone
just because he put cameras there
is jumping to a conclusion.
Yeah...
lf Mr Tamiya had killed someone,
we'll all be arrested for
committing that crime.
Inducement of murder.
Yes, that.
What are you talking about?
It seems that
if someone dies in the game,
it's possible that everyone involved
will be just as guilty.
This is unreasonable!
I have no such intention at all!
Indeed.
We all think it's unreasonable.
Will we drop this topic?
Can we just pretend that we didn't
play the game in the first place?
New facts have been found.
Doctor Yutaro Yamagiwa,
whose body was found last month,
was a graduate of Touo University's
medical department,
and worked as a GP.
Touo University Hospital
He had been appearing in
breakfast shows and variety shows,
and expanded his field of work.
Actually...
l want to say something
regarding the game.
I just said we should
drop the topic.
Actually, at that time,
l wrote my own name.
Yoko lshizaki
What?
Why did you do that?
Because there was no one
l want to kill or want dead.
What's wrong with you all, to have
written names so casually!
I didn't write it casually!
It was just the atmosphere
at that time...
You can kill someone
just because of that?
We didn't go that far.
Anyway,
someone drew the piece of paper
with my name on it, right?
Who is it?
I wrote it!
Don't try to kill me
even by mistake.
Why don't you say anything?
Wait, you are scaring me.
Please don't kill me!
Maybe it was someone
who is absent today.
When did we decide
that we have to kill the person on
the piece of paper?
This is ridiculous!
If we instigate anxiety here, it'll
influence children in a bad way.
Who'd have thought that you would
mention influence on children?
What do you mean?
Fine.
Let's tell each other clearly
what name we wrote,
then we'll all feel relieved.
- Mrs Tezuka, we'll start from you.
- What?
Say it. Who do you want dead?
Sorry, l am late.
Please continue.
Miss Kinoshita,
our meeting just finished.
But l heard someone shouting
from outside.
Our conclusion is we have nothing to
talk about this month.
But you just...
Thank you, everyone.
- Thank you...
- Wait, what's going on?
Wait.
Miss Kinoshita, don't use force.
It hurts! Wait!
Your hands are wet!
The good season has come.
Let's end the meeting for real.
Thank you, everyone...
- Mrs Tezuka.
- Yes?
I am not convinced.
Why?
What name did you write?
You started the game,
so you should tell me first.
No, l didn't start the game.
Come on.
How can we say what name we wrote
in front of everyone?
But if you could be killed,
you would also...
Sachiko Akaike.
It isn't the name l wrote.
It's the name on
the ballot paper l got.
So at least,
I'm not going to kill you.
Are you happy now?
I cannot be.
What the heck?
There are other people...
Sachiko Akaike?
She is Room 502's old lady.
Yes.
So the one who wrote it
must have been Mrs Akaike.
What you were trying to do just now
was to get Mrs Akaike to
tell everyone that
she wanted to kill
her mother-in-law.
Well...
l can understand
why she wanted to write the name.
I thought the two of them
were very close.
No, they had a fight the other day.
She kept chanting,
"Fried meat cake..."
She kept shouting "fried meat cake."
You talk a lot today.
Speaking of that, there's something
wrong with Mrs Akaike too.
Misato is very nice!
You didn't realise?
She'd never say anything back
when l talk to her.
The wind chime is so noisy.
Right?
He's the doctor who goes on
tabloid shows as a pundit.
Mr Fujii is the person involved,
but he's absent.
You're imagining things.
No, l am sure.
I talked to her on purpose
to confirm this.
Do you have any clue why?
No idea.
Well, I'm used to people hating me
because of my job.
Anyway, l talked about the paper
in the flow of our conversation.
What about you guys?
It's okay to say
the name someone else wrote!
Tell me what's on
your pieces of paper.
Do sit down.
Come on!
The name on my piece of paper
was Oda Nobunaga.
Oda Nobunaga
What?
The person probably had nobody
they want dead,
and just wrote a random name.
That's clever!
l should've wrote that.
The name on my piece of paper
is Yoshimura.
But l don't know who it is.
None of the residents here
is called Yoshimura.
The name on my piece of paper
was Takafumi Kono.
In Hiragana.
No one is called Kono either.
Old Mrs Akaike is the only one
we know for sure.
I hope she won't be killed.
But Mr Ukita, you're the one
who has the piece of paper.
She won't be killed
if you don't do anything.
No, I'm saying,
Mrs Akaike could take advantage of
the game and kill the old lady.
If l have no motive, l won't even
be suspected. Am l right?
That's right.
You have no motive.
Exactly. None at all.
No way.
Most mothers-in-law and wives
want to kill each other.
If they seem to get along,
it's because one of them
is insensitive.
I think it will be okay.
You never know.
Lately, everyone looks like
a murderer to me.
What's the matter?
Nothing. lt's nothing.
I'll make supper now.
Okay.
Who'd have thought that you would
mention influence on children?
- Gosh, Nana!
- Yes?
You're gloomy every time
after the residents' meeting!
Am l?
- Should l go from now on?
- lt's okay.
I'm gloomy because of
something at work.
Work? What happened?
I don't want to talk about work
in our private time.
But l want to help you, Nana.
I get the energy
to solve the problem alone
by spending time with you, Shota.
So that's already enough.
I want to solve it with you.
I know how you feel,
but sometimes you solve a problem
better on your own.
For example?
Working out?
Even if l do something next to you,
it won't help you build muscles.
But if you cheer for me,
l can work harder
and get double the amount of
muscles l can build.
And you can cheer for me just by
staying here by my side.
I'm convinced now.
You don't look convinced.
I'm convinced in my mind,
but my face hasn't caught up.
I'll go to bed. Even my face will be
convinced tomorrow morning.
There's something else.
Please keep it,
and submit it when you want to.
Whenever you submit it,
I'm fine with that.
Okay.
- Good night.
- Shota.
- Good morning.
Aren't you going to be late
for work? Let's hurry.
Ono...
Oh, that's right! This...
lt's for you.
Lunchbox? l can't keep taking
things from you...
Put food inside yourself.
It's just the box?
The timber was processed
as construction material,
this was made with the edges that
were going to be thrown away,
so it is environment-friendly.
Wow, l had no idea.
It was more difficult
than l thought.
Did you make this too?
I am happy that
it makes you so happy.
Well, I'm actually more surprised.
Sorry! l am happy.
You hurt my feelings,
may l change the topic?
Sure, of course...
ls there anyone you want to kill?
Why ask it out of the blue?
It isn't out of the blue.
lt's all we talk about lately.
All of you?
It's the people who attend
our residents' meeting.
- Why?
- What?
Your wife didn't tell you?
It's the game.
It's the Werewolf game, right?
It isn't Werewolf,
it's the murder-swap game.
Could your wife have been
lying to you?
I wonder why. How strange.
Calm down...
lt is easy to ask her.
But before that,
l will try to deduce it.
Orangutan Time.
Nana said...
We became friends
after playing Werewolf.
Why did she lie to me?
And...
Why did she not tell me
about the murder-swap game?
Mr Tezuka.
You scare me
when you talk to yourself.
Sorry, l can't think
if l don't say it out loud.
Oh...
lf Nana also played the game,
that means she wrote the name of
someone she wanted to kill?
But she didn't want to tell me
whose name she wrote,
so she didn't tell me
about the game.
In that case...
That means she wrote the name...
of someone she doesn't want
to tell me about?
You look very puzzled.
Mrs Akaike could take advantage of
the game and kill the old lady.
Yes?
I am Room 302's Tezuka.
Please accept it.
Wow... Thank you so much.
That's amazing, Mrs Akaike.
It's got pink, the colour you like.
Sorry,
l've got nothing to thank you.
It's okay, l thought it wasn't nice
of me to give her a sample,
but it's easy to move in this,
so l wanted to give it to you.
Would it be too flashy?
No, it will look good on you.
And this is for Misato.
Thank you, l'll give it to her.
You haven't got one for me?
Oh, l'll bring a men's tracksuit
next time.
Sorry, how assuming l am!
Mrs Akaike,
why don't you try it now?
You'll surely look great!
Oh?
Lately, everyone looks like
a murderer to me.
Okay. This side too.
Is it good?
Awesome!
She looks so good!
You look so good in it!
- Wow...
- A flashy one like this is great.
Mrs Tezuka.
Thank you.
No need to come and thank me.
Visit us from time to time
if you don't mind.
Sure.
Everyone is gossiping about
the women of our household, right?
- So they really do?
- No, they don't.
It's a long story,
but it's just natural.
They were raised in different times
and environments,
it's okay if it was a couple
who love each other,
but they became family and live
together without knowing each other.
Considering that,
l think they get along.
Yeah, perhaps.
So please don't worry about it,
and visit again.
Sure.
Will you at least get out of bed?
You're too old to
shut yourself in the room.
What do you want me to do?
- Hi ya.
- Hello.
Madam Kinoshita.
Would you read this out for me,
please?
"My condolences to you."
"l am the person
introduced just now."
Totally different.
It is really difficult!
Will you attend a funeral?
Yes, the owner of the diner
l worked at.
The one in the fire.
"The destination this time..."
Japanese people
don't say this clearly.
No?
It's "... to you."
Say it like that.
Just move your mouth, like you're so
sad that you can't say anything.
So just remember "to you"
and you'll be fine.
You're helpful.
You aren't as horrible as they say.
See you.
For funeral
lt's the girl just now?
Coriander crisps
Miss Sawa Kuroshima
l am okay.
Condolence money envelopes
Hiding something?
Your wife?
What do you think?
All married couples
keep a secret or two to themselves.
- But this isn't usual.
- What do you mean?
Well...
Good evening, Miss Shinohara.
Oh, sorry to call you here suddenly.
Don't worry about it.
ls it a new product?
Amazing!
You make things easy for me.
The murder-swap game you said
is crazy.
It is, isn't it?
Maybe your wife thinks it's stupid,
so she didn't tell you.
Is that so?
Well, it's that, or...
She wrote your name, Sho.
I see!
She wrote you as the person
she wanted to kill,
so she couldn't tell you.
Well, she is cheating on you.
That's for sure.
- I didn't tell you, but...
- Yes?
My wife and l...
love each other to bits!
So this is totally impossible.
Yeah?
But if in the unlikely case...
No, if in the very unlikely case
that Nana wrote my name,
if this is what Nana wants,
l don't mind dying.
But l'll disguise it as an accident,
so that Nana won't feel guilty.
Oh! You'll help me disguise it as
an accident and push me...
No!
Why? Please kill me.
How can you ask such a favour?
I guess l have to ask her, then.
She worries about it so much
that she couldn't tell you,
it would be awful of you to ask her
this and that out of curiosity.
I ask because l am worried.
lt's out of kindness.
You can be kind by
letting her worry about it too.
In many cases, letting someone
solve a problem alone
is for their own sake.
Don't mistake curiosity
for kindness.
Okay.
I am kind, so l will wait and see
for a bit longer.
Yes.
If you'll design it for autumn
and winter, how long do you need?
A week.
Thank you!
Don't worry about it.
Thank goodness!
By the way,
did you move house?
Oh. Yes, l did.
Could you have bought it?
Yes, actually.
I'm so jealous! You own a home!
You say it too loudly!
And your husband is here
at the perfect time.
What?
You are here too?
Hello.
Oh? Wait...
Are you having a fight?
No, we don't mix our job
and our private life.
Right, Nana?
This is so private.
I'm jealous.
Just joking.
You've helped us so much,
Mr Managing Director.
I'm totally fine with you
getting lovey-dovey.
Thank you.
See you later, then.
I am counting on you!
See you.
Oh, that reminds me.
What is this murder-swap game?
Secrets?
You're so gross.
See you.
What is it? Tracksuit?
Ukita speaking.
About last month's case...
Got your handkerchief?
I'm not a kid. l don't need one.
But it might fly everywhere.
Having a handkerchief
won't help, then.
Sorry, I'm late.
It's okay.
I'll cook right now.
- Nana...
- Yes?
- Look!
- Wow!
I knew you would be home late,
so l made supper!
Thank you!
Thank you.
They're like outfits for a couple.
Sorry.
What's the matter?
Dorj's Diner, coupon
lt is your turn to kill.
l kind of have an idea
who wrote this.
What will you do?
Happy birthday to you.
What? l thought
it was something serious.
Whose birthday is it?
Happy birthday, dear...
lt's mine!
- Bon appetit.
So...
A bit...
Delicious! I'm so surprised!
Yes!
It's Sanae.
Hello?
Nana? Somehow...
l heard a noise from above.
I must be imagining things.
Sorry, I'm alone right now,
so I'm worried.
The flat above yours is...
Room 502...
the Akaike family.
Let's go.
Mr Fujii?
Well, l heard a loud voice.
Voice?
Mr Akaike?
I think they're home.
Excuse me, we're coming in.
Excuse--
Hello?
Mrs Akaike!
I'll call someone here!
Old Mrs Akaike!
Oh, my Julia!
Mrs Akaike!
Mrs Akaike, are you okay?
Mrs Akaike...
Misato Akaike
Your Turn to Kill
lf all the residents are suspects,
everyone will say it's
a murderers' condo.
Murderer
lf you tell me to trust you, l will.
Maybe you'll be killed.
This drama is fictitious