On the first day we moved here,
the residents played a murder-swap
game without me realising it.
"Caretaker, Yutaro Yamagiwa"
lt's easier than doing surgery.
Every time a person dies,
someone threatens
and someone else is threatened.
Mrs Akaike!
Another murder happens...
Julia!
During our investigation,
we realised that murders not related
to the game could have happened...
Nana!
Even so, l have no time to be sad.
It's the last time, please smile.
Shota, l...
There is something
that l have to do now.
If you had reported the murder-swap
game to the other detectives,
then Nana didn't have to die!
Potassium chloride caused her death.
We haven't got much data now,
but if we let the Al analyse it,
it'll say Fujii is the murderer.
It's trespassing!
Call the police, then.
Photos of the suspects of actor
Yoshihiko Hakamada's murder
have been released.
The wanted men are
an Iranian man, Ali Moharrami...
Shota, call back at once
when you hear my message.
Let go! Hey!
Mr Fujii!
Wait, what are you doing?
Did you kill him? Hang on...
Aren't you just carrying him?
Wait, what will you do?
Let go...
lt's so troublesome.
Nikaido?
What's going on?
What?
What is... this...
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Mr Yomogida, thank you!
No, l... Don't worry about it.
Doyan, what are you doing?
Will you call the police?
Sure...
Hello, l was suddenly attacked
by two foreigners. Yes...
Two men. Well, l'm all right now.
Is there any other way
to settle this?
No. The police will definitely
come here too.
Flee now. We'll think about
what we should do later.
Okay.
I'll see what's going on outside.
We're going to meet again,
aren't we?
We will. We can. We can!
Starting today, l'll sleep
at 1:00 am every day.
Sleep at the same time as me, Xinyi.
Let's meet in our dreams for now.
I'm going to feel lonely.
Don't worry.
There's a legend in Vietnam
that says
if you fly in the sky
on Tom Hap Nuoc Dua in your dream,
then you can get married.
"Tom Hap Nuoc Dua"?
Let's have the same dream
at the same time.
- Tom Hap...
- Can l kiss you?
I don't want a kiss that feels like
we'll never meet again!
Kiss me like you're just going to
the convenience store.
See you...
"Sumida Police Station"
You attacked Shota Tezuka,
attempted to kidnap him,
on top of that...
Why did you kill Yoshihiko Hakamada?
- Mr Mizuki.
- What?
Is this okay? The case is handled
by another police station.
That's why l'll ask
before he is sent there.
I don't like Hakamada's face,
so l killed him.
They obviously agreed
to say the same thing.
There is another person besides
the other man we caught, right?
The footwear impressions...
Well, footprints.
Three people's footprints
were left at the crime scene.
We only haven't found who the 24.5
centimetres long one belongs to.
It's hers, isn't it?
No!
- I know you want to cover for...
- lt really isn't hers!
I told you, l don't know anything.
The two men saw Mr Tezuka
and they suddenly...
Mr Tezuka said he saw a large amount
of drugs at your home.
They were just medicine.
Xinyi asked me to send some to
her home's village, so l got them.
Then the men came to take them.
The condo is awful!
Too many murders happened.
Maybe it's cursed.
You think so too?
How can it be cursed?
No, l'm sorry. You are right.
The reason that many people died
at the condo...
is because they're playing
a murder-swap game.
What game?
Ask Mr Kamiya. He knows the details.
What do you mean? l don't get it.
Murder-Swap Game?
It's a free app, but in the end,
you have to spend money to win.
There are many apps
like this lately.
Forget it.
I can't trust you anymore.
Calm down...
Are you free now?
I'm going to tell you
a pretty long story now.
Sure.
"Your Turn to Kill"
l can't forgive them.
Sora, it's been a while.
This is normal!
When is this going to stop?
It's about Kuroshima.
Something isn't right about her.
What isn't?
What is this all about? Hey!
How long have you known?
I don't remember so precisely.
You're defiant now?
- Mr Mizuki, it's your fault.
- What?
If you knew that the residents
killed each other in a game,
you'd say it was scary
and it was a curse, right?
I can't stand it anymore!
You frighten me most now.
It's a misunderstanding.
I... l am really sorry.
- If possible, please don't...
- Report it yourself.
Everything. Honestly.
Depending on what you report,
l'll decide whether l will
trust you or not in the future.
Yes, sir.
The suspects of Yoshihiko Hakamada's
murder have finally been arrested.
The repertory cinema in lidabashi
is holding
a memorial all-night film screening
titled "Really Amazing,
Yoshihiko Hakamada."
Our programme will give out tickets
to four pairs of our audience.
Mummy, l am hungry.
- What do you want to have?
- Curry!
Curry? Let's go to the place
near our home
where we went the other day .
- It was delicious!
- Let's go there.
Let's go there!
I am so confused.
When is this going to stop?
You were too reckless.
It's pointless to use Al
if you do that.
- Kuroshima.
- Yes?
Oh, Doyan too.
Sorry l made you worried,
but this might continue to happen.
What...
So far, every time
l did something reckless...
l am sorry.
Shota...
We made progress
in investigating the case.
- But still...
- Moreover,
when they put a bag over my head
and beat me up...
l thought, "l'm going to be killed,"
and l was terrified.
At that time...
l thought maybe this was
how frightened Nana was too.
Shota...
So l can't forgive them.
l swear, l won't forgive them!
Will you talk about something else?
You do something reckless when
you're beside yourself with anger.
I've input the data into the Al,
so l want some other data.
Okay.
Didn't you say you were blindfolded?
Yes.
Under a similar situation,
did it remind you of anything?
Like the voice of
the third person in the room.
I make my decisions quickly.
No, l don't know.
But at least it wasn't
the two foreigners.
It wasn't Mr Fujii too.
Please sort your rubbish properly
and just act sensibly.
Oh, Mr Sano! l'll introduce you.
Your new neighbour...
Wait! You ignore me?
We don't get along, do we?
Wait... Hang on!
Oh?
What? l was going to say hello
and give him the gift.
- He won't accept it anyway.
- Why?
Somehow his looks and curly hair
are the only decent things he has,
he's unsociable.
What's 501's resident called?
Oh, it's Sano.
A guy? How old is he?
Yes, a guy, but l don't know
how old he is.
No? Will you introduce me
to everyone here?
In that case, an urgent residents'
meeting will be held later.
Will people involved in the murder
be there?
Yeah, probably.
Good! l'll attend, then.
lt's for you.
Wow, thanks!
- So... which way?
- This way.
Let's go.
- It's really tasty.
- Yeah?
"Murder-Swap Game
at Kuramae Condo"
Why did they play this game?
It seems to be entertainment
after their residents' meeting.
Why did so many people die, then?
This isn't right!
The table is just a summary of
the information Tezuka gave me,
- l don't know the details.
- Kamiya.
Yes?
If you don't know the details,
is there anything
that you don't feel right?
Well, for example,
Kuzumi wrote Yoshihiko Hakamada
as the person he wanted to kill,
and two men staying with Xinyi were
arrested as the murder suspects.
They have no motive to kill
Hakamada.
If there was trouble
between the residents,
we can still guess the motive.
They're foreigners who've overstayed
and an actor, respectively.
If anything,
it's more likely that
they're really playing the game.
The matter is quite horrible
and l can't believe it right away,
but let's bear this in mind
and use it for our investigation.
Yes, sir.
What? We will really do it?
Yes, we do it annually,
and we did nothing suspicious.
Suspicious, huh?
We run a stall every year at our
neighbourhood group's festival.
But isn't it bad
to run a stall at this time?
What do you mean?
You want to say that
nobody will come
to a stall run by
the murderers' condo, right?
Yes, indeed,
but Mr Ukita gave it his all
every year before,
so l'll help too.
We might as well
make a haunted house!
We'll pretend to be killers
and scare people.
It sounds fun!
The real one is among us too.
What are you talking about?
So, what did this girl say
about the men who stay with her?
She said she had met them,
but she didn't know them well.
However, when we inspected her flat,
we thought she must know them.
There were beds for four people.
And pillows for seven people.
Among them, the most likely
third suspect of Hakamada's murder
was Xinyi, but...
On the day of the murder,
Xinyi had an interview in Tokyo
for a part-time job.
The man, Cuong,
accompanied her there.
She has an alibi?
And this guy was working
at his office too?
We've sent lqbal home.
Many points in Xinyi's statement
are unknown,
so we're still investigating.
We haven't found the third murderer
in Hakamada's murder?
"List of residents
at Chiunque Kuramae"
Let's talk about
the summer festival later,
and we'll drop this for now.
- Mr Yomogida.
- Hello.
I'll introduce you all
to your new neighbour.
He has moved in
and you can't say no this time.
- What?
- Well then...
- Come in.
- Thanks.
Well...
l'm Minami and l've move in to
Room 502. Nice to meet you.
502?
The Akaike family's...
Mrs Akaike!
It's terrifying, isn't it?
It's unusual, isn't it?
But the rent is cheap.
Is that why you think
it isn't normal? But it is normal!
Don't worry!
One, two, three... All of you have
a questioning look on your faces!
Well, guys, be friends with him.
- Do sit down.
- Thanks.
Let's vote to see
how many are against him moving in!
Wait, ma'am.
And neighbours.
Don't look at me like that.
So many things happened
in this condo,
so l should be the one to... Right?
You should be the one to what?
To close the distance between us
and build
a mutual trust relationship.
Yeah. That.
So, will you tell me your names?
Let's start from me.
Room 204's Nishimura.
- Mr Nishimura.
- Yes.
And your housemate was killed?
No, not me.
What? We'll start from those
whose housemate was killed.
Are you a reporter or what?
I am not.
So, who are you? Tell me your name
and the murdered...
You jerk!
Room 302. Shota Tezuka.
My wife, Nana Tezuka, was killed.
The murderer hasn't been caught.
Well...
l hope they will be caught soon,
Mr Tezuka.
Yes.
Think about what you want to put
at the stall until next time.
- Okay...
- Thank you.
Mr Tezuka.
You can't.
What?
I can't give it back yet.
"Fujii"
"Ono, Tezuka"
But l made lots of effort
to collect them.
Doyan, let's go.
They're important data for my job.
Your job?
Wait, what are you doing?
I'm taking my revenge.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
"Suiyo Publishing"
Kinoshita speaking.
Yes. Thank you.
Well, regarding that...
l am home.
See you.
You'll go already?
The real thing is three days later,
the real thing
is three days later.
No need to say that twice.
Well then, do your best.
Hello!
Sorry, l'd like to check the lines
with you before the performance.
Sure. lt's important.
It's where he asks for the bill?
Yes, just a bit before that...
Bon appetit.
It's so darn hot,
but you make hot pot every time.
Bon appetit.
You don't say anything
and just eat now.
It's only the look on your face.
Look like you enjoy it more.
It tastes good,
but my tongue and my face
have different personalities.
Oh.
What will you do about Mr Fujii?
I told the police about the game, so
l'll wait for them to take action.
Also, there is too little data
about Miss Ono.
She stubbornly refused
to tell me about the names.
I had pretended to want to
tell the same story as her
and went to her flat.
But l didn't find anything fishy.
Filling the table is the shortcut
to solving the case, but...
Sanae lied about what she wrote,
and l'm thinking about
asking the police
to analyse the fingerprints
on Mrs lshizaki's paper.
Another question is
Mrs Misato Akaike.
"502, Akaike"
And the names drawn by Mr Tamiya
and Kuroshima.
Well, there's something about
Kuroshima.
It's been bothering me.
What is it?
Her... you know...
Her smell is weird.
- Smell?
- Yes.
I really hate other people's smells.
So l spray room deodoriser,
even after you leave too.
But only her smell
doesn't bother me.
What are you talking about?
This is important!
I'm going to input this data
into the Al.
Food influences body odour,
so her diet can be deduced.
For example, you know
that someone eats curry a lot
if you can verify the spices on some
fibres left at the crime scene...
lt can be connected like this.
I see.
Yes.
But judging by what you just said,
probably it's because...
You're in love.
In love?
Doyan, you're in love
with Kuroshima,
- so it doesn't bother you.
- What?
Well, for example,
dogs smell another dog's butt
to judge whether it's
a friend or enemy.
Their smell changes
when they are in heat too.
If you find someone's smell
acceptable, it's out of instinct.
Oh...
l loved Nana's smell very much too.
When l hug her,
l always smell
a light, pleasant smell.
It would make me think,
"Oh, this is Nana.
I feel so blessed."
No matter how many times l hug her,
l still want to hug her even more.
Even now, when l smell her smell,
it reminds me of
her smile and gestures.
They just come to my mind.
So, when Nana's smell
gradually disappears from the flat,
it makes me scared.
I still can't open the wardrobe yet.
So, Doyan...
it is very lucky to meet
someone like this.
"Goodbye Rhapsody"
So you released her?
We know clearly the time
that Yoshihiko Hakamada was killed.
If she has an alibi,
we can't continue to question her.
Cuong called. He's all right.
Don't worry.
It's all my fault.
I found Yoshihiko Hakamada's
schedule.
Amazing.
Are you really going to do it?
This is the chance
to repay Xinyi's kindness.
We did it ourselves.
It isn't your fault, Xinyi.
"Goodbye Rhapsody"
We really are going to break up
for real?
Yes.
Instead of forcing ourselves
to be friends,
we should make more effort
on something else.
Effort? Don't say it like that.
Excuse me, the bill, please.
Certainly, sir. The bill.
When he says "the bill,"
l dance towards the dining area,
reacting to the curse that my body
became familiar with before l knew.
It's the same when someone says,
"Some beer first."
Flying orders, dancing steps!
Days repeat themselves,
the wage is low.
No matter how many seasons come and
go, they never lose their beauty.
But every time
my life repeats itself...
it gets duller.
Mr Tamiya...
You came! Thank you.
- It was interesting.
- Really?
You were acting in
a dimension different from them.
Those who really see it can tell.
Can l have an autograph?
Come on! Don't tease me.
Have you got a pen?
Your autograph,
and l'd like to see the video taken
by the security cameras you set.
I heard that you set them up.
I don't know how to handle machines,
so nothing was taken.
But you only need to press a button.
Why? l said you didn't have to come!
I was so nervous!
Half-way through it,
maybe l was possessed by something,
l don't remember anything
after he said, "The bill, please."
lt wasn't scripted.
l guess l entered "the zone"...
Check the alibi of each person
in the murder cases so far again.
Also, check if anyone close to them
is involved in a murder too.
That's all.
Yes, sir.
You're so fishy that
l don't want to be your partner.
How can you doubt
a fellow detective?
Where are you going?
I'll try to start attacking
from the weakest one.
"Murder-swap game"?
- You did it, right?
- Yes.
Our chairlady told us that
it has been reported to the police.
We talked about it
at the residents' meeting.
A series of murders
continued to happen
as if they were related to the game,
but they aren't related.
According to the information we got,
you wrote Yutaro Yamagiwa's name,
Sanae drew the piece of paper,
and she killed Yamagiwa.
That's what we've got.
Is that correct?
Hang on.
Yes, l did write Yamagiwa's name,
l admit it.
Everyone talked. Talked...
lt's weird to say so, huh?
Oops, l spat. lt's so dirty.
After Sanae Enomoto killed Yamagiwa,
she threatened you.
You yielded to her threat,
so you killed Masao Tanaka,
the owner of a Bhutanese diner
in the neighbourhood.
After that, you threatened
Room 203's Xinyi.
Am l right so far?
You got one thing wrong.
I did not kill the diner's owner.
So you admit that
you threatened Xinyi?
You got two things wrong.
Xinyi...
On a bath towel
we found at Sanae Enomoto's home,
we found DNA that didn't belong
to the Enomoto family.
May we take a sample of your DNA
just in case?
This is your bath towel.
Your DNA and Yutaro Yamagiwa's DNA
will be found on it.
May l stand up?
Okay, l give up.
I'll say everything honestly.
I wrote Yamagiwa's name.
Then, Yamagiwa was killed.
For some reason, when l went home,
his head was in my washing machine.
I was shocked,
so l dashed out of my flat.
But when l returned,
the head was gone.
The door was locked
when you came home, right?
Yes.
The question is how she broke into
the flat and took the head back.
Yeah.
The key...
"Master key"
After that,
l yielded to an incredible number
of extremely evil threats,
and l had no choice
but to unwillingly...
The diner owner.
The diner owner...
Sorry, sir, please...
idiot! Come in later!
No, sir! Now...
What? He has an alibi?
Fujii was working the night shift
at the time Masao Tanaka died,
and he was treating
an emergency patient.
Sorry about
the various things we did.
Seven,
eight...
nine...
ten.
Okay, well done.
Let's do one more set.
- Excuse me.
- Okay, let's do it.
- Excuse me!
- One...
l've done 12 sets.
My arms are killing me.
Sorry, l've been thinking...
What? 12 sets?
Yes.
You should've told me earlier!
Your arms break
if you do three sets of this!
Your muscles are
surprisingly strong.
I do physical work in a sense.
I am very sorry.
Sora.
We'll have shiitake mushrooms.
What?
Shiitake mushroom hamburger steak.
- Hamburger steak?
- Yes.
- Yes!
- Good. Let's go.
- Well...
- l want to buy some snacks.
- Snacks?
- l'll go and have a look.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
Sora.
It's been a while.
You can come out now?
Yeah.
"Room 402, Soichi Enomoto"
l successfully escaped.
Glad to hear that.
Sorry that l scared you
at that time.
It's okay.
Sora?
Sora.
Sora!
Gosh! l thought you went
to the snacks aisle?
Yeah, but...
But what?
Nothing.
"Sumida Police Station"
l'll ask again.
How did you put Yamagiwa's head
into Fujii's washing machine
and take it back?
Aren't your eyes dry?
Well, in the usual case,
it's either you,
or your husband, Masashi, or...
Oh, it was me.
I did it. l did everything.
I'll tell you in that order.
First, about Yutaro Yamagiwa.
The hospital is famous,
so l knew where it was.
So l waited until he left.
After that, l drove
for about 30 minutes in Tokyo...
"Touo University Hospital"
"30th April, 2019. 22:58"
"Doctor: Department of Orthopaedics
Atsushi Fujii"
lt really says that
l was seeing a patient.
You've been taking
many half days lately.
Yeah, a bit.
Have you been questioned
by the police?
Why?
The police has contacted us.
For what?
No idea. Ask the director.
However,
they asked whether you came to work
or not on 30th April,
so l gave them the record.
- On that day, l...
- Yes.
So l think the director
will be angry at you.
You weren't supposed to be on duty,
but you saw a patient.
No, l...
Doctor,
you saw a patient on that day.
Did you alter the record?
Don't ask. lt's annoying.
First,
tell me honestly
what you did on that day.
Come on! Tell me now!
You actually want to
tell someone everything
and get it off your chest, right?
So tell me.
On that day, l...
l sneaked
into the Bhutanese diner...
and killed Masao Tanaka.
"Tokyo Metropolitan Police Hospital"
- l told you yesterday!
- l know. l'm sorry.
- You know? You haven't got it.
- But it's...
The bag...
lt can't possibly be in the bag!
I said sorry.
You're Mr Ukita's...
So you've visited him many times?
Yeah, dad...
Mr Ukita...
seemed to have met him
right before he died.
So we thought he must know something
and came to see how he's doing
from time to time.
Either that,
or this Yoshihiko Hakamada
look-alike killed Mr Ukita.
It doesn't make sense that
he fell down an escalator!
No, it was an elevator.
It was escalator.
- What?
- An elevator.
No, it's the box thing, right?
Are you serious?
You lost your wife too, right?
Are you okay with this?
Of course you can't be okay.
I want to find the murderer
and kill them.
Mr Ukita was strangled
and he died a horrible death,
but despite that,
he had a smile on his face.
Seeing that made me even sadder.
What?
In detail!
He was smiling?
So it seems.
I remember that Nana too...
l thought it was because
the drug didn't make her suffer,
but l just remembered something.
Mr and Mrs Akaike were smiling too.
What a strange coincidence.
The murder happened in...
Room 502.
I want to see it.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Please come in!
You're my first visitors.
Wow, l'm so happy.
Sorry, we know this is rude...
lt's okay. lt's natural that you
want to check out various things.
Even the cleaning service staff
couldn't remove it.
Well, stuff like this
doesn't bother me.
Have you found any clues?
- No.
- l'll ask one thing, then.
Do you know where
Mrs Sachiko Akaike is?
Julia!
Well, l rent this flat cheaply,
so l want to say thank you,
but l still haven't met
the old lady herself.
I don't really know.
As l thought, he is weird.
People who move here now
are all weirdos.
We didn't get anything here.
I'll go see the old lady tomorrow.
Okay.
"International Science
and Engineering University"
Mr Nikaido.
Are you going home?
Shall we go together?
It's fine, but...
What's the matter?
If we have nothing to talk about
on the way
and there is an uncomfortable
silence, l can't deal with it.
If you promise you won't talk to me
at all, then l'll go with you.
Sure.
Then let's say nothing
when we walk home.
There she is.
Hello.
Mrs Akaike,
can you see the Ferris wheel?
Her relatives haven't been here
since they sent her here,
so l come here.
Does Sachiko remember the case...
Don't.
She recalled it the other day
and she was confused.
Lately, l, Sumika Kitagawa,
have been looking for cooling sounds
in summer,
like the murmur of a stream
or a ringing wind chime,
to try to get over this hot summer.
Yeah.
Okay, l'll read out
a few messages sent to us...
"Let's go to the festival together"
Soichi. Are you going somewhere?
Yes, l am going
to my friend's place.
- You've made friends?
- Yes.
But please hang out
with me too, Sawa.
Sure.
See you.
It's your job to
do something about it!
This one is moving.
Mrs Akaike, do you remember me?
Are you the same?
You mean Nana?
The boy.
Who do you mean?
He praised me and said it suited me.
Why did he praise you?
It's that. You know, that.
Don't you know?
You should be educated.
The night of her birthday.
"Misato Akaike"
Julia!
Sano!
Mrs Akaike!
What are you doing?
Mrs Akaike! Can you hear me?
Mrs Akaike! Mrs Akaike!
I'll say goodbye here.
Oops, l can't let them find
this outfit.
Get rid of them for me.
"Your Turn to Kill"
"Preview"
On the night of the summer festival,
there will be a new victim.
"Who is the target?"
Who is the target?
"This drama is fictional"