Everyone must have someone
whom they want to kill.
l think what he said started it.
We wrote the names of the people
we want to kill as a kind of joke,
and showed each other secretly.
Takafumi Kono
But maybe, someone
didn't think that it was joke.
Do you suspect me?
l'll tell you now,
the name l wrote
was Yutaro Yamagiwa.
Mr Fujii, look!
The unidentified body found
in a mountain in Kanagawa Prefecture
was Dr Yutaro Yamagiwa,
commonly known as Dr Yamagiwa...
Several unbelievable incidents
happened right under my nose.
It wasn't me...
They couldn't find his head.
Even at somewhere l don't know...
Something started to happen.
Hair...
Why?
You startled me.
Mr Fujii, are you okay?
Somehow your face looks
even weirder than usual.
No, l...
Could you have found
Dr Yamagiwa's head in your flat?
Yes, l did.
No, l didn't! lt isn't in my flat!
How can it be?
My flat is totally empty!
Anyway, what's wrong?
Let's say, in the unlikely case
that the head is there,
if it is so obvious,
then the murderer can't be me,
right?
You must be the murderer, then.
You don't normally have
someone's head.
Gosh!
Yutaro Yamagiwa
Someone killed the person
that you want dead,
you have to kill someone's too,
or you'll violate the rule.
Ground floor.
Obey the rules properly.
Your Turn to Kill
Episode 3
Will you throw away the rubbish,
please?
Yeah, sure.
You know, Yutaro Yamagiwa
didn't just have his head removed,
it seems that his fingerprints
were burned too.
Not interested.
Orangutan Time.
Shota?
It appears that the murderer
hid the dead body's identity
to delay the process
of the investigation.
In other words,
the murder was planned.
You'll be late.
The murderer bore a deep grudge,
and swore to kill him one day.
They had imagined how to kill
Yamagiwa and deceive the police
when the time comes.
How is my suspicion?
ls it a bull's-eye?
Stop thinking about that
and go to work now.
But you've been thinking a lot
lately too.
And you're absent minded.
What? Why do you think so?
Because that's my toothbrush.
What?
Why? Do you think it's gross?
- No, l...
- Do you not love me?
I do, but using another person's
toothbrush is...
But l can use yours.
- Don't use it!
- Just occasionally.
No, loving someone and this,
are different matters.
To me, loving someone is being able
to use the same toothbrush.
What?
I've actually used yours many times.
You lied.
You know?
But you look so depressed!
The property manager
suddenly died and l...
l'm sorry that giving you a hug
is all l can do.
It's okay. Thank you.
You don't look okay, so l'll hug you
for ten more seconds.
Whose stomach just rumbled?
I don't know.
You don't know, right?
I want to stay so close to you that
l can't tell whose stomach rumbles.
I won't hide anything from you.
l swear.
Premium Contemporary
Dr Yamagiwa's Murder
Dr Yamagiwa
Where is his head?
It is your turn to kill
- Excuse me.
- Whoa, chai, chai, chai!
Oh, it's you, Miss Kinoshita?
Just now...
Did you say
"Whoa, chai, chai, chai?"
l was startled. l couldn't help...
What does
"Whoa, chai, chai, chai" mean?
It doesn't mean anything.
l shouted because you startled me.
I startled you,
so you carelessly cursed me?
I didn't curse you!
What are you doing anyway?
I was made to clean
the rubbish collection area.
Did you sort it properly?
I'll curse you if you didn't.
I did!
- Hello.
- Good morning.
Which floor?
You won't get off?
Oh, yes, l will.
- Hang on.
- Yes?
Will you be available tonight?
Yes.
Sora, do you have to go
to nursery school?
What about the live programme?
We can't do it without a guest.
Yes.
- Hey...
- What?
If you want to say something,
say it when the kid isn't here.
If you shout at his mother
in front of him, it'll hurt him too.
Okay. Yes, you can bring that.
Hurry up! Or l'll beat you up!
Come on, he'll beat you up.
I'll take it...
l'll also...
Yes, someone might be able to come.
You two are always so close.
Not exactly, l just always
rely on her to look after me.
- That's not the case.
- Right.
No need to be modest.
You really help me a lot.
Oh, by the way, Misato,
show the lady that.
- "That"?
- Yes, you know...
What l asked you to keep for me.
Okay!
You know what she refers to just by
that? You two are really close!
Mum!
Oh, no!
- Are you okay?
- Are you all right?
- I'm okay...
- Please forgive me!
- Sachiko...
- l'm sorry.
I'm so sorry...
You don't have to tell Goro,
or he will be angry at you that you
forgot to lock the wheelchair.
Okay.
How kind of you to cover it up
for your daughter-in-law!
I should learn from you.
It is your turn to kill
lt is your turn to kill
Dr Fujii?
Will you tell me when you come in?
What's the matter?
What else? l'm here to work.
Of course. l am sorry.
You haven't been yourself lately.
l am worried.
Sorry. Thank you.
You see, your reputation is very bad
among the patients and nurses,
so l am worried
that you will be fired soon.
What?
I'm saying that if l complain
about you,
even if it's something trivial,
you'll be fired at once.
That's how much your job is at risk.
Is that so?
Yes, it is.
So don't you dare
cause me any problems, Fujii!
- Answer me!
- Yes!
I look forward to working with you
today too.
What do you think about Mr Fujii?
What do you mean?
I mean, Mr Fujii...
Someone said
that maybe he killed Dr Yamagiwa.
Who said that?
Almost everyone.
I don't think he did.
At that time, Mr Fujii...
The unidentified dead body has been
found to be Dr Yutaro Yamagiwa.
It wasn't me...
He was shocked and it seems
that he really had no idea.
Yeah...
He couldn't have killed the doctor.
The deaths of the property manager
and Yutaro Yamagiwa...
have nothing to do
with the game, right?
Do you find anyone
among the residents suspicious?
I don't want them dead, but there
is someone l hope will disappear.
The person l want to kill
and l don't know everyone.
I wanted him to die once,
come back to life, then die again.
Why don't we reveal it together?
Do not show anyone else.
Now, open it!
I don't.
I think.
Kojima Kids' English Class
Thank you for teaching me.
See you...
See you next week.
Has everyone got biscuits?
- Come to my home!
- Let's go!
Let's go home.
Fumi.
Kazu, you haven't been coming
to my lessons lately,
what's the matter?
We had a cold.
Mummy told us to say
that we had a cold.
Gosh!
I am home.
"I'll attend the urgent
residents' meeting. Nana."
My point is,
the rumour is groundless,
let's not hurt Mr Fujii's feelings
because of that.
And my point is,
don't call us to meet
just for something like that!
It isn't trivial.
You have no right
to summon us to a meeting.
I do. lt is written on the contract
we signed when we moved in.
If something makes
the residents suffer any harm...
- You know...
- Yes?
I love seeing middle-aged men
getting desperate.
The contract is about water leakage!
The person concerned, Mr Fujii,
is absent in the first place.
Everyone, calm down.
Our property manager
and Yutaro Yamagiwa died,
it's made all of us worried.
Why are you worried?
Because they could've been
killed by someone.
Why? Mrs lshizaki, do you think
someone among us killed them?
No! l just...
Because some people are absent
from the meeting today.
I don't want to get suspicious
like this!
Please be careful of what you say!
You are being too serious as usual.
Hang on.
Mr Ukita, you always say
that l am a serious person,
but l am not that serious!
I may not look it,
but l joined a theatre group called
Humour Estate when l was young.
Like The Third Stage in the East,
Sotobakomachi in the West,
Minami Banzai lchiza
and Gekidan Shinkansen,
it was full of humour...
That's why l say you're serious!
Everyone.
I don't suspect anyone of you,
but Mr Fujii has been
receiving threatening notes.
Threatening notes?
Yes.
Lately, l find these every day
when l go home.
This one too.
Murder lnducement
What is this? Murder...
lt is murder inducement.
A person who induces another
to commit a crime
shall be dealt with in
sentencing as a principal.
ln other words...
lnducement.
It means incite, right?
Even if you didn't carry it out,
if you incite or urge someone
to murder,
you'll be punished,
like the murderer.
You know a lot!
You copied those?
I didn't. lt's mentioned
in detective stories occasionally.
Who sent them to Mr Fujii and why?
If they were sent by the person
who killed Yutaro Yamagiwa,
l think they mean,
he is just as guilty as they are.
This is absurd.
If you say that, everyone
who participated in the game
induced someone
to commit murder.
Why do you have this conclusion?
If writing who we want to kill
makes us guilty,
then we're all guilty.
But l just wrote a name!
I was forced to participate.
That's why l said it was absurd.
But that's what the law is.
Even though you had no idea
and had no such intention,
it is still a crime
and you will be arrested.
But it's quite funny
if we'll all be arrested.
It isn't funny.
In the end,
who sent them to Mr Fujii?
Someone among us.
Stop looking at each other
with suspicion.
First of all, everybody here
didn't kill Yutaro Yamagiwa.
That means it was someone
who is absent today?
For example, the Chinese girl,
or the workaholic woman,
or the S&M university student.
S&M university student?
You know, the girl in Room 202.
She always has bandage
on a part of her body.
Is that what it is?
It's obvious.
The same thing turns me on.
Don't get the wrong idea.
l am an extreme masochist.
What did we get wrong?
This isn't a place for you to
talk about something so dirty!
You had never fought with anyone
even when you worked at the back.
l didn't have a fight.
l only slammed the table.
What?
Go and find something new
to be enthusiastic about,
like when you used to have a job!
Don't say it like l'm an old man
retired from the world.
Recruiting theatre group members
Since we became friends,
we've only been talking
about murderers and victims,
and it's awful.
I want to hear you brag
about your new married life.
There is nothing
worth talking about.
You look like you do.
- Hello.
- Are you all right?
I am all right.
- I think we shouldn't ask.
- Why?
You're joking. Really? ls it true?
So in the end,
what did you talk about?
- What do you mean?
- The residents' meeting.
Why did you have an urgent meeting?
Well...
Are you going to lie?
Nana, you have a habit
to bite your lip when you lie.
Why do you lie?
You lied about me biting my lip,
didn't you?
How do you know?
You always scratch
your right chest when you lie.
Actually, l have used it many times.
Nana, you have a habit
to bite your lip when you lie.
Really?
What? l'm not aware of it at all!
- You often do it.
- What?
So, what is it, then?
Well, Room 103's Mr Tamiya
said that residents haven't been
sorting their rubbish properly,
so he told us to pay attention.
A lady got angry at me for that
in the rubbish collection area too.
She's probably in charge
of cleaning the area...
Miss Kinoshita, right?
- How do you know?
- Because we talked for a bit.
She is single,
and she said she liked
watching musicals.
You really get along
with everyone right away.
What? That's not true.
Yes, it is true.
Is that so?
No, not get along quickly,
you get too familiar right away.
You dissed me a bit, didn't you?
No, l didn't.
Sho, l am saying that this
is what people like about you.
Okay.
- You speak too loudly.
- No, it's you.
Sorry, we'll be more careful.
Okay...
How about doing 50 more times?
You're a demon!
Okay, one.
Two.
- That's enough!
- Yes?
- Good bye!
- Wait!
Yes?
What's the matter?
It's your turn to kill
Write this.
Write what?
Write "It is your turn to kill."
- Now.
- Okay.
It is your turn to kill
lt's different?
What's wrong, Mr Fujii?
What the heck?
l can't stand it anymore!
- Mr Fujii?
- l hate this.
Do l have to go
to every single flat?
Everyone is going to think
l'm a weirdo!
Are you okay?
I am not okay!
Obviously something is wrong
with me now!
Just calm down.
Let's talk about it inside.
Are you sure?
Well, let's talk here first.
- You don't want to?
- l...
You don't want a weird guy
in your flat?
No, that's not what l mean.
Kuzumi...
Do you know a Masao Tanaka?
Who?
Forget it if you don't.
Bhutanese Cuisine, Dorj's Diner
This is delicious.
Don't worry.
l guarantee that it's delicious.
- It's hot!
- But delicious, right?
Come on, give him some.
Masao Tanaka
Who is this?
It's better to have a big bite.
What's the matter, Dorj?
What will you do
on our next regular day off?
Go to school.
I see. I'm impressed
by how hard-working you are.
By the way,
have you fixed your DVD player?
Why don't you come
and watch at my place?
I couldn't fix it,
so l bought a Blu-ray player.
I spent a lot!
I bought a cushion too!
An expensive one.
Why don't you come
and feel it at my place?
I've got a cushion at home too.
Come on, just come and feel it once.
You can come anytime.
I'll give you my spare key.
No, thanks!
But don't bring the friends
who share the flat with you along.
Excuse me, do you mind
if l ask your name?
Yes?
If you are Mr Masao Tanaka,
l might kill you.
What is your name?
- Tell me your name.
- What did you say?
Mr Fujii!
I'm home!
Sorry, l went to have dinner
with Sanae.
I wondered if they knew him,
so l asked.
Masao Tanaka
Even if they do,
what were you going to do?
What will l do?
Someone hates this Tanaka so much
that they want to kill him,
so l want to see what he looks like.
Is that all?
Of course.
Xinyi, do you know a Masao Tanaka?
I have no Japanese friend.
The way you say that is cute.
You're Chinese, why do you work
at a Bhutanese restaurant?
There are Japanese people
working at Italian restaurants too!
She's not cute at all.
What did you say?
You're not thinking that you have
to kill someone this time, are you?
Of course not!
We heard that you've been threatened
and we are worried.
It wasn't you guys, right?
Of course not.
The murderer who killed Yamagiwa
has to be one of the residents.
Why do you think so?
I don't trust anyone of you too.
I don't want to say it.
Good morning.
Did you buy those?
There are various types nowadays.
Why did you buy so many?
Do l need to explain?
Yes, if possible.
To make the world better.
You didn't explain anything.
There is an air of unrest
in the residential tower,
it has been causing suspicion
and fear in the residents.
I can't let it pass.
Even so, why do you have to do this?
If it doesn't need me to do it,
that means l can do it.
It's sophism.
I can foresee a bad outcome,
l'm fed up with doing nothing
and letting it pass.
Please.
Just forget what happened
when you worked at the bank.
First, l'll get the whole picture
of what is going on.
Then, analyse it based on that,
come up with ways to deal
with the incident and solve it.
- Please go home.
- No, it's fine.
- It's fine.
- Please.
- What's going on?
- l will go and buy it.
I don't want to cause you trouble,
so l'll go myself from now on.
What happened?
We've been talking
about what to eat for supper.
Let her eat what she wants.
- No...
- You got it wrong.
I wanted to have
deep-fried meat cake
and Misato prepared it for me.
You shouldn't eat that.
Yes. The doctor stressed that
l shouldn't eat anything deep-fried.
What are you doing?
Mum insisted on having it.
Is that so?
I am sorry.
I was being childish.
There are more and more things
l can't do when l grow old,
so l say l want to eat this
or l want to do this
and use words
to take my mind off it.
But Misato takes
what l say seriously.
On top of that, she made a meat cake
as big as a sandal.
When l saw it,
it made me feel so sorry for myself,
that my health is too bad for me
to eat it.
Okay, mum. lt's okay.
Do you enjoy making old people cry?
Of course l don't enjoy it!
You should at least
make it bite size.
How can you make it like a scandal?
Or you can make soy pulp croquette.
From this morning,
for the whole day,
your mother
has been saying this nonstop,
"Fried meat cake..."
She has been chanting that!
What's wrong?
I thought l would do anything
to stop her meat cake chanting
and l did my best
to make a huge meat cake.
Can you imagine just a bit
how l felt at that time?
Don't shout. lt's embarrassing!
Sorry, l haven't done good enough.
I will go and buy something else.
Masao Tanaka
Nana, do you want to hang out
somewhere this weekend?
Why?
We haven't been to anywhere
since we moved here.
Many things happened.
I'm not in the mood.
Many things happened, that's exactly
why we should go out for a change.
Yeah. l'll think about it.
At least go to the city office,
then.
It's time to register our marriage.
I actually wanted you to say that.
Sorry. l am not in the mood
to do that even more.
All right.
Then...
Let's do something
we can do at home.
What will we do?
Let's have a bath together.
That's what you mean?
Now?
- It's too sudden.
- l suddenly want to do it.
I have to do something.
Why? You have been going out
every night lately!
Not every night. Just twice, right?
What?
Okay, then.
Let's fix a date.
What do you mean?
I won't arrange anything
on that day,
and l won't make myself too tired
during the day.
But l don't mean
l want to do it so vigorously,
and l don't want to schedule it.
We do that when our feelings
bond together,
then our bodies bond together too.
Don't say it like a girl.
Fine!
I'll satisfy my unfulfilled desire
by turning it
into the desire for food!
Just look.
Look closely
at how l eat the lettuce!
Look and think
that l really love you!
Okay.
Come here.
See you.
Shota!
Oh, Ono. Good morning.
You look happy.
You can tell?
Could you have expected
to have a present from me?
Oh, what is it?
Ono, this way...
They're sweet rice crackers.
l made them.
The rice, the oil and the syrup used
are all organic.
You can make sweet rice crackers
yourself?
Tell me what you think next time.
I'm in a hurry.
Touo University Hospital
Dr Yamagiwa's murderer
still has not been caught
Truth Weekly
It is your turn to kill
lt is your turn to kill.
Attachment
Yamagiwa was my classmate
in college.
I've always hated him so much
that l wanted to pull his head off
many times.
Someone recorded it.
New email: lt is your turn to kill
Attachment: Movie
Hello, Mr Atsushi Fujii.
Does this look familiar?
It is your bath towel.
On the towel,
your DNA and Yutaro Yamagiwa's DNA
will be found.
This and the voice recording
sent to you just now
will confirm
that you are the murderer.
This is ridiculous!
But if you obey the rule
and do what you should,
l will take the responsibility
and dispose both of them.
Now...
lt is your turn to kill!
Of course it isn't!
First of all...
l don't even know where the guy
l'm supposed to kill is!
The patient is waiting.
What are you doing?
Shut up! l am coming!
This guys is hopeless.
l want to kill him.
I'll call the next patient in now.
Okay, thanks.
Number 214, Mr Tanaka.
Mr Masao Tanaka.
Tanaka?
Masao?
Who is this?
Masao Tanaka
Number 214, Mr Tanaka.
Mr Masao Tanaka.
Tanaka?
Masao?
What...
Oh, my? You are a doctor?
The Bhutanese diner's...
l am the owner, Dorj. Cheers, mate!
Masao Tanaka
But Tanaka...
Oh, l'm sorry.
Actually, l am not Dorj.
What do you mean?
If a Bhutanese restaurant is run
by an Osaka guy with a thick accent,
it won't be popular.
That's why l pretended to be
a Bhutanese guy.
Like, "Welcome!"
That means you are...
Mr Masao Tanaka?
Yes.
Bhutanese Cuisine, Dorj's Diner
l will go home now.
You'll go now?
I have something to do.
Come on, come and watch a DVD
at my place.
I'm going to meet someone.
With your friend
who is staying illegally?
If you don't want me to tell
the police about your friend,
come and watch a DVD at my home!
Hey, this is nasty.
I am not nasty!
I only want to watch a DVD with you
on my fluffy cushion.
You get it, right?
Slow and steady wins the case,
right?
I am home.
You went on a date again?
We just met up after work.
We had dinner, though.
You can invite me occasionally too.
Can we change the topic?
Yes, you can.
Do you know Room 403's Fujii?
What about Fujii?
Fujii came and asked me whether you
and the diner's owner were friends.
What time did he come?
The owner of the number you dialled
cannot answer your call.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
Sir! Mr Dorj!
Masao Tanaka!
Masao Tanaka! Masao Tanaka!
Why? Xinyi, you sound desperate.
Are you alive?
I am alive. l am very alive.
Thank goodness!
Are you alone in the diner?
I am alone.
Why? Have you made up your mind?
You should go home right now!
Should l?
Will you come to my home?
You should have taken my spare key.
But now your friend is safe,
everyone is happy.
What?
It doesn't matter,
you're totally my type.
What can l do?
What are you talking about?
Xinyi, you lit up my heart.
Manager: Murder? Suicide?
Yamagiwa: Killed by the one
who wants the manager dead?
Masao Tanaka: Will Fujii kill him?
Nana, let's do
core training together!
Xinyi. Xinyi, come here.
Come. Hurry!
Hurry up!
Look at this.
- What is it?
- Look at this.
What is this?
It is your turn to kill.
Your Turn to Kill
Your wife didn't tell you
about the game?
Shota found out his wife's lie
Did she lie to you?
Maybe she wrote your name, Sho.
There is another murder--
l just heard a loud noise.
This drama is fictitious