On the first day we moved here,
the residents played a murder-swap
game without me realising it.
It's easier than doing surgery.
During our investigation,
we realised that murders not related
to the game could have happened...
Nana!
But l didn't have time to be sad.
What is this?
Nana...
lt's the last time, please smile.
You want to say something
to your husband, right?
Shota.
I...
There is something
that l have to do.
I've brought the new resident here.
I mainly do research on Al,
artificial intelligence.
My wife was murdered,
and l'd like you to
profile the murderer.
Hey!
You gave my flat's key
to Miss Kinoshita?
It was Room 304's.
My flat?
Miss Kinoshita lives
in Room 401, right?
What are they?
"Room 403, Fujii"
"Room 301, Ono, Room 302, Tezuka"
You're a bit too early.
At this timing,
you have already found me?
Wait, what is going on?
The one who should tell us
what is going on isn't me, is it,
murderer?
What are you talking about, Akane?
Yomogida!
You're noisy.
Come on, don't leave me out!
As you can see,
l have checked everything here.
What have you checked?
For what?
To pursue the truth.
By searching rubbish?
Instead of what people say,
they hide what they really think
in what they don't say.
So, instead of what they treasure,
a person's truth is in
the rubbish they throw away.
By opening many bags of rubbish,
l have found you...
murderer.
Now, will the murderer be honest...
and raise their hand?
What?
"Your Turn to Kill"
Did you hear someone else's voice?
It's a delicate period of time
for Sou!
Did you plot everything?
Mrs Akaike!
Mr Nikaido.
I'm thinking about something.
"Episode 12"
You're joking, right?
Oh, it isn't me. Those...
"Akane Kinoshita"
Akane Kinoshita?
They're all about rubbish.
Did you write all of them?
You haven't been making sense to me.
I wanted to see how you'd react
if l said l have checked everything,
so l said it on purpose.
It didn't upset you at all.
But you surprised me.
I don't suspect you.
Anyway...
it isn't okay to do this.
I've published many stupid books,
but still,
as a social nonfiction writer,
l do this because l think revealing
the truth is my life's purpose.
As you're here,
so l'll check with you.
When the police talked to you
about Akaike's murder,
l somehow heard them say
something like, "Oh, my..."
ls this the song?
Julia!
Yes.
Have you seen a long,
narrow CD like this?
We, especially Shota...
are very sad because
someone close to us was killed.
You said it was your life's purpose,
but it's just for your books.
I am sorry.
Of course the people involved
would feel unpleasant,
but from the real, dark cases,
if we can learn our lesson...
So have you got a clue
who the murderer is?
This is embarrassing,
but not at all.
Did you borrow Room 304's key
to look for the murderer?
Yeah, Ms Kitagawa moved away,
I didn't think that
there would be any clues,
but l wanted to check anyway.
You entered Shota's flat too,
didn't you?
In other words, you're saying
that l killed his wife?
This isn't funny.
Before you suspect someone,
open 100 bags of the rubbish
they threw away.
This is what Rubbish Writer
Kinoshita said.
It's okay, Kuroshima. Let's go.
No, it isn't okay.
This flat is a treasure house
of data.
Let's do some treasure hunting.
Was this found in
Sanae Enomoto's flat?
Yes, sir. Yutaro Yamagiwa's DNA
was found on this bath towel.
Was anyone else's DNA
found on this towel?
We found another person's DNA,
but it isn't a match
with anyone in the Enomoto family.
Oh?
What's the matter?
Nothing, it's just...
Kamiya.
Kamiya!
- Yes, sir?
- Explain.
Regarding this case,
l have nothing more to add.
Not this. Room 302's Nana Hosokawa?
Wait, Hibino?
We use Tezuka for convenience.
I mean Nana Tezuka's call record.
We still haven't found
Nana Tezuka's mobile,
but we've gotten the record.
She talked to Mr Kamiya.
She sought my advice on something.
My husband has gone missing
since this morning.
Is it related to the game?
She said she couldn't get hold
of Shota Tezuka...
lt's what you should've
reported first!
Sorry, sir.
How long had Nana Tezuka been dead
when her body was found?
It was 29 to 31 hours
after her death.
Give us your alibi
during that time, idiot.
Yes, sir. Right away.
Excuse me, sir,
l've got more to report.
What?
The last call was made
to the nurses station.
Well, her husband was hospitalised.
Yes, but it was to
another hospital's nurses station.
"Nurses Station"
What the heck?
That's scary.
We'll borrow these.
Give it back afterwards.
We can't promise you
that we'll give it back.
They aren't originally yours.
I know, but...
Sorry. Thanks.
You have school, right?
- We'll finish the rest alone.
- But...
lt's okay.
Okay.
"Blender Housewife and
her husband's strange life"
Every single one of them...
This is my case.
I have to go to school too.
And l didn't sleep.
"2nd April, at collection point
Yoko lshizaki"
Actually, at that time,
l wrote my own name down.
"Sachiko Akaike"
"Sachiko Akaike."
lt's the name on
the piece of paper l drew.
"25th March,
201 Ukita's rubbish bag"
lnput this...
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Please input them.
"Paper with Yoko lshizaki written
was thrown away on 2nd April"
This one too.
"11th May, 501 Sano's rubbish bag"
But Sano didn't participate
in the game.
Input it anyway.
"Condolence Money Envelope"
"3rd May,
202 Kuroshima's rubbish bag"
Are you not going to defend me?
Please tell me the truth,
so that l can defend you.
When will l be released?
Damaging and abandoning
a dead body will be about 3 years.
Sou will be 17 years old
three years later...
However, if you had also
committed murder...
How is Sou now?
You could be charged
for imprisoning Soichi...
No! l'm asking how his life is now!
Is Masako
looking after him properly?
- I think he's fine.
- l don't care what you think!
Things are now...
very delicate... for Sou now...
He's a teenager.
So, about Yamagiwa's murder...
Yamagiwa doesn't matter at all!
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
It's okay.
I only brought some stuff
for your parents,
but they inspected my belongings
for some reason.
Because you look funny.
What?
Do you mean suspicious
or interesting?
If you mean interesting,
l'll forgive you!
Don't look so serious, teenager,
or l'll kiss you on the cheek.
Let's go home.
Hey!
"Tsutsuji Elderly Home"
Oh? Mrs Sachiko seems to be
in a good mood today.
Yes, thank you.
What's the matter?
You want to watch it?
Wait a minute.
There you go.
- Thank you! Thank you!
- He always sings this.
Thank you for this year too.
l sang my favourite song.
Thank you-- ls he sleeping?
Okay, who requested...
He took my mic!
Oh, my Julia!
Mrs Akaike!
I feel guilty for coming every time
l want to deduce something.
I don't mind, though.
But l'll let you decide.
In that case, l'll borrow it.
Will you help me?
Why are you doing that again, Doyan?
Well...
please don't call me that.
But you hate your first name, right?
So you're Doyan.
Come on, please.
We'll borrow this.
Be careful.
What's this?
Well...
Could this be
the Fibonacci sequence?
Yes, l love it.
"Bochi" what?
- Fibonacci.
Oh. What's that?
Well...
lt's this.
I can stare at
this equation forever.
Yeah.
I think you should explain it
with a diagram.
First, the Fibonacci sequence
is like the
ammonite shell's structure...
lt's all right.
You science people
can get excited about it.
Doyan, what do people call you?
Just Nikaido.
What? lt's so boring.
Thank you for this morning.
Please tell me if you remember
anything else.
It's okay, don't bother.
"Xinyi, Misato and Goro Akaike"
We can't hide anymore!
What's the matter?
Those guys have investigated a lot.
It's a matter of time
that they find out!
What are you talking about?
Mr Tezuka and his friends
wrote things about the game
on the whiteboard,
and it says l killed
Mr and Mrs Akaike!
That's...
They guessed wrong.
Yeah, they guessed wrong, but...
lt's okay, then.
But if they have dug so deep,
they'll find out about you
and our friends' visa!
Mr Tamiya...
Nana...
And Mrs lshizaki too.
"Yoko lshizaki"
Really?
See? That means
Mrs lshizaki didn't lie.
Of course, it isn't
entirely impossible that
someone made a fake one
and threw it away.
And Mr Ukita didn't lie either.
Also...
After what happened,
we can be sure about this too.
"Yutaro Yamagiwa"
"Sanae Enomoto:
Paper drawn: Yutaro Yamagiwa"
Looking at this,
we haven't made much progress.
No.
Also, Miss Kinoshita took this too.
Kuroshima, she got it from
a bag of your rubbish.
Do you remember this?
I...
Will you answer me right away?
If you think too long, l'd think
that you're concocting a lie.
Sure.
My last boyfriend passed away.
What?
I used it for his funeral.
I think you met him once.
- Where's the convenience store?
- l don't know.
Go to the main road and turn right.
lt's just 100 metres away.
He got drunk
and had a fight with a stranger,
and suddenly...
Sorry, l had no idea.
It's okay.
He wasn't a nice person.
He appeared to be very normal,
but he was very violent.
I was often physically abused too,
so l could accept that he died
after a fight.
Of course, l was sad that he died,
and l was surprised too,
but when l was freed
from my boyfriend...
l felt a bit relieved too.
People around me said
l became more cheerful.
She kept shouting
"minced meat cutlet" very loudly.
You talk a lot today.
It's awful to say l became cheerful
because someone died, but...
l think l am more awful.
After listening to what you said,
l still suspect you.
If your boyfriend abused you,
did you actually write his name?
No, l...
Does this person really exist?
Yes, he does.
l think l had mentioned it before...
We are on very bad terms,
and he said he'd definitely
make me repeat.
Make you repeat?
Yes. Why?
Maths Department's Hayakawa?
You study at lnternational Science
and Engineering University too?
Yeah, but l am
a postgrad student now.
Wow, you are my senior!
That professor hates
all the students.
Yes. l don't want to
talk behind his back, but...
But you wrote him as
the person you want to kill.
"Kuroshima, Professor Hayakawa"
l did.
I am sorry!
It's the second time l suspect you
for something l shouldn't.
I'm sorry.
Kuroshima, you have helped me
so much, but l...
l am so horrible!
It's okay. Please don't say that.
Sorry.
Mr Tamiya!
Oh?
Miss Higashi?
What?
You're my junior in the drama group,
but you are experienced in life
and l think l can count on you.
There are other people
l can count on,
but when l was pondering
why l kept thinking about you...
l realised...
that it was love.
In other words, at the critical time,
before our actual performance,
you propose to have
an affair with me?
That isn't my intention.
Please forget it if it is unwanted.
I am a man who has only
dated his wife.
I've been austere in my life, so...
l am so sorry!
So when a young lady like you
says that to me...
l give up easily!
Yes?
Oh, no!
What?
Your hand is soft.
I shouldn't!
No!
I am sorry!
I know l shouldn't
say this now either,
but a short while ago, you said...
l have no time left!
What do you mean?
I thought maybe you had a disease,
so l had to tell you.
Mr Tamiya,
please spend
the rest of your life with me!
It is true that l have no time left,
but l don't have a disease.
There is something
that l haven't done.
What is it? Please tell me!
Live a pure and right life
is my motto.
However, if l want to be right...
sometimes l cannot stay pure.
That's what l really think.
Sorry, l didn't answer
your question.
At least...
l want to make sure
that l was right.
I...
What am l doing?
I'll get that much?
Will you also come on weekends?
Yes, you can count on me.
Will meals be provided?
You can choose from the menu,
but they don't taste good.
Manager! Have pride in your job.
Customers come to enjoy the
nostalgic atmosphere not the food.
"Stand-up meal, school meal"
Well, l need money, but even so...
Manager!
Have you got other outfits?
I'll pay you a lot,
so put up with it.
Mr Ukita's follower number two!
- What?
Excuse me...
l hope you would let me
wear something else if possible.
But it suits you. Or you can wear
the same outfit as Kakinuma's.
Say that before l wear it, jerk!
Oh! Number one too.
What?
I asked you to talk politely
at the restaurant, didn't l?
Endure it!
He is going to pay us a lot, right?
I'm looking forward to it, Manager.
- She's cute.
That got on my nerves!
It seems that he runs
other restaurants too,
we'll use him well.
Somehow that guy creeps me out.
He suddenly started hiring
the residents.
We haven't got a job
after Mr Ukita passed away,
and we have to pay
the out-of-court settlement too.
Before we take revenge for Mr Ukita,
- we should make a living...
- Shut up. l know.
So, follower number two.
- I am Kakinuma!
- Kaki...
And why am l number two?
- Well, you aren't wrong though!
- Right?
She is wrong!
We'll sell something else at
that shop at the end of August.
Idiot, nobody drinks Bubble tea
in autumn.
Now is the time to withdraw.
Ouch!
Drive off the dodgy guy!
Ow...
Ow... Wait, it's me!
It's me!
What?
I am sorry!
But what have you been doing?
What? This is my home.
It's the first time
l see that look on your face.
I decided to sell this flat
after all this,
but l can't find anyone to buy it.
It's a murderers' condo.
I can't stay where l've been
staying forever either.
You were kicked out of
your lover's home.
Anyway, l will live here
starting today.
I absolutely refuse!
What?
You're suspected for dismembering
Kayo with your lover!
I am not suspected.
Go and ask the police.
I suspect you!
The husband is back.
Husband?
Mr Kojima!
He'll stay at that flat again.
Is he okay?
Has he gotten over his wife's death?
Why don't you stop worrying
about other people
and worry about me?
I worry about you.
But you're playing!
Your guitar is noisy.
How can you be so calm?
I can't stay calm,
that's why l do this.
Don't tell me...
Was it you?
What do you mean?
Did you...
Did you plot everything?
- Wait, what are you talking about?
- Don't get near me!
Bon appetit.
So good!
I think l've told you that
l don't like it.
Yes.
But you have to eat properly,
because your body
isn't only yours now.
I'll be fine.
What...
l'm not joking.
l'll cook for you every day.
Every day, until the person
who murdered Nana is arrested.
If you don't like this,
finish making the Al quickly.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, but the data l've got
is insufficient.
If you've kept the texts
and photos you took with Nana,
will you show me all of them?
Sure. Please wait a moment.
"Room deodoriser"
What are you doing?
You'd better tidy up your room.
How did you come in?
Your door wasn't locked.
If your room is messy,
it makes your mind messy...
Ow...
Don't do anything
that makes me suspect you!
What?
If l assume that
you are the murderer,
what do you think l'll do?
Before l turn you to the police,
l'll push you down the balcony.
No, you won't.
I am serious.
I start to think that l can't search
who murdered Nana one by one anyway.
So l'll kill all the residents here.
The murderer must be among you.
That means l'll have taken
my revenge.
That's what l think.
Even l am scared of myself.
I am sorry.
He's scary.
He is scary.
Don't say you can't!
Okay, all right!
Yes!
Please marry me.
Yes.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Why did you lie?
Oh, it's hot!
It's surprisingly tasty!
Yes!
We'll change many times,
we'll love each other
after we change,
and let's fall in love with
each other again and again.
Excuse me.
The pot is getting cold.
Look.
Nana is smiling in all the photos.
Both of you are smiling.
Well, l'm aware that those people
have been fishing for information.
They've been here many times.
So, what are you here for?
I see.
You went down from there?
"Fire ladder"
Room 303 is empty,
and l thought scaring you as much as
possible would be effective.
But you killed the owner yourself.
Why did you get us involved?
At that time,
l thought everyone would shut up
if there were more accomplices.
But the matter
has gotten too serious now.
What? Are you here to blame me?
We aren't.
We're here to apologise.
What?
I hacked into the computer
at your workplace.
"Murderer"
l knew you did it!
It was because
you kept threatening us.
You realised that
l overstayed my visa,
then you threatened us again.
"It's your turn to kill,
or you'll be deported!"
"lt's your turn to kill
That's... Hang on.
It doesn't benefit me
if l talk so much.
I want to be with Cuong forever.
What?
You too, lqbal! l want to stay with
our friends at home.
Yeah?
So l want to work with you
and hide this.
But you still haven't told me
what you want to hide.
We killed Yoshihiko Hakamada.
"Yoshihiko Hakamada"
That's what l thought.
We regret it.
We shouldn't have done this.
To make up for it at least a bit,
- we watched all Hakamada's films.
- All?
"A Touch of Fever" was amazing.
Will you watch it, Fujii?
Yeah, l will...
but how did you kill him?
Iqbal hacked into the computer
at Hakamada's agency.
It's hacking again?
So we got his work schedule
and looked for a place
to attack him.
Iqbal said
that was the only place...
Ouch!
Cut it out!
Hey, handsome,
do you think l'd do anything
just because you're handsome?
I tell you...
l am not going to help you do that!
"Try Up Gym"
Oh? Mr Tezuka.
Good morning.
I haven't seen you in a while.
Yes, l was on holiday.
Starting today,
l will be working again.
Are you okay now?
I am not okay,
but l can pretend to be okay!
Well, someone asked you to be her
personal trainer, what do you say?
I'll do it.
- The lady is waiting over there.
- Okay.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Nice to meet you.
I am Tezuka.
Oops.
"International Science
and Engineering University"
Mr Nikaido.
You really are my senior.
It's a wonder that
we've never met before.
Even if we had,
l had no idea who you were.
Hello?
Oh?
Oh, l'm sorry.
I was thinking about something.
About Shota?
No...
May l?
Wait!
What's the matter?
Sorry, l have to do a presentation.
Soichi?
Sawa!
A cat?
Is that...
He doesn't move.
Do you know where the hospital is?
But l think he's dead.
Don't cry.
Well...
Let's bury him somewhere.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Let's go.
You shouldn't take him around
at such a late hour.
I am very sorry.
But auntie...
Oh? Soichi?
I heard you were staying at
an orphanage!
I am sorry.
I thought you knew.
He has started going to school.
I didn't... What a surprise!
You were in the room
with him, weren't you?
Yes.
I am sorry,
l didn't want him to see
anyone involved in the case,
so l didn't let him
go and say hello.
Okay.
I am sorry.
You are fine, because you're cute.
But l would like to ask
you something.
Not about the case.
Okay.
- When we were imprisoned,
- l said no!
Did you hear another person's voice
besides your dad's and your mum's?
I make my decisions quickly.
I don't really know.
- I see.
- That's enough!
Let's stop here.
There was definitely
a third person's voice.
I told the police too.
Oh, it's Doyan.
What will we have
for supper tonight?
Hello.
May l talk to you for a bit?
See? l knew it!
What do you know?
All these towels belong to
the Enomoto family, right?
Have you realised something?
No.
They are all camel!
Indeed, they are all beige.
Indeed, they are beige.
What about beige?
You call it beige too.
And this is the bath towel that
we found Yamagiwa's DNA on.
It's purple?
This towel doesn't belong to
the Enomoto family, does it?
I see.
If we dig further along that line,
maybe we will find out
who the other DNA belongs to.
I've got something
that might cause a stir.
What is it?
It isn't related to our case,
but the suspects of the murder of
Yoshihiko Hakamada were narrowed down
and they've searched
all over the country.
They seem gentle though.
"Profiling Results"
What do you mean?
For example, most of
the Japanese people are this tall,
which means we don't know anything.
Why do you show me this?
I just want to.
You seem to expect too much from Al,
so l should tell you how little
the data we now have can do.
What about "committed by
the same murderer" here?
It's the probability that
Nana and the other victims here were
killed by the same person.
But l have too little data about
this too and l can't say anything.
Did the data about
Ono and Fujii help?
Somehow you look scary.
We found that
the chemical used to kill her
was pharmaceutical
potassium chloride.
Well, l doubt it.
Especially in Dr Fujii's case...
What?
Potassium chloride
was what killed her.
If we let the Al analyse it
when we have so few samples,
it'll say Fujii is the murderer.
I thought Fujii was suspicious too.
It is a chemical that
a doctor can easily get.
We use the Al to avoid
simple guesses like this.
Thank you. See you tomorrow.
Okay.
Good night.
I have to eliminate
the possibility one by one.
Right, Nana?
You come here every day.
This isn't right.
Wait...
Hey... What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Looking for evidence.
That's trespassing!
It is. Please call the police.
I will!
I'll call the police!
They'll be here at once!
You'll be in trouble!
Then, l'll say to them,
"This guy killed Nana!"
The police will search your flat.
Are you okay with that?
With what?
Will you really be okay
even if they search your flat?
Yeah, l will.
You talk like a child when you lie.
Hey! Wait... No! Hang on...
Oh?
Oh, gosh! lt isn't my fault, okay?
We've got some breaking news.
This May,
Actor Yoshihiko Hakamada was killed
in a mountain in Tochigi Prefecture,
and photos of the murder suspects
have been released.
The wanted men are
an Iranian man Ali Moharrami
and an American...
This is Kuroshima.
Shota, can you watch the TV now?
Please call back
when you hear my message.
Stop it.
No...
lt's getting more and more serious
and l don't know
what they're saying.
"Your Turn to Kill"
l am Minami and
l've moved to Room 502.
What a nuisance.
He had a smile on his face.
In details!
I'll say everything.
I beat him with a hammer.
When will this stop?
About Miss Kuroshima.
She is strange.
Why?