On the first day we moved
to our new flat,
at the residents' association
meeting...
- Do you want to kill me?
- Pardon?
And our conversation started.
Everyone has a moment
that they want to kill someone
or just want them dead, right?
I want to kill them
if I wouldn't be caught,
but I will, right?
The police first checks
if there is someone
among the people the victim
knew had a motive to kill them.
So if someone has no motive,
they won't be caught?
I think it'd be difficult.
Then no one will find out if we swap
the targets we want to kill.
It's murder-swap, right?
Why don't we reveal it together?
Before I realised,
it turned into a game that we tell
each other who we want to kill.
Do not show other people.
Now, open it!
I thought it was a silly joke...
"Takafumi Kono"
But on that night...
"Our property manager”
You mean he suddenly fell down?
"Sumida Police Station detective,
Masato Kamiya"
Yes. I had no idea
that it was a man at first,
so I was shocked
when I went outside.
Where was your husband at that time?
He is on a business trip.
Good evening, Sir.
Mr Mizuki.
- Is he dead?
- Would you like to check?
Idiot! It's scary!
It's fine if you've checked.
"Sumida Police Station detective,
Youji Mizuki"
But...
- have you checked the roof?
- Yes, Sir.
There was no trace of struggle,
so it could be suicide.
If it's the case,
he could've fallen anywhere,
but he fell in front of this flat.
Does it mean anything?
I see.
- Sir, will you go to the roof--
- I said I'm scared!
- Mr Kamiya.
- Yes?
"Room 402, Masashi Enomoto"
Good evening.
"Room 302, Nana Tezuka"
"Room 302, Shota Tezuka"
- Maybe I should take a day off?
- Why?
You must feel helpless on your own.
I know I should mind
my own business,
but this happened on
the first day you moved here,
so I thought you must be worried.
Yes, I am worried, but I'm okay.
Well, I'm the chairlady
of the residents' association,
but we take turns to do it
so I guess you can't count on me.
Don't say that.
Thank you for coming.
By the way, it was suicide, right?
Why? Could he have been killed?
No, it's just there are
so many police officers here.
Indeed! If in the unlikely case
that it was murder, this--
- Oh, aren't you going to be late?
- But...
Sanae is here and I really am fine.
Okay then, I'll go now.
- See you.
- Thank you, ma'am.
- See you!
Nana, do you have to go to work?
I work at home.
Do you?
It's shocking to know
that someone I know died.
And he killed himself.
Yes, he killed himself.
Yes. It's upsetting
that he killed himself.
Ground floor.
"Obey the rules properly”
"Our property manager”
"Room 403, Atsushi Fujii"
The tough time continues.
Dr Yamagiwa, is there any
breakthrough in the treatment?
Well, I'm a doctor,
so I shouldn't say this,
but you can only treat the symptoms
of hay fever when they appear.
For example--
I'll go now.
Ground floor.
"Manager's office"
"Room 204, Jun Nishimura"
Maybe I should attend the next
residents' association meeting?
You and the chairlady seemed close,
and I am jealous.
It's not fair that only you
became friends with them!
We played Werewolf
and became friends.
You don't actually want to attend,
right? I'll go next time too.
Mr Tezuka, the members are here.
Sorry, coming!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Let's get fired up and be friends
with our muscles today!
- Okay.
"Our property manager"
"Your Turn to Kill"
"Episode 2"
"Touo University Hospital"
Come again a week later.
- Take care.
"Nurse, Ruri Sakuragi"
Schlecken!
- Dr Fujii.
- Yes?
You think I don't know if you say
something dirty in German?
What did I say?
You always do that, that's why
you can never get married.
Oh, what you just said
was more insulting.
If you appear on TV,
maybe you'll get a bit popular
like Doctor Yamagiwa,
who is popular lately.
Don't lump me in
with Yutaro Yamagiwa!
You know his full name?
Are you a fan?
Of course I am not!
It beeps every day
and it's so noisy.
Sorry, I'm practising
how to reverse my car.
You can't drive at all.
Don't drive a car better than mine.
"Amulet"
"Tokoshima"
Mr Mizuki, I found it.
He wrote a suicide note?
No, it's...
Hey, sprinkle some salt
before you come close!
It's a hospital's
medical certificate.
What?
"Disease: Brain tumor"
Seems that he had a brain tumor.
He gave in to despair
and killed himself?
By the way, about the manager...
Don't talk about that.
No. I think it wasn't suicide.
Just drop it.
But a murder doesn't happen
so close to us every day.
The case is worth deducing.
It's not appropriate.
Why? Isn't it more inappropriate
to let the real culprit
go unpunished?
I think we should seek the truth.
The police said it was suicide,
then it's the truth.
The truth is,
it's always the orangutan.
- You get it, right?
- I do, but...
So listen to me, great detective.
Stop calling me that.
I have almost found out the answer.
It'll get cold.
The real culprit is...
Room 301's Ono!
Nice to meet you.
"Room 301, Mikiha Ono"
Our next door?
I checked all the flats just now.
Only Room 301's Ono actually uses
the name plate made by the manager.
So maybe they were
in a relationship?
Their relationship turned ugly.
Thanks for supper.
How was my suspicion?
Look! It's bull's-eye!
Don't you think?
Who knows?
Are you worried?
But if something bad happened,
something good must happen too.
Don't worry.
Yes, the leaflet.
The food allergens aren't written,
what do you think about this?
Yes.
No, no need to call your manager.
I only want to know what you think.
Ground floor.
Is everybody there?
Misato, Mr Tamiya...
"Room 104, Yoko Ishizaki"
I've called Miss Ono here.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
Sorry, we're late.
There are even fewer of us
than last time.
- Mrs Enomoto.
- Okay.
"Room 103, Junichiro Tamiya"
We suddenly asked you to come today
to talk about our property manager,
Mr Tokoshima.
Well...
Should our residents' association
send flowers to his funeral?
You called us here just for that?
Yes.
He had been helping us.
No need to check and just send them.
We'll use the reserve,
so we'd better check first.
Let's vote to make the decision
now, then.
But will 2 funerals be held?
Of course there'll be.
"Room 101, Yuzuru Kuzumi"
But...
Even for someone who killed himself.
Mr Fujii, what you said wasn't nice.
Of course, I agree
that we should send flowers,
but how much gift money
should we send?
Let's discuss the amount.
"Room 502, Misato Akaike"
Why don't we send a sum together?
But how much per person?
Let's agree on that.
Mr Tamiya worked at a bank.
Let's ask him.
My former job isn't related.
But you must've been to many
funerals of small company owners
who killed themselves
because you didn't lend them money.
You've been acting mean!
"Room 203, Xinyi"
Tamiya, you're always so unique.
Xinyi, Mr Tamiya didn't say
anything funny.
Gosh!
I got it wrong!
How can you smile?
He could've been killed
because of you.
Because of me?
If you hadn't said the police would
not find out about murder-swap,
we wouldn't have told each other
who we wanted to kill.
I didn't suggest the murder-swap.
Wait. First of all, none of us wrote
the property manager, right?
He was so close to us.
What?
Actually...
This was pinned on the notice board.
"Our property manager"
Whose handwriting is it?
Will you drop this?
But this...
Put yourselves in the shoes
of the person who wrote it.
They wrote the manager's name
as a joke,
but he happened to kill himself.
I'm sure that the person
can't describe how they feel now.
You are right.
That's why
they can't attend today...
That means it was Mrs Kitagawa?
"Room 304, Sumika Kitagawa"
We don't know who wrote it!
I am sorry.
In the end,
we all happily wrote a name.
We're all accomplices.
Don't say that! I am not involved!
- I am not either!
- Right?
This is not right!
Let's throw it away. Give me this.
What? Do you suspect me?
Just so you know,
I wrote Yutaro Yamagiwa.
Could you possibly mean
Doctor Yamagiwa?
"Dr Yamagiwa (Yutaro Yamagiwa)
Director of Yamagiwa Medical Clinic"
Who's that?
He appears on TV?
The doctor is a pundit
on talk shows.
Yamagiwa was my classmate
in college.
I've always hated him so much,
that I wanted to pull his head off
many times.
Okay. I said it honestly.
Whose name did you guys write?
"Manager's office"
Why don't you say anything?
You guys are a lot more suspicious
than me.
Stop it, Mr Fujii.
So as I thought,
it wasn't a suicide.
The man was murdered
by someone among you?
- I said...
- By the way,
let's say that one of you
wrote "Our property manager" here.
Someone killed the man
that you want dead,
so you have to kill the person
on the piece of paper you drew,
or you'll violate the rule.
Nobody mentioned this rule!
But you made someone
take the risk for you,
how can you stay safe yourself?
Wait. We did write the name
of the person we want dead,
we didn't tell anyone to kill them!
Well, that woman said you wouldn't
be caught if it was a murder-swap,
so someone took it seriously.
I said, I didn't...
- What are you doing?
- Wait!
We all get suspicious
because of this.
- It's evidence...
- I'll eat it.
- Gosh!
- Mr Tamiya!
What are you doing? Spit it out!
He swallowed it.
Nobody in this residential tower
is a murderer!
- You know...
- Yes?
I don't like to gossip,
but Mr Tamiya is too serious
and many things happened
to him at work.
He was made to resign early
because of that.
Even now, his serious power
has gotten too strong.
Have a good evening...
Please move the tables to the edge.
Okay.
Please move this there.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
It's yours.
I'll give you back the 1,000 yen.
"Room 202, Sawa Kuroshima"
Thanks for your help.
- Well...
- Yes?
This is cute.
Right?
It is cute, isn't it?
Excuse me.
There you are!
He's my husband.
Hello.
What's the matter?
The window is broken.
What?
What happened?
The window!
Masashi?
Oops.
So... I was passing by
when I saw the broken window.
I think some of you don't know,
but I am a police officer.
So I've been checking
the office again.
Gosh, you startled me!
I thought it was
Mr Tokoshima's ghost.
I did frighten you, didn't I?
Sorry for bringing you trouble.
Oh, excuse me...
Yes?
In the end, our property manager...
We inspected his home
and found that he had a disease.
In other words?
He killed himself
after worrying for some time.
At least, we think
that it wasn't a murder.
I see.
It was suicide.
We had no idea
that he had a disease.
I knew it!
I thought his face was pale.
Everyone,
I know you must be worried...
"Room 401, Akane Kinoshita"
Anyway, shouldn't you have been
a bit more helpful?
I am sorry.
Don't just say sorry.
Why do I have to be suspected?
Because of that,
that Central Circular Route and...
It's so annoying.
Go and switch it off.
From the Gotanda part
of the inner route
of the Central Circular Route,
vehicles in front
of Hey Junction...
- Hey...
- Yes?
Did you keep the receipt
of our dinner last night?
Receipt!
You talk too loudly.
Receipt.
- Receipt.
- Wait a second.
This?
Okay.
Now we have an alibi.
At the time that the manager died,
we were having dinner outside.
It's the unmistakable truth.
Does the police suspect us?
No, nobody suspects us.
But! I'm saying, but...
I don't know who will try to frame
me at this period of time.
I'll cause everyone in
the deputy chief's faction trouble.
Do you get it?
Until our faction wins,
I have to do everything carefully.
"Chiunque Kuramae"
After the property manager's funeral
was held,
we took back the peaceful life
we had until then.
- See you!
- See you.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Hurry up, Sora! Come on!
See you.
Wait for me!
The property manager's death
was sad,
but when nothing happens
in our daily life,
it becomes the power
that helps us overcome sadness,
and we all know that.
"Room 201, Ryo Kakinuma"
Watch it! What are you doing?
Hurry up! I'll cut your neck next.
- It will get messy soon anyway.
- Shut up.
Here you go.
The day is getting longer.
It looks like the setting sun
in Van Gogh's painting, Misato.
Van Gogh?
"Room 502, Sachiko Akaike,
Goro Akaike"
Yes.
Sower with Setting Sun?
It's a nice painting.
Misato could almost remember it.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Speaking of setting sun,
"The zinc roofing
eats a rice cracker..."
And then what?
Yes?
Chuya.
It's Chuya Nakahara's poem.
"Ashes being thrown underhanded
go pale."
And?
Go pale...
"It is quiet
when the sun sets in spring."
I told you.
Misato was just going to answer me.
Yeah.
The poem was written in
a middle school textbook.
How can Misato not know it?
I wasn't good at
Japanese literature.
Oh, I am so sorry.
Your Japanese is worse than
a middle school child.
I had no idea. Will you forgive me?
Of course.
Glad to hear that!
I'm so happy!
It's nice that
you're always so happy.
Thank you! I roll with laughter
every single day!
Let's go.
Oh, hey?
Mr Tezuka?
- Oh! Hello.
- Hello.
- What's the matter?
- Nothing, your hair accessory...
I mean...
Oh, this?
It looks so good on me, right?
You praised me. I'm so happy.
So maybe it isn't exactly
a thank you gift...
What is it?
Wafers.
I made it.
What?
I've never seen anyone
make wafers themselves.
It isn't cut, so maybe
it's difficult to eat.
- May I?
- Sure.
Thank you.
- It's good!
- It is, right?
I made it with organic rice flour.
I haven't tried this before.
Is there anything
that you have never tried before?
It can be anything,
I want to be your first, Mr Tezuka.
What the heck? You're funny.
But it's really good.
Glad to hear that.
Yes, there are three
of each color pattern,
so there are 21 patterns in total.
Yes. If you would check it.
Okay, thank you.
Sanae?
Sorry, I shouldn't cry.
Reversing a car is difficult
until you get used to it.
Okay, it's parked.
Thank you so much!
I feel so ashamed of myself!
Mr Tezuka,
your new customer is here.
Already?
Thanks.
Mr Hosokawa,
who applied for our personal plan?
Yes, I'm Hosokawa.
"Asao Hosokawa"
Your goal is to keep yourself fit,
so we'll tighten your waistline
after you get used to it a bit.
Sure. Thank you.
You can count on me!
Okay, let's begin our first step.
Please call me Sho
when we're doing the training.
- Sho?
- Yes, Sho.
But may I say no?
Does it make you shy?
Does anybody not feel shy?
But during training,
your body will be under stress,
it'll be difficult to call me
“trainer” or "Mr Tezuka".
So we'll keep our names short.
My name is Shota,
so please call me Sho.
Now, say "Sho"!
Sho.
Once more.
Say it louder.
Sho!
Three times!
Sho! Sho! Sho!
Okay, let's do some stretching!
Then, the new customer said
that he loved detective stories,
so I was really happy too.
What should I lend him?
Don't tell him how it ends.
When you recommend someone
a detective story you like,
you say the ending first.
I don't.
"It's amazing!
The murderer was shot up to the sky
with the fireworks
and died in pieces mid-air!"
You said that.
That was the best final scene.
But I couldn't enjoy it
because I knew how it'd end.
Okay.
What?
What is that?
Oh, I bought it for a change.
It's a coffee maker.
Its design is good, right?
Yeah. How much was it?
A bit over 30,000 yen?
It's expensive!
I stay at home all day,
it's capital investment.
You did it again.
It's your bad habit.
You use difficult words to try
to draw away my attention!
No, capital investment
aren't difficult words.
Moreover, I paid it myself. Why not?
What? I didn't say it
because I have no money.
Sorry. What is it, then?
Yes, indeed,
I can't pay half of the sum of that.
I can't. But you've bought it.
So I'll pay.
Because we own it together.
I want everything in our flat
to be our common property.
I'll buy things after asking you
next time.
That's not what I mean.
It is true that the amounts
of our income are different,
but I don't want you to consider
my feelings and my income
and hold yourself back
from buying things you want.
It makes me sad
if you're considerate in that way.
But I don't want you to buy things
without considering me too.
So just get something I can pay
half of from the start!
Say you want a coffee maker
that costs 5,800 yen!
My point is,
please be careful not to let me
find out how much it really is!
Oh, this is fine,
but it is like I am lying to you,
and it makes me feel guilty.
No. It's a lie if you consider
my feelings and I find out.
But if I don't find out,
it's kindness.
If you save up
to three kindnesses like that,
it turns into love.
On the contrary, if there is love,
you can show me such kindness
three times.
Oh, I mean just in one day.
Three times a day.
That means, I can be kind to you
1,095 times in a year.
It applies to the opposite case!
If you live up to 100 years old,
then you can show me
such kindness 54,750 more times!
You can do calculations so quickly!
I can do all addition, subtraction,
multiplication but not division.
I'm glad that we're married.
Why?
I don't know.
I just thought of that
when I looked at you just now.
But your husband can't do division.
Everyone will laugh at you.
Even if everyone laughs at me,
I fell in love with you.
So I can't leave you anymore.
Wait...
There were more varieties of things
at the supermarket we went to today.
Yeah, let's find out more places.
I found an interesting restaurant
right after we said that.
What is Bhutan cuisine?
I'll look it up.
Sir Tezuka!
- Take one.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Come with me.
Welcome.
- Oh, what.
- What?
In 2018...
You bump into your neighbours
quite often here.
I came here to eat alone,
but there are four people now.
Hey, beer!
Beer!
- Oh, beer?
- Yeah.
Would you please wait?
What the heck?
This is very spicy.
Bhutan cuisine seems to be
the world's most spicy.
It's hot!
Tell me, where did you two meet?
Well, both of our jobs
are sports-related.
All right, so you met at work?
No one I meet at work
falls in love with me,
that's why it's tough for me!
Nobody knows what you're talking
about if you get angry suddenly.
It's obvious!
I'm saying that I'm not popular.
Right?
I'm impressed
that you got yourself a man.
How did you get this young husband?
I...
Oh, I pursued her relentlessly.
You pursued her?
I kept pursuing her,
but she kept rejecting me.
About 30 times.
Thirty times? Why?
Don't ask them every detail.
It's fine! She wants to talk.
Obviously, our age gap,
and I had divorced once too.
Correct!
Yours.
Change the channel!
Would you please wait?
What the heck?
It was found at another river...
It's the Doctor Yamagiwa you hate.
That's why I want
to change the channel.
You hate him? I quite like him.
He doesn't just hate him. Right?
Speaking of which,
who drew my ballot paper?
What paper?
Shota, try this.
It's hot!
Fujii!
What? I have to change it myself?
Let's start.
Six buildings in Meguro were burned.
Anyway, many things happened
in the past.
The doctor was his classmate
in college.
He is no big deal as a doctor,
but it annoys me that he earns
so much as a celebrity.
This will never end
if you kill him just for that.
That's not all.
What, for example?
What do you want to talk about?
Have you finally made up your mind
to marry Kaoru?
Well, almost like that.
You've been dating
since you were students.
I'm amazed
that she waited for so long.
Kaoru?
Well, she's the girl you loved
originally, right?
What? She was just a cute junior
in the club I joined.
But you confessed your love for her.
It's been a long time,
so I'll tell you.
At that time, Kaoru asked me
to pretend to be her boyfriend
because you were too persistent.
It was boring just to pretend.
So I slept with her.
Well, whatever the reason was,
you dated for a long time
and you'll finally get married.
I'm happy.
No, I'm dating an actress.
She's in the morning drama.
What?
I'm thinking about marrying her.
What about Kaoru?
That's why,
it's time to go for Kaoru.
Maybe even you can do it too.
Don't be afraid!
She won't cost you a lot,
even if you only have a modest
income as a hospital doctor,
she isn't going to complain.
I promise.
Mr Fujii?
I can still stand it
if it was only about me,
but that's not all!
What?
It's not fun if I just kill him.
I'll travel back in time
and kill Yamagiwa
when he was in college
and I'll start my life over again
in a world without him!
Mr Fujii!
I want to kill him more and more!
- Mr Fuji
- What?
Look!
What?
It was identified
as the missing celebrity
and doctor,
Yutaro Yamagiwa,
Doctor Yamagiwa.
Our reporter, Sasaki,
is at the scene
where the body was found.
Dr Yutaro Yamagiwa's body
was found here
in a forest in Isehara City,
Kanagawa Prefecture.
In the forest 300 metres ahead,
Dr Yamagiwa's body was found
buried underground.
It wasn't me.
Is it okay to leave Mr Fujii there?
Well, he wanted to be alone.
Anyway, Yamagiwa--
Oh, hurry up! Run!
Hey, wait.
Okay.
What?
You two had better train
your quadriceps muscles again!
Could he be killed
by one of the residents as well?
"As well'? Please don't say that.
Also...
Yes?
Did you tell your husband
about the game?
I didn't tell him.
It's a long story.
Xinyi.
We're closing.
Fujii, what about the rule?
Rule? What are you talking about?
If someone killed your target,
you have to kill theirs.
You said this.
I was joking. There is no such rule.
You're saying
that you won't kill anyone?
Why do you only talk to me
so casually?
Fujii, just go home!
Someone killed the man
whom you want dead,
so you have to kill the person
on the piece of paper you drew too,
or you'll violate the rule.
"Masao Tanaka"
Who is this?
"Obey the rules properly”
"Chiunque Kuramae"
"Room 501, Go Sano"
- Morning.
You bought more?
Yeah, there's a follow-up story
about the murder.
In the news, it was only reported
that the body was dismembered,
but it seems that his head
hasn't been found, great detective.
I don't want to hear that
so early in the morning.
The suspect hasn't been found--
Really, stop.
Sorry...
It's okay. I should be the one
to apologise.
"Dr Yamagiwa's Dead Body.
Where is his head?"
"Truth Weekly"
- Dr Fujii.
- Yes?
What?
You'll open the plastic bag, right?
What do you think I am?
You always tear it open.
I look forward
to working with you today too.
"Mr Atsushi Fujii"
"Where is his head?"
"It is your turn to kill."
Could he be killed...
by one of the residents as well?
Fourth floor.
Yes?
What's the matter?
This.
What is this?
"It is your turn to kill."
Lately, I've been getting them
every day when I go home.
Something like this too.
"Soliciting to murder"
What does this mean?
Ask the person who put it
through my door for details.
And warn everyone
not to play pranks like this!
Last Monday,
celebrity and doctor,
Yutaro Yamagiwa's body was found...
"Off"
Hair...
"Dr Yamagiwa
Where is his head?"
"Your Turn to Kill"
"The next person to be killed is..."
It says that it's my turn to kill!
Mr Fujii is getting
threatening letters.
"Rule of murder-swap"
You aren't thinking that
it's your turn to kill, right?
This is ridiculous!
The culprit has to be someone
from the residential tower.