An murder-swap game that was played without me realising it
Stop ~~‼
To conceal the crime
A runaway person appears...
Maybe Sanae's child.
As soon as I realized that there might be some murders
Unrelated to the game...
Nana-chan
I'm full of revenge.
Then, little by little...
It's trespassing!
I'm getting close to that someone,
The unknown murderer...
I can only hope...
Sora-kun, it's been a long time.
Brother, Did you get out?
I came to room 502. I'm Minami.
- 502?
- Akaike-san's...?
- That person.
Gave me a good looking...
Birthday night?
♪ ~ Julia ~
Sano ~
Grandmother!
What are you doing?
Grandmother! Can you hear!?
Grandma! Grandmother!
That person?
Say someone gave her something.
Huh?
So when I asked who that person was...
Ah... wasn't that person your dead wife?
Nana-chan?
Yes, the day when Mr. Akaike's incident occurred...
Isn't it too flashy?
You look great
What does it mean…?
Kuzumi-san
Ah, Tezuka-san.
I'm glad I was there.
No, he's not ready to talk.
I think it's hard just because I woke up.
- No, it's not.
- Nice to meet you...
- Huh?
- That is...
- It's not memory loss...
- Nice to meet you.
My name is Yoshihiko Hamada.
What?
He has regained consciousness
but he doesn't know himself
He thinks he is Yoshihiko Hamada.
When he was 18 years old.
- What about the incident?
- Seem like he doesn't remember.
- Damn...
- Well, about him?
You will have to monitor the progress.
That's right...
Take a leisurely investigation.
You're good at investigating.
Well don't bully me ~.
I have found out.
The fingerprint on the paper labeled “Yoko Ishizaki”.
- Whose was?
- Uhm about that...
Residents whose fingerprints were detected...
Great...
Yes?
Residents' association.
Forcing me to talk to you
What is the intention?
Ms. Ono please tell me about the paper
you wrote and drawn.
Search for the criminal who killed Nana.
Yes, for Tezuka-san.
- Isn't it good?
- With who?
Oh Tezuka-san and me?
Huh...
Thank you for this time.
Would you like to go back together?
If you promise not to speak from the beginning.
Let's go home now!
Ah!
No...
Huh...
Eh ~ Ono's
Organic grilled corn
is chosen.
Then, the accountant and the cook
- And the caller...
- I...
I will refuse the same person as that person.
Huh...
Then I will run as a poster clerk.
Instead, no participation on the day.
Ahh! I understand.
- What are you doing?
- That person
While you are attending the festival
- He is trying to commit the next murder.
- Oh? next….
- What... what do you mean?
- Details now.
- In other words, this person...
- Wait.
- Wait!
- Please stop talking scary stories.
Chairman has spoken!
By the way, only your wife legs has been found.
- Where is the rest?
- The rest, you said...
Minami-san, such a story is...
- Good idea?
- Everyone is interested.
So isn't it fun to talk about the festival?
Isn't it obvious?
There are times and places to worry about.
That's right!
Now it's best to calm down and think about the festival.
It is certainly like a festival.
The event to create an extraordinary space together.
There is also an idea that the preparation time is bliss.
- Everyone, get along well.
- Wow, your story
I won't come in!
It's a fresh reaction.
We are already used to this.
Hahaha... Huh...
Ah...
Well... I'm sorry.
Then you entered Fujii's room no. 403.
Wrap Yamagiwa head with a bath towel in the room
Left it in the washing machine and then recovered.
- Are you sure?
- There is no mistake.
But...
- You were in another place.
- No?
- Just before Mr. Fujii came home
- Please listen!
That matter has been confirmed.
And then you immediately leave the room
You were shopping at a nearby convenience store.
It has been confirmed with the security camera video
Wasn't your husband stealing the master key?
Several residents have witnessed your husband invading the manager's room.
Was your husband who entered Fujii's room?
Yes I'm sorry.
I lied to cover my husband.
However, your husband
He was drinking at a girls bar with colleagues.
Who are you really trying to cover?
Is that also?
I need your help in each shift.
Each time allocation is...
Can you tell me how to cook?
Just grilling?
But what is the organic part?
Ono-san, explain.
- Ono-san?
- Eh?
Explain what is different from ordinary corn.
Ah... It doesn't use pesticides or chemical fertilizers.
Recently, there are a lot of fertilizers used.
You see, the absorption of cesium
Something to hold back.
I don't understand what you said at all.
Ne everyone...
Oh, potassium chloride.
The poison used for the killing is...
I understand that it was potassium chloride.
Is Ono-san familiar with fertilizer?
Is there an obligation to answer personal questions?
Well, as a fertilizer you can get it online
It's safe, but potassium chloride itself
or animal euthanasia in the United States,
It is a drug used for execution.
Right? Dr. Fujii.
Huh? Yeah...
Minami-san, you are familiar.
- Actually I….
- You
- What have you been doing since a while ago?
- Ahh….
I'm taking the minutes.
What is it for?
It's my fault.
I've been complaining that there are too many residents meeting
Make sure the meeting is organized in one session.
Oh, yes.
I'm sorry for causing you inconvenience.
So today's resident association is finished.
That!
This is a paper with the name of Ishizaki.
- That!
- It was thrown away
Ms. Kinoshita discovered it.
I want to know who drew it.
Show me a bit...
Isn't it okay to answer honestly?
Mrs. Ishizaki is safe.
There is no doubt.
Well certainly.
I asked the police to check for fingerprints.
Fingerprints other than Mr. Kinoshita whose remained on this paper
Ms. Kitagawa, Mr. Kuzumi, Mr. Manager
Mr. Tamiya.
Mr. Fujii.
Ms. Ono.
6 people.
Did you get your hands on it when you drew the paper?
I just touched it at that time.
I mean, Wasn't it Mr. Manager?
Well, there is a possibility.
When was first time Ishizaki-san told everyone she wrote it herself?
At that time, no one came forward.
The person who was already dead at that time must drew.
Uhm...
Yes.
Ah, okay, but nothing yet.
- Yeah...
- All the residents are weird.
You usually move, don't you?
- Then do you believe in Ono-san?
- Do you believe her?
- I thought there was nothing.
- Yeah.
Paper that doesn't need to be hidden
After all, the previous manager drew it...
Damn! Not a clue...
Such...
It's progressing step by step.
Sorry.
If it's not the husband
There is only one person left.
It's Soichi.
So-chan was locked up in handcuffs.
How did he get out? So that...
Wrong!
No different, different...
So-chan... Not so-chan!
Um... different!
Wrong!
Wrong! Different, different...!
No different...!
You are disqualified from investigation!
- Be replaced, Be replaced!
- Just calm down!
- This guy... Let this guy do it!
- Please calm down.
Be replaced be replaced! Be replaced be replaced!
Instead...!
Soichi-kun.
I just went to my room.
I wanted to return this.
Oh, I'll give you.
It's originally a gift and I'm not good at letters.
Well then.
In terms of possibilities, the son will become the most suspicious.
Maybe he was forced to do it
Did he do it on his own?
14 years old carrying pad thai….
Thank you.
No….
Nana-chan was so happy.
No matter how many times I hug her.
I still want to hug her even more.
It's great to meet such person
Fibonacci
The story is probably love.
Let's go home
What's wrong?
It's the current result,
but it's a little interesting.
After all, Akaike couple, Ukita-san and Nana-san were killed
The possibility of the same person is high.
And the relevance to the murder-swap game seems weak.
But someonewho has the motive to kill all four...
I don't think so.
The criminal has the taste of committing murder in search of pleasure.
From that point, analyzing the data of the residents...
Huh?
I can't conclude that it's a certain murderer.
This is a fairly high percentage.
Wasshoi Wasshoi...
Wasshoi Wasshoi
It's true that Soichi is a little bit strange
Even now I still really wonder if he could escape from that room.
What did he want me to do at that time?
I think a lot.
However, the cat is dead
He wanted to bring it to the hospital.
He is a very kind boy...
- This boy killed cat.
- Eh?
The rate at which animals
are harmed before the killer commits an incident
is quite high.
This feels good….
Uh... I can't understand.
No...
I'm sure there are many strange things.
In the first place, Soichi was on the veranda?
He was handcuffed when we were confined.
And the absolutely off limit cooler box.
I was curious. There was no lock or anything.
But when Nana-san was killed
Wasn't Soichi in the facility?
That's... right.
I understand that, but wait a little longer...
This time there is a guy who can catch the tail.
Ah..
Huh...
- Ah... Ms. Sakuragi Stop...!
- All right!
No, no!
You're overdoing... Stop Stop.
If you don't do too much...?
That...
Do you want to kill someone, Tezuka-san?
Huh?
I've been having too much laughing at work.
There was such a man as to feel murderous.
If you don't let it go like this, you can't be serious.
If this is enough for you,
then you'll have to go ahead.
Are you going about another set?
Please listen.
In the first place, my workplace...
- I don't think there's anything to say this morning.
- Eh?
- Ah... I'm a little busy now.
- In front of Shota-san
What about the overjoy of the criminal hunting?
- Did I look like that?
- I saw it.
- Itadakimasu.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Nikaido-san probably doesn't know but...
Shota-san was a much brighter person before.
I want him to go back to the original Shota-san...
- What is it?
- No...
You're gonna eat so much...
Huh? Ahh….
If you have a problem,
your blood sugar level will go down.
- Huh...
- Huhu...
- Don't look like that.
- Ah… I'm sorry.
Kitagawa-san, excuse me?
Ah detective.
- In the case of the murder-swap game.
- Is it going to be solved?
No... Well...
- Oh, are you together?
- Yeah.
I make my decision quickly
- That? That child...
- Just a little bit will do.
- I want to cooperate.
- Thank you.
I'll buy some drinks.
You have had trouble with Kojima before
- So you just wrote her name.
- Yes.
But until who drew my paper...
Eh, you can use the game
AND KILLED KOJIMA.
I can imagine it.
What about the night of May 21?
Ahh….
Ah, I was broadcasting live at night.
I was in the station before and after the broadcast time.
- You can check it.
- I see
There is information that a threatening sentence was flying around.
In my place... No threat.
Hey, can I go to brother's house?
Eh ~ It's annoying.
Then we will still play in the park.
Uhm... When I was protected...
You were there, weren't you?
Yes, il'm Mizuki of Sumida Station.
Can you delivered message to my mom?
To tell her I'm fine.
I got it.
I'm used to school
I'm doing a lot of experimentation.
We met at this park by chance.
Is he Enomoto's child?
Yeah well... what about the incident?
I read daily newspapers.
Ahh….
But he's a very honest child
I am relieved.
That brat...
Why are you here?
I'm really sorry. I had you come often.
No...
Did you remember about Nana Tezuka?
So what about Akaike-san?
Mr. Ukida.
There is a possibility
that everyone is killed by the same criminal.
Uh….
So what about Hosokawa Asao?
Please don't kill this person by mistake.
It's fragmentary but I remembered something.
Yes.
It is a large and bright place.
I'm swinging golf.
At that time, two women called out...
Is that Nana-chan?
Another one?
No….
RIKACO and Yuki Matsushita.
- What?
- So why
I was asked if the appeal performance
was a golf swinging...
It maybe
Isn't this about the
Junon Superboy contest?
That's right!
Those two are judges...
Mr. Kuzumi!
You're not Yoshihiko Hamada!
Then...
None of that Grand Prix?
- Huh….
- Tezuka-san?
Ah….
So as soon as I woke up,
You called Nana.
Yes.
At that time, she said, “I'll be right there.”
The shift was over, so I went home.
But the next day
I heard you didn't see your wife yet...
Can't answer the phone right now.
If you have a job request...
I only left a message.
If you ask later, then...
Did you meet Nana-chan?
Of course.
Mrs.?
Ah... yes
I need to lie down and rest a little
Mrs. would falls down before
your husband wakes up
But...
If no one is around when he wake up
Shota-kun would feel very lonely
She was holding your hand.
I can't hear anything.
Mr. Kuzumi, excuse me.
Did you take medicine properly?
Hey!
This is bad, Akane-san.
- Did you follow me?
- Yes.
Akane-san is easy to follow from behind.
- Go home.
- No, it's a crime.
It will be exciting scene in a book.
- If you write about trespassing...
- Because I am a non-fiction writer.
Stop... Good!
- Let me go!
- Be quiet.
Let me go...!
- Yes.
- It is a courier service.
- Please ~
“I'm on the sofa.
I want to hang out with you
"I have hope."
- It was for you.
- Ah... Yeah.
This is….
I wrote the name of a man named Takafumi Kono
Mr. Kono
- What is it?
- That's nothing.
No way... This is Kono's name tag...?
Forget that.
Oh this!
Creepy.
No! In the next play, as a high school student...
Isn't this an affair?
- Compensation calculation...
- Kimiko!
I will do it thoroughly.
First, leave this house now.
Please drown at the right time!
Oh...!
Then Kuroshima was angry.
Yes, I was so rude?
Yes, it's rude.
But that's it, right?
Having lunch with Kuroshima-chan.
- You didn't say anything, did you?
- No, why is that?
You can talk to me about love
And what we're not going to talk about
It's rude
I didn't talk about love.
Did you kiss?
- No. Nothing like that.
- Maybe at the festival?
- I will not!
- If you get so nervous
It's obvious. You really like her.
Hahahaha...!
Hit the nail on the head.
Ahaha... Tears came out...
- You're laughing too much.
- Yeah... ha ha ha ha...
Yup….
Ah... That...?
Sorry.
I have fun
It reminds me of Nana-chan right away.
Sorry...
Little by little from this room
Nana-chan's smell would disappear
I can't open the closet yet.
Nana's smell...
Ah…!
I'll fix it in no time!
Give me 1 year
Even though I told you I'd fix it.
Nana-chan, when did this happen?
♪ ~ We are the children of science
♪ ~ Today is everyone's experiment time ~
♪ ~ 12342234
♪ ~ We are the children of science
♪ ~ Together today...
Organic. Chemical fertilizers and pesticides
- Are not used at all.
- Hey...
It is free time ~.
I knew this would happen.
Did you eat, minions 2?
Kakinuma!
Would you like some corn?
Good waves will come in.
- Ahahaha...!
- No, It's scary.
- Yes, do yourbest.
- Then it's my turn.
Oh ~.
Hoh... hoh!
Yeah!
Oh, I'm good.
- Yes, congratulations!
- Thank you.
- Eh ~ Amazing!
- Yeah?
- Eh, Are you sure?
- This one
Doyan will take it.
Why don't you give it to her?
- Yes yes... Doyan's turn.
- Wait a minute...
Ah! It's time for me to replace the caller.
Sorry, I'm going.
I'll leave you two alone.
- Huh?
- Huh…?
Today I'm not going to talk about Yamagiwa.
Not as a suspect but as a mother.
- Do you have any concerns?
- How about So-chan?
- He wanted to tell his mother.
- Did you meet?
What is it? It's about science class.
I'm really excited to do the experiment.
Speaking of experiments, Soichi used to have them at school.
♪ ~ Science Child ~ Science Child ~!
♪ ~Today is everyone's experiment time!
♪ ~ 1234223...
♪ ~ Science Child ~ Science Child ~!
- There he is!
- Ahh….
- Hello.
Thank you for today.
Oh, your pocket money is in your bag
- If you want something, use it.
- Yes.
And then this is for Soichi.
Oh... I'm sorry.
- Let's go!
- Thank you.
- Have a good day ~
- Hahaha...
- You're good at ring throwing.
- No... it's just a fluke.
If it's a fluke, it's even more precious.
I'm glad...
- Ouch...
- Are you okay?
It's worn out...
I think I twisted it a little.
I'm sorry.
No….
How is my wife?
She's a little tired.
Well, she laughed after that,
so I think it's okay.
Something must have been triggered.
- Is it an “experiment”?
- Experiment?
Yes, it's a message from Soichi.
"Do my best in experiments" he said.
- Do my best?
- What is it?
- NO.
- That…. Kamiya….
- Catch Soichi.
- Yes?
It has to be stopped!
Arrest him!
- What was that sudden?
- Soichi is...
Soichi is...
He is not an ordinary child.
- Have you seen what I did.
- I was watching, but...
I saw you but no…
Wasshoi
I thought it was an accident
that happened while they were playing.
But all the children that were with them
said that was intentional.
When we confronted him...
- Experiment?
- Yes, it's an experiment
I wanted to see
When the dead die
In fact, there was a sign.
He killed the chicken.
- How about it?
- It's delicious!
Organic grilled corn!
You're doing great.
Thanks.
You're doing great too
and don't mess up.
- It's delicious!
- There are other
Repeated attacks on insects and stray cats.
My wife said, “At this rate
"He might do something to classmates again."
It's going crazy...
Ah...! Ahh…
What are you doing!
Stop it!
Kill So-chan then I will die too.
- Sanae!
- Impossible!
Mom could never do something like killing a man.
Between a crazy son and a crazy wife
I was still thinking about protecting myself.
If Soichi did something,
I would lose my promotion.
So I agreed on my wife's crazy proposal
We decided to keep Soichi away from the world.
But this plan broke down in no time.
- Ou
- Manager…
I heard a rumor that you kept a pet, so I came to see it.
No, no...!
That no... Nothing, nothing...!
- What's going on here?
- I'm sorry...!
Please! Don't open...
Oops... A large dog?
Haa…
He knew something was wrong.
She was asked for hush money.
While obeying it reluctantly
In the murder-swap game, my wife just wrote “Property Manager”
He was really killed...
Then she was forced to continue the game...
Please wait!
We're talking
about a very important thing... Eh?
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Um... I was suddenly called by Professor Hayakawa.
Ahh….
Is it okay? Do you want me to accompany you?
It's okay.
In other words, someone threaten with
the story of Soichi-kun...
So my wife drew the paper with Dr. Yamagiwa name.
- I'm sorry.
- What is it?
- I ran over a dog there.
- Even if I tell you...
You're a doctor, right?
- That appeared on TV…
- Ah...
I understand
Eh?
That was what my wife did alone.
When I noticed, I had to cooperate.
Even if you think the matter is over
This time she can't stand to bear her sins alone.
To increase the number of accomplices...
Uwa!
She started to threaten Fujii,
just like when she was threatened.
About the incident, it doesn't matter what you get
- And Soichi's involvement is….
- That...
To delay identification of Yamagiwa
That child went out without permission.
He's a child who can do anything even with a severed head!
- Contact the guardian immediately!
- Yes.
So-chan.
So-chan...
I hate experimenting alone...
Mom will experiment too...
Uhu... Huhuhu...!
Even if it's time they still haven't come back.
Yes, two people,
5 years old and a junior high school boy.
Uh….
What about you?
Oh... So, did you see Soichi?
No….
Yes, please.
I told the police.
The kids are gone.
The culprit commits murder in search of pleasure
How about Kuroshima-chan?
Ah, suddenly went to university...
We'll go manually search!
- Excuse me, please.
- Let's go.
Excuse me.
♪ ~ We are the children of science
♪ ~ Today is everyone's experiment time ~
♪ ~ 12342234
♪ ~ We 're the children of science, the children of science…
♪ ~ Today is everyone's experiment time!
- Sora!
- Isn't he with junior high school student?
Why are you so worried?
There is no time to explain to you!
That explained enough.
That...
If you choose a place where there are no people,
Here
Hurry up.
♪ ~ We are the children of science
♪ ~ Today is everyone's experiment time ~
Hey, if we don't go back soon, mom'll be angry.
- It's okay.
- But...
Because she won't see you again.
Huh?
U...
Uh... Uh...
Mrs. Enomoto!?
No, I can't contact Masako.
Ah!?
GO DIRECTLY NOW!!
Hey, calm down...
Hey! ARE YOU SO BORING!?
♪ ~ We are the children of science
♪ ~ Today is everyone's experiment time ~
What…!
- Uh... Uh!
- Uh...
Huh huh...
He seems to be okay for the time being.
Soon the train will be on Line 2.
Please stand outside of the yellow line.